const bookData = {
  "Level A Book 1": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 제이드야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jade.",
      "Scrambled": "Jade"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 제이드야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jade.",
      "Scrambled": "My / is / name / Jade"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 수지야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Suzie.",
      "Scrambled": "Suzie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 수지야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Suzie.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Suzie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 현주야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Hyunju.",
      "Scrambled": "Hyunju"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 현주야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Hyunju.",
      "Scrambled": "My / is / name / Hyunju"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 동인이야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Dongin.",
      "Scrambled": "Dongin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 동인이야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Dongin.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Dongin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 토니야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Tony.",
      "Scrambled": "Tony"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 토니야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Tony.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Tony"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 샐리야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Sally.",
      "Scrambled": "Sally"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 샐리야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Sally.",
      "Scrambled": "My / is / name / Sally"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 진호야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jinho.",
      "Scrambled": "Jinho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 진호야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jinho.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Jinho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 민지야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Minji.",
      "Scrambled": "Minji"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 민지야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Minji.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Minji"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 앤디야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Andy.",
      "Scrambled": "Andy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 앤디야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Andy.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Andy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What's your name?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 지민이야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jimin.",
      "Scrambled": "Jimin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "My name is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 이름은 지민이야",
      "English/Answer": "My name is Jimin.",
      "Scrambled": "My / name / is / Jimin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋아",
      "English/Answer": "I am fine.",
      "Scrambled": "fine"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋아",
      "English/Answer": "I am fine.",
      "Scrambled": "I / fine / am"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 배고파",
      "English/Answer": "I am hungry.",
      "Scrambled": "hungry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 배고파",
      "English/Answer": "I am hungry.",
      "Scrambled": "hungry / I / am"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바빠",
      "English/Answer": "I am busy.",
      "Scrambled": "busy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바빠",
      "English/Answer": "I am busy.",
      "Scrambled": "I / busy / am"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you a student?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 학생이야",
      "English/Answer": "I am a student.",
      "Scrambled": "a student"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 학생이야",
      "English/Answer": "I am a student.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / am / student"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 행복해",
      "English/Answer": "I am happy.",
      "Scrambled": "happy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 행복해",
      "English/Answer": "I am happy.",
      "Scrambled": "happy / I / am"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피곤해",
      "English/Answer": "I am tired.",
      "Scrambled": "tired"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피곤해",
      "English/Answer": "I am tired.",
      "Scrambled": "I / tired / am"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 졸려",
      "English/Answer": "I am sleepy.",
      "Scrambled": "sleepy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 졸려",
      "English/Answer": "I am sleepy.",
      "Scrambled": "I / am / sleepy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you a teacher?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 선생님이야",
      "English/Answer": "I am a teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "a teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 선생님이야",
      "English/Answer": "I am a teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / am / teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 기뻐",
      "English/Answer": "I am glad.",
      "Scrambled": "glad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 기뻐",
      "English/Answer": "I am glad.",
      "Scrambled": "glad / am / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How are you today?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 슬퍼",
      "English/Answer": "I’m sad.",
      "Scrambled": "sad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I am ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 슬퍼",
      "English/Answer": "I’m sad.",
      "Scrambled": "I / sad / m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 아홉 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m nine years old.",
      "Scrambled": "nine"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 아홉 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m nine years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / years / nine / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 여덟 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m eight years old.",
      "Scrambled": "eight"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 여덟 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m eight years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / years / eight / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m ten years old.",
      "Scrambled": "ten"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m ten years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / ten / years / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열다섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m fifteen years old.",
      "Scrambled": "fifteen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열다섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m fifteen years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / fifteen / years / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 여섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m six years old.",
      "Scrambled": "six"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 여섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m six years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / years / six / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열한 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m eleven years old.",
      "Scrambled": "eleven"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열한 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m eleven years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / years / eleven / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How old are you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 마흔 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m forty years old.",
      "Scrambled": "forty"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 마흔 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m forty years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / forty / years / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "How old is your teacher?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 마흔다섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m forty-five years old.",
      "Scrambled": "forty-five"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 마흔다섯 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m forty-five years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / forty-five / years / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How old is your brother?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열두 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m twelve years old.",
      "Scrambled": "twelve"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 열두 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m twelve years old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / twelve / years / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How old is your sister?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 한 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m one year old.",
      "Scrambled": "one"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m … years old.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 한 살이야",
      "English/Answer": "I’m one year old.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / one / year / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 한국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Korea.",
      "Scrambled": "Korea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 한국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Korea.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Korea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 프랑스에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from France.",
      "Scrambled": "France"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 프랑스에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from France.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / France"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 중국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from China.",
      "Scrambled": "China"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 중국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from China.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / China"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from America.",
      "Scrambled": "America"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from America.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / America"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 이탈리아에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Italy.",
      "Scrambled": "Italy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 이탈리아에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Italy.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Italy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 캐나다에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Canada.",
      "Scrambled": "Canada"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 캐나다에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Canada.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Canada"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 태국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Thailand.",
      "Scrambled": "Thailand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 태국에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Thailand.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Thailand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 일본에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from japan.",
      "Scrambled": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 일본에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from japan.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Japan"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 인도에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from India.",
      "Scrambled": "India"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 인도에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from India.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / India"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are you from?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 호주에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Australia.",
      "Scrambled": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m from ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 호주에서 왔어",
      "English/Answer": "I’m from Australia.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / from / Australia"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is he?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 젊어",
      "English/Answer": "He is young.",
      "Scrambled": "young"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 젊어",
      "English/Answer": "He is young.",
      "Scrambled": "is / young / He"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is she?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 똑똑해",
      "English/Answer": "She is smart.",
      "Scrambled": "smart"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 똑똑해",
      "English/Answer": "She is smart.",
      "Scrambled": "is / smart / She"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is he?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 아기야",
      "English/Answer": "He is a baby.",
      "Scrambled": "a baby"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 아기야",
      "English/Answer": "He is a baby.",
      "Scrambled": "He / is / a / baby"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is she?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 내 엄마야",
      "English/Answer": "She is my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "my mom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 내 엄마야",
      "English/Answer": "She is my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "She / is / my / mom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is he?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 귀여워",
      "English/Answer": "He is cute.",
      "Scrambled": "cute"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 귀여워",
      "English/Answer": "He is cute.",
      "Scrambled": "He / cute / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is she?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 키가 작아",
      "English/Answer": "She is short.",
      "Scrambled": "short"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 키가 작아",
      "English/Answer": "She is short.",
      "Scrambled": "is / short / She"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is he?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 친절해",
      "English/Answer": "He is kind.",
      "Scrambled": "kind"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 친절해",
      "English/Answer": "He is kind.",
      "Scrambled": "is / kind / He"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is she?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 나의 이모야",
      "English/Answer": "She is my aunt.",
      "Scrambled": "my aunt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 나의 이모야",
      "English/Answer": "She is my aunt.",
      "Scrambled": "She / is / my / aunt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is he?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 키가 커",
      "English/Answer": "She is tall.",
      "Scrambled": "tall"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 키가 커",
      "English/Answer": "She is tall.",
      "Scrambled": "tall / She / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "Who is she?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 강해",
      "English/Answer": "He is strong.",
      "Scrambled": "strong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "He/She is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 강해",
      "English/Answer": "He is strong.",
      "Scrambled": "strong / is / He"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 그림이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a picture.",
      "Scrambled": "a picture"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 그림이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a picture.",
      "Scrambled": "This / a / is / picture"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What is that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 부엉이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is an owl.",
      "Scrambled": "an owl"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 부엉이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is an owl.",
      "Scrambled": "That / is / an / owl"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "여기는 내 방이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is my room.",
      "Scrambled": "my room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "여기는 내 방이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is my room.",
      "Scrambled": "This / is / my / room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What is that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람은 사라야",
      "English/Answer": "That is Sarah.",
      "Scrambled": "is Sarah"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람은 사라야",
      "English/Answer": "That is Sarah.",
      "Scrambled": "is / Sarah / That"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 소나무야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a pine tree.",
      "Scrambled": "pine tree"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 소나무야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a pine tree.",
      "Scrambled": "This / a / is / pine / tree"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What is that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 내 책이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is my book.",
      "Scrambled": "my book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 내 책이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is my book.",
      "Scrambled": "That / is / my / book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람은 내 남동생이야.",
      "English/Answer": "This is my brother.",
      "Scrambled": "brother"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람은 내 남동생 민호야.",
      "English/Answer": "This is my brother, Minho.",
      "Scrambled": "This / my / brother / is / Minho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What is that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저기는 부엌이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is a kitchen.",
      "Scrambled": "a kitchen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저기는 부엌이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is a kitchen.",
      "Scrambled": "That / is / a / kitchen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 쓰레기통이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is a trash can.",
      "Scrambled": "trash can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 쓰레기통이야",
      "English/Answer": "That is a trash can.",
      "Scrambled": "That / trash / is / a / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What is that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "여기는 욕실이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a bathroom.",
      "Scrambled": "a bathroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "This/That is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "여기는 욕실이야",
      "English/Answer": "This is a bathroom.",
      "Scrambled": "This / is / a / bathroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 자니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your ruler?",
      "Scrambled": "your ruler"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 자니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your ruler?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / your / this / ruler"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 거위니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this a goose?",
      "Scrambled": "a goose"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 거위니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this a goose?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / a / this / goose"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "저기가 빵집이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that a bakery?",
      "Scrambled": "a bakery"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "저기가 빵집이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that a bakery?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / that / a / bakery"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "여기가 네 교실이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your classroom?",
      "Scrambled": "your classroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "여기가 네 교실이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your classroom?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / your / this / classroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 새 애완동물이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your new pet?",
      "Scrambled": "new pet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 새 애완동물이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your new pet?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / your / that / new / pet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이분이 네 삼촌이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your uncle?",
      "Scrambled": "your uncle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이분이 네 삼촌이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your uncle?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / your / this / uncle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 연필이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your pencil?",
      "Scrambled": "your pencil"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 연필이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your pencil?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / your / that / pencil"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람이 톰이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that Tom?",
      "Scrambled": "that Tom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람이 톰이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that Tom?",
      "Scrambled": "that / Tom / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 내 차례니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this my turn?",
      "Scrambled": "my turn"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 내 차례니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this my turn?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / my / this / turn"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "[Pattern 7]",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 염소니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this a goat?",
      "Scrambled": "a goat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this/that …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 염소니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this a goat?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / this / goat / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What are these?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 오렌지들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are oranges.",
      "Scrambled": "oranges"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 오렌지들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are oranges.",
      "Scrambled": "are / These / oranges"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What are those?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 내 양말들이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are my socks.",
      "Scrambled": "my socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 내 양말들이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are my socks.",
      "Scrambled": "Those / my / are / socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What are these?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람들은 내 친구들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are my friends.",
      "Scrambled": "my friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람들은 내 친구들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are my friends.",
      "Scrambled": "These / are / my / friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What are those?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 새 거야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are new.",
      "Scrambled": "new"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 새 거야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are new.",
      "Scrambled": "are / new / Those"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What are these?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 내 부츠들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are my boots.",
      "Scrambled": "my boots"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 내 부츠들이야",
      "English/Answer": "These are my boots.",
      "Scrambled": "These / are / my / boots"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are those?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저분들은 내 부모님이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are my parents.",
      "Scrambled": "my parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저분들은 내 부모님이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are my parents.",
      "Scrambled": "Those / my / are / parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are these?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 무거워",
      "English/Answer": "These are heavy.",
      "Scrambled": "heavy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 무거워",
      "English/Answer": "These are heavy.",
      "Scrambled": "These / heavy / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are those?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 낡았어",
      "English/Answer": "Those are old.",
      "Scrambled": "old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 낡았어",
      "English/Answer": "Those are old.",
      "Scrambled": "are / Those / old"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What are these?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 복숭아들이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are peaches.",
      "Scrambled": "peaches"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 복숭아들이야",
      "English/Answer": "Those are peaches.",
      "Scrambled": "peaches / Those / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are those?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 작아",
      "English/Answer": "Those are small.",
      "Scrambled": "small"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "These/Those are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 작아",
      "English/Answer": "Those are small.",
      "Scrambled": "small / are / Those"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Practice pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 레몬들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these lemons?",
      "Scrambled": "lemons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 레몬들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these lemons?",
      "Scrambled": "lemons / Are / these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Make sentence",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 진짜 꽃들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those real flowers?",
      "Scrambled": "real flowers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 진짜 꽃들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those real flowers?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / those / real / flowers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Use pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이분들은 네 부모님이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your parents?",
      "Scrambled": "your parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이분들은 네 부모님이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your parents?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / these / your / parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Try",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 신선하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those fresh?",
      "Scrambled": "fresh"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 신선하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those fresh?",
      "Scrambled": "fresh / those / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Can you answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 네 신발들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "your shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 네 신발들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / these / your / shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Give me example",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람들은 네 사촌들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those your cousins?",
      "Scrambled": "your cousins"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람들은 네 사촌들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those your cousins?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / those / your / cousins"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Your answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 깨끗하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these clean?",
      "Scrambled": "clean"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 깨끗하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these clean?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / clean / these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Tell me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those big?",
      "Scrambled": "big"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저것들은 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are those big?",
      "Scrambled": "big / Are / those"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Show me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 네 바지니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your pants?",
      "Scrambled": "your pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 네 바지니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these your pants?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / these / your / pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What about you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these small?",
      "Scrambled": "small"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "Are these/those …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these small?",
      "Scrambled": "small / these / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 탁자야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a table.",
      "Scrambled": "a table"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 탁자야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a table.",
      "Scrambled": "It / a / is / table"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What's that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 이구아나야",
      "English/Answer": "It is an iguana.",
      "Scrambled": "an iguana"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 이구아나야",
      "English/Answer": "It is an iguana.",
      "Scrambled": "It / an / is / iguana"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 갈색이야",
      "English/Answer": "It is brown.",
      "Scrambled": "is brown"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 갈색이야",
      "English/Answer": "It is brown.",
      "Scrambled": "It / brown / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What's that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 부드러워",
      "English/Answer": "It is soft.",
      "Scrambled": "is soft"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 부드러워",
      "English/Answer": "It is soft.",
      "Scrambled": "soft / It / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 지구본이야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a globe.",
      "Scrambled": "a globe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 지구본이야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a globe.",
      "Scrambled": "It / is / a / globe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What's that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 케이크야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a cake.",
      "Scrambled": "a cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 케이크야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a cake.",
      "Scrambled": "It / a / is / cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 둥글어",
      "English/Answer": "It is round.",
      "Scrambled": "is round"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 둥글어",
      "English/Answer": "It is round.",
      "Scrambled": "round / is / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What's that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 정말 맛있어",
      "English/Answer": "It is very delicious.",
      "Scrambled": "delicious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 정말 맛있어",
      "English/Answer": "It is very delicious.",
      "Scrambled": "It / very / is / delicious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What is this?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 사자야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a lion.",
      "Scrambled": "a lion"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 사자야",
      "English/Answer": "It is a lion.",
      "Scrambled": "It / a / is / lion"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What's that?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 무서워",
      "English/Answer": "It is scary.",
      "Scrambled": "scary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "It is ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 무서워",
      "English/Answer": "It is scary.",
      "Scrambled": "is / It / scary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "해가 쨍쨍한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s sunny.",
      "Scrambled": "sunny"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "해가 쨍쨍한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s sunny.",
      "Scrambled": "sunny / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "구름 낀 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cloudy.",
      "Scrambled": "cloudy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "구름 낀 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cloudy.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / cloudy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "비 오는 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s rainy.",
      "Scrambled": "rainy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "비 오는 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s rainy.",
      "Scrambled": "rainy / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "더운 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s hot.",
      "Scrambled": "hot"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "더운 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s hot.",
      "Scrambled": "hot / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "추운 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cold.",
      "Scrambled": "cold"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "추운 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cold.",
      "Scrambled": "cold / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "따뜻한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s warm.",
      "Scrambled": "warm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "따뜻한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s warm.",
      "Scrambled": "warm / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "서늘한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cool.",
      "Scrambled": "cool"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "서늘한 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s cool.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / cool"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "바람이 부는 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s windy.",
      "Scrambled": "windy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "바람이 부는 날씨야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s windy.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / windy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "날씨가 맑아",
      "English/Answer": "It’s clear.",
      "Scrambled": "clear"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "날씨가 맑아",
      "English/Answer": "It’s clear.",
      "Scrambled": "clear / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How's the weather?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "눈이 와",
      "English/Answer": "It’s snowing.",
      "Scrambled": "snowing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "눈이 와",
      "English/Answer": "It’s snowing.",
      "Scrambled": "snowing / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 컵이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a cup.",
      "Scrambled": "a cup"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 컵이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a cup.",
      "Scrambled": "I / have / a / cup"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종이가 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have paper.",
      "Scrambled": "paper"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종이가 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have paper.",
      "Scrambled": "have / I / paper"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 긴 목을 갖고 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a long neck.",
      "Scrambled": "long neck"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 긴 목을 갖고 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a long neck.",
      "Scrambled": "I / long / have / a / neck"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 두 명의 남동생들이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have two brothers.",
      "Scrambled": "two brothers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 두 명의 남동생들이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have two brothers.",
      "Scrambled": "I / have / two / brothers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 크레용들이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have crayons.",
      "Scrambled": "crayons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 크레용들이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have crayons.",
      "Scrambled": "crayons / have / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 질문이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a question.",
      "Scrambled": "a question"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 질문이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a question.",
      "Scrambled": "I / have / a / question"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 갈색 머리카락을 갖고 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have brown hair.",
      "Scrambled": "brown hair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 갈색 머리카락을 갖고 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have brown hair.",
      "Scrambled": "I / have / brown / hair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 형과 여동생이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a brother and a sister.",
      "Scrambled": "a sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 형과 여동생이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a brother and a sister.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / and / a / brother / have / sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 풀이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have glue.",
      "Scrambled": "glue"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 풀이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have glue.",
      "Scrambled": "glue / have / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you have?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피아노 수업이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a piano lesson.",
      "Scrambled": "piano lesson"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I have ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피아노 수업이 있어",
      "English/Answer": "I have a piano lesson.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / piano / have / lesson"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 고기를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like meat.",
      "Scrambled": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 고기를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like meat.",
      "Scrambled": "meat / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 햄스터를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like hamsters.",
      "Scrambled": "hamsters"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 햄스터를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like hamsters.",
      "Scrambled": "I / like / hamsters"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 겨울을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like winter.",
      "Scrambled": "winter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 겨울을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like winter.",
      "Scrambled": "like / I / winter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 수영을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like swimming.",
      "Scrambled": "swimming"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 수영을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like swimming.",
      "Scrambled": "like / I / swimming"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 아이스크림을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "ice cream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 아이스크림을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "I / like / ice cream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 영어를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like English.",
      "Scrambled": "English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 영어를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like English.",
      "Scrambled": "English / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 체리를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like cherries.",
      "Scrambled": "cherries"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 체리를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like cherries.",
      "Scrambled": "like / I / cherries"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 테니스와 축구를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like tennis and soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "tennis and soccer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 테니스와 축구를 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like tennis and soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "I / like / and / tennis / soccer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 생선을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like fish.",
      "Scrambled": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 생선을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like fish.",
      "Scrambled": "fish / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 달걀을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like eggs.",
      "Scrambled": "eggs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "I like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 달걀을 좋아해",
      "English/Answer": "I like eggs.",
      "Scrambled": "eggs / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 인형을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a doll.",
      "Scrambled": "a doll"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 인형을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a doll.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / want / doll"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우산을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want an umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "an umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우산을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want an umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / an / umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 물을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some water.",
      "Scrambled": "some water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 물을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some water.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / some / water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 휴대 전화를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a new cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "cell phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 휴대 전화를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a new cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / want / new / cell / phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 이 셔츠를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want this shirt.",
      "Scrambled": "shirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 이 셔츠를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want this shirt.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / this / shirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 사전을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a good dictionary.",
      "Scrambled": "good dictionary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 사전을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a good dictionary.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / a / good / dictionary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 케이크를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some cake.",
      "Scrambled": "some cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 케이크를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some cake.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / some / cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 코트를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a nice coat.",
      "Scrambled": "nice coat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 코트를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want a nice coat.",
      "Scrambled": "I / nice / a / want / coat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 저 재킷을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want that jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "that jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 저 재킷을 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want that jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "I / that / want / jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 주스를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some juice.",
      "Scrambled": "some juice"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "I want ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 주스를 원해",
      "English/Answer": "I want some juice.",
      "Scrambled": "I / want / some / juice"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "May I help you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 공책이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need a notebook.",
      "Scrambled": "a notebook"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 공책이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need a notebook.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / a / notebook"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you need?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 가위가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need scissors.",
      "Scrambled": "scissors"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 가위가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need scissors.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / scissors"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "May I help you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 돈이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need some money.",
      "Scrambled": "some money"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 돈이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need some money.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / some / money"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you need?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 옷이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need nice clothes.",
      "Scrambled": "nice clothes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 좋은 옷이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need nice clothes.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / nice / clothes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "May I help you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 그 지도가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need the map.",
      "Scrambled": "the map"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 그 지도가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need the map.",
      "Scrambled": "I / the / need / map"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you need?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 색연필들이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need colored pencils.",
      "Scrambled": "colored pencils"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 색연필들이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need colored pencils.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / colored / pencils"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "May I help you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 신발이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need new shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "new shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 신발이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need new shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "I / new / need / shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you need?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 밀가루가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need some flour.",
      "Scrambled": "some flour"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 약간의 밀가루가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need some flour.",
      "Scrambled": "I / some / need / flour"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "May I help you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 접시가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need a dish.",
      "Scrambled": "a dish"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 접시가 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need a dish.",
      "Scrambled": "I / need / a / dish"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you need?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 친구들이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need new friends.",
      "Scrambled": "new friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "I need ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 친구들이 필요해",
      "English/Answer": "I need new friends.",
      "Scrambled": "I / new / need / friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Practice pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 여동생이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a sister?",
      "Scrambled": "a sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 여동생이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a sister?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / have / you / a / sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Make sentence",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 레몬을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like lemons?",
      "Scrambled": "like lemons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 레몬을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like lemons?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / like / you / lemons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Use pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 약간의 치킨를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want some chicken?",
      "Scrambled": "some chicken"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 약간의 치킨를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want some chicken?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / some / you / want / chicken"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Try",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 색연필들이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you need colored pencils?",
      "Scrambled": "colored pencils"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 색연필들이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you need colored pencils?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / need / you / colored / pencils"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Can you answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 컴퓨터를 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a computer?",
      "Scrambled": "a computer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 컴퓨터를 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a computer?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / you / a / have / computer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Give me example",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 수학을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like math?",
      "Scrambled": "like math"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 수학을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like math?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / you / like / math"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Your answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 약간의 간식을 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want some snacks?",
      "Scrambled": "some snacks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 약간의 간식을 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want some snacks?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / you / want / some / snacks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Tell me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 큰 가방이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you need a big bag?",
      "Scrambled": "big bag"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 큰 가방이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you need a big bag?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / you / need / a / big / bag"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Show me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자전거를 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "a bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자전거를 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you have a bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / have / a / you / bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What about you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 영화를 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like movies?",
      "Scrambled": "like movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 영화를 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like movies?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / you / like / movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What sport do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 축구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "play soccer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 축구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "soccer / I / play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What instruments do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 농구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "play basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 농구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "I / play / basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What sport do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피아노를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the piano.",
      "Scrambled": "the piano"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 피아노를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the piano.",
      "Scrambled": "I / play / the / piano"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What instruments do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바이올린을 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the violin.",
      "Scrambled": "the violin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바이올린을 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the violin.",
      "Scrambled": "I / the / play / violin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What sport do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 야구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play baseball.",
      "Scrambled": "play baseball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 야구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play baseball.",
      "Scrambled": "I / play / baseball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What instruments do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 골프를 쳐",
      "English/Answer": "I play golf.",
      "Scrambled": "play golf"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 골프를 쳐",
      "English/Answer": "I play golf.",
      "Scrambled": "I / golf / play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What sport do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 첼로를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the cello.",
      "Scrambled": "the cello"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 첼로를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the cello.",
      "Scrambled": "I / play / the / cello"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What instruments do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 기타를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the guitar.",
      "Scrambled": "the guitar"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 기타를 연주해",
      "English/Answer": "I play the guitar.",
      "Scrambled": "I / the / play / guitar"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What sport do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 테니스를 쳐",
      "English/Answer": "I play tennis.",
      "Scrambled": "play tennis"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 테니스를 쳐",
      "English/Answer": "I play tennis.",
      "Scrambled": "play / tennis / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What instruments do you play?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 배구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play volleyball.",
      "Scrambled": "play volleyball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I play ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 배구를 해",
      "English/Answer": "I play volleyball.",
      "Scrambled": "play / I / volleyball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스웨터를 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a sweater.",
      "Scrambled": "a sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스웨터를 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a sweater.",
      "Scrambled": "I / wear / a / sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 모자를 써",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a hat.",
      "Scrambled": "a hat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 모자를 써",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a hat.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / wear / hat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 벙어리장갑을 껴",
      "English/Answer": "I wear mittens.",
      "Scrambled": "wear mittens"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 벙어리장갑을 껴",
      "English/Answer": "I wear mittens.",
      "Scrambled": "mittens / I / wear"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 부츠를 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear boots.",
      "Scrambled": "wear boots"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 부츠를 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear boots.",
      "Scrambled": "wear / boots / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 재킷을 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "a jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 재킷을 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear a jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "I / a / wear / jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바지를 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear pants.",
      "Scrambled": "wear pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 바지를 입어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear pants.",
      "Scrambled": "I / pants / wear"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 선글라스를 써",
      "English/Answer": "I wear sunglasses.",
      "Scrambled": "wear sunglasses"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 선글라스를 써",
      "English/Answer": "I wear sunglasses.",
      "Scrambled": "I / wear / sunglasses"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 신발을 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear new shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "new shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 새 신발을 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear new shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "I / wear / new / shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 안경을 껴",
      "English/Answer": "I wear glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "wear glasses"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 안경을 껴",
      "English/Answer": "I wear glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "wear / glasses / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you wear?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 양말을 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear socks.",
      "Scrambled": "wear socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I wear ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 양말을 신어",
      "English/Answer": "I wear socks.",
      "Scrambled": "wear / socks / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How is your food?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 좋은 맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes good.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes good"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 좋은 맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes good.",
      "Scrambled": "It / good / tastes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How does it taste?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 맛있는 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells delicious.",
      "Scrambled": "smells delicious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 맛있는 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells delicious.",
      "Scrambled": "smells / It / delicious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How is your food?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 쓴맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes bitter.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes bitter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 쓴맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes bitter.",
      "Scrambled": "bitter / tastes / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "How does it taste?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 나쁜 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells bad.",
      "Scrambled": "smells bad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 나쁜 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells bad.",
      "Scrambled": "bad / smells / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How is your food?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 짠맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes salty.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes salty"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 짠맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes salty.",
      "Scrambled": "salty / tastes / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How does it taste?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 달콤한 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells sweet.",
      "Scrambled": "smells sweet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 달콤한 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells sweet.",
      "Scrambled": "sweet / It / smells"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How is your food?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 신맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes sour.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes sour"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 신맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes sour.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes / sour / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "How does it taste?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 매운 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells spicy.",
      "Scrambled": "smells spicy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 매운 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells spicy.",
      "Scrambled": "smells / It / spicy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How is your food?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 신선한 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells fresh.",
      "Scrambled": "smells fresh"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 신선한 냄새가 나",
      "English/Answer": "It smells fresh.",
      "Scrambled": "fresh / It / smells"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How does it taste?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 꽤 좋은 맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes pretty good.",
      "Scrambled": "pretty good"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "It tastes/smells ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 꽤 좋은 맛이 나",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes pretty good.",
      "Scrambled": "It / pretty / tastes / good"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Practice pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go.",
      "Scrambled": "to go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / time / to / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Make sentence",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "공부할 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to study.",
      "Scrambled": "to study"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "공부할 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to study.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / to / time / study"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Use pattern",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "잠잘 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to sleep.",
      "Scrambled": "to sleep"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "잠잘 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to sleep.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / to / time / sleep"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Try",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "점심 먹을 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to eat lunch.",
      "Scrambled": "eat lunch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "점심 먹을 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to eat lunch.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / time / to / eat / lunch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Can you answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "휴식을 취할 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to begin.",
      "Scrambled": "to begin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "휴식을 취할 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to begin.",
      "Scrambled": "It's 's / time / to / begin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Give me example",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "집에 갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go home.",
      "Scrambled": "go home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "집에 갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go home.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / to / time / go / home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Your answer?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "일어날 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to get up.",
      "Scrambled": "get up"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "일어날 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to get up.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / to / time / get / up"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Tell me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "학교 갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go to school.",
      "Scrambled": "to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "학교 갈 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go to school.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / time / to / to / go / school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Show me",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "떠날 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to leave.",
      "Scrambled": "to leave"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "떠날 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to leave.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / time / to / leave"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What about you?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "잠자리에 들 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go to bed.",
      "Scrambled": "to bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s time to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "잠자리에 들 시간이야",
      "English/Answer": "It’s time to go to bed.",
      "Scrambled": "It's / to / time / to / go / bed"
    }
  ],
  "Level A Book 2": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 가방은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 가방은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is my bag?",
      "Scrambled": "my bag"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 가방은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is my bag?",
      "Scrambled": "bag / is / my / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "쇼핑몰은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "쇼핑몰은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the mall?",
      "Scrambled": "the mall"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "쇼핑몰은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the mall?",
      "Scrambled": "mall / is / Where / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 체육관은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 체육관은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is your gym?",
      "Scrambled": "your gym"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 체육관은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is your gym?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Where / gym / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "버스 정류장은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "버스 정류장은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the bus stop?",
      "Scrambled": "the bus stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "버스 정류장은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the bus stop?",
      "Scrambled": "stop / the / is / Where / bus"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 양말들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 양말들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are my socks?",
      "Scrambled": "my socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 양말들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are my socks?",
      "Scrambled": "socks / Where / my / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 동물들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 동물들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are the animals?",
      "Scrambled": "the animals"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 동물들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are the animals?",
      "Scrambled": "are / animals / Where / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내 장갑들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내 장갑들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are my gloves?",
      "Scrambled": "my gloves"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내 장갑들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are my gloves?",
      "Scrambled": "are / gloves / my / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 친구들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 친구들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are your friends?",
      "Scrambled": "your friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 친구들은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where are your friends?",
      "Scrambled": "friends / are / Where / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is he?",
      "Scrambled": "he"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is he?",
      "Scrambled": "he / is / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "출입문은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "출입문은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the gate?",
      "Scrambled": "the gate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Where is/are ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "출입문은 어디에 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where is the gate?",
      "Scrambled": "Where / is / gate / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 옷장 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the closet.",
      "Scrambled": "in the closet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 옷장 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the closet.",
      "Scrambled": "the / It’s / in / closet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 테이블 위에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s on the table.",
      "Scrambled": "on the table"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 테이블 위에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s on the table.",
      "Scrambled": "table / It’s / on / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 침대 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s under the bed.",
      "Scrambled": "under the bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 침대 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s under the bed.",
      "Scrambled": "It’s / bed / under / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 소파 옆에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s next to the sofa.",
      "Scrambled": "next to the sofa"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 소파 옆에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s next to the sofa.",
      "Scrambled": "next / sofa / to / the / It’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 서랍 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the drawer.",
      "Scrambled": "in the drawer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 서랍 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the drawer.",
      "Scrambled": "the / drawer / in / It’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 바닥 위에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s on the floor.",
      "Scrambled": "on the floor"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 바닥 위에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s on the floor.",
      "Scrambled": "floor / the / on / It’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 의자 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s under the chair.",
      "Scrambled": "under the chair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 의자 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s under the chair.",
      "Scrambled": "under / chair / It’s / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 책상 옆에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s next to the desk.",
      "Scrambled": "next to the desk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 책상 옆에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s next to the desk.",
      "Scrambled": "desk / next / It’s / the / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Where is it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 새장 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the cage.",
      "Scrambled": "in the cage"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 새장 안에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "It’s in the cage.",
      "Scrambled": "It’s / cage / in / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "Where are they?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것들은 나무 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "They’re under the tree.",
      "Scrambled": "under the tree"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "It’s in [on, under, next to] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것들은 나무 아래에 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "They’re under the tree.",
      "Scrambled": "They’re / the / tree / under"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "문을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "문을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the door.",
      "Scrambled": "the door"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "문을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the door.",
      "Scrambled": "Open / door / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "커튼들을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "커튼들을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the curtains.",
      "Scrambled": "the curtains"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "커튼들을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the curtains.",
      "Scrambled": "curtains / Close / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 벌려.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 벌려.",
      "English/Answer": "Open your mouth.",
      "Scrambled": "your mouth"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 벌려.",
      "English/Answer": "Open your mouth.",
      "Scrambled": "mouth / Open / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 눈들을 감아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 눈들을 감아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close your eyes.",
      "Scrambled": "your eyes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 눈들을 감아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close your eyes.",
      "Scrambled": "eyes / your / Close"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "상자를 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "상자를 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the box.",
      "Scrambled": "the box"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "상자를 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the box.",
      "Scrambled": "box / Open / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the window.",
      "Scrambled": "the window"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the window.",
      "Scrambled": "Close / window / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 책을 펴.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 책을 펴.",
      "English/Answer": "Open your book.",
      "Scrambled": "your book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 책을 펴.",
      "English/Answer": "Open your book.",
      "Scrambled": "book / Open / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 우산을 접어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 우산을 접어.",
      "English/Answer": "Close your umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "your umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 우산을 접어.",
      "English/Answer": "Close your umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "your / umbrella / Close"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the gift.",
      "Scrambled": "the gift"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 열어.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the gift.",
      "Scrambled": "the / gift / Open"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "병을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "병을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the bottle.",
      "Scrambled": "the bottle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Open .... / [Close ….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "병을 닫아.",
      "English/Answer": "Close the bottle.",
      "Scrambled": "Close / bottle / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 머리를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 머리를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your head.",
      "Scrambled": "your head"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 머리를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your head.",
      "Scrambled": "your / Touch / head"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your neck.",
      "Scrambled": "your neck"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your neck.",
      "Scrambled": "neck / Touch / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 귀들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 귀들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your ears.",
      "Scrambled": "your ears"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 귀들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your ears.",
      "Scrambled": "ears / Touch / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 다리들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 다리들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your legs.",
      "Scrambled": "your legs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 다리들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your legs.",
      "Scrambled": "legs / your / Touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your nose.",
      "Scrambled": "your nose"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코를 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your nose.",
      "Scrambled": "nose / Touch / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 팔을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 팔을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your arm.",
      "Scrambled": "your arm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 팔을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your arm.",
      "Scrambled": "your / arm / Touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 어깨들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 어깨들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your shoulders.",
      "Scrambled": "your shoulders"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 어깨들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your shoulders.",
      "Scrambled": "shoulders / Touch / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 발들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 발들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your feet.",
      "Scrambled": "your feet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 발들을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your feet.",
      "Scrambled": "your / feet / Touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your mouth.",
      "Scrambled": "your mouth"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 입을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your mouth.",
      "Scrambled": "mouth / your / Touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your hand.",
      "Scrambled": "your hand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Touch your ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 만져.",
      "English/Answer": "Touch your hand.",
      "Scrambled": "your / hand / Touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at me.",
      "Scrambled": "me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at me.",
      "Scrambled": "at / Look / me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "칠판을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "칠판을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the board.",
      "Scrambled": "the board"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "칠판을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the board.",
      "Scrambled": "the / board / at / Look"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "거울을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "거울을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the mirror.",
      "Scrambled": "the mirror"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "거울을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the mirror.",
      "Scrambled": "at / the / mirror / Look"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 사진을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 사진을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at your picture.",
      "Scrambled": "your picture"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 사진을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at your picture.",
      "Scrambled": "picture / Look / at / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at him.",
      "Scrambled": "him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at him.",
      "Scrambled": "at / him / Look"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 지도를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 지도를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at this map.",
      "Scrambled": "this map"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 지도를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at this map.",
      "Scrambled": "map / Look / this / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그의 차를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그의 차를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at his car.",
      "Scrambled": "his car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그의 차를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at his car.",
      "Scrambled": "car / at / his / Look"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the birds.",
      "Scrambled": "the birds"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the birds.",
      "Scrambled": "Look / birds / the / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 호랑이를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 호랑이를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the tiger.",
      "Scrambled": "the tiger"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 호랑이를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the tiger.",
      "Scrambled": "Look / tiger / the / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "아름다운 꽃들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "아름다운 꽃들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the beautiful flowers.",
      "Scrambled": "the beautiful flowers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Look at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "아름다운 꽃들을 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Look at the beautiful flowers.",
      "Scrambled": "beautiful / the / at / Look / flowers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코트를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코트를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your coat.",
      "Scrambled": "your coat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네 코트를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your coat.",
      "Scrambled": "your / Put / on / coat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "your jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "off / your / Take / jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 모자를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 모자를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your hat.",
      "Scrambled": "your hat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 모자를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your hat.",
      "Scrambled": "your / on / Put / hat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 양말을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 양말을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your socks.",
      "Scrambled": "your socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 양말을 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your socks.",
      "Scrambled": "your / off / socks / Take"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 치마를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 치마를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on this skirt.",
      "Scrambled": "this skirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 치마를 입어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on this skirt.",
      "Scrambled": "skirt / Put / on / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스웨터를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스웨터를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your sweater.",
      "Scrambled": "your sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스웨터를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your sweater.",
      "Scrambled": "off / Take / sweater / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발들을 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발들을 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on these shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "these shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발들을 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on these shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "these / on / Put / shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 바지를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 바지를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your pants.",
      "Scrambled": "your pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 바지를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your pants.",
      "Scrambled": "Take / your / pants / off"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장화를 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장화를 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your rain boots.",
      "Scrambled": "your rain boots"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장화를 신어.",
      "English/Answer": "Put on your rain boots.",
      "Scrambled": "on / rain / your / Put / boots"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목도리를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목도리를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your muffler.",
      "Scrambled": "your muffler"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "Put on …. [Take off….]",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 목도리를 벗어.",
      "English/Answer": "Take off your muffler.",
      "Scrambled": "Take / muffler / your / off"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "일어서 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "일어서 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Stand up, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Stand up"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "일어서 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Stand up, please.",
      "Scrambled": "up / Stand / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "바닥을 청소해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "바닥을 청소해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Clean the floor, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Clean the floor"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "바닥을 청소해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Clean the floor, please.",
      "Scrambled": "floor / Clean / the / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 열어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 열어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the window, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Open the window"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "창문을 열어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Open the window, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Open / window / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "불을 꺼 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "불을 꺼 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Turn out the light, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Turn out the light"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "불을 꺼 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Turn out the light, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Turn / out / light / the / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "앉아 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "앉아 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Sit down, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Sit down"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "앉아 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Sit down, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Sit / please / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 도와줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 도와줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Help me, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Help me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 도와줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Help me, please.",
      "Scrambled": "me / Help / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "조용히 해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "조용히 해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Be quiet, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Be quiet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "조용히 해 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Be quiet, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Be / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Raise your hand, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Raise your hand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 손을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Raise your hand, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Raise / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "여기로 와 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "여기로 와 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Come here, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Come here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "여기로 와 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Come here, please.",
      "Scrambled": "here / Come / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 말을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 말을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Listen to me, please.",
      "Scrambled": "Listen to me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "…, please.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 말을 들어 줘.",
      "English/Answer": "Listen to me, please.",
      "Scrambled": "to / me / Listen / "
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "가자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "가자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s go.",
      "Scrambled": "go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "가자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s go.",
      "Scrambled": "Let’s / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "TV를 보자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "TV를 보자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s watch TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watch TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "TV를 보자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s watch TV.",
      "Scrambled": "Let’s / TV / watch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "함께 공부하자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "함께 공부하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s study together.",
      "Scrambled": "study together"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "함께 공부하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s study together.",
      "Scrambled": "study / Let’s / together"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "눈사람을 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "눈사람을 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s build a snowman.",
      "Scrambled": "build a snowman"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "눈사람을 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s build a snowman.",
      "Scrambled": "a / snowman / build / Let’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "역할놀이를 하자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "역할놀이를 하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s role-play.",
      "Scrambled": "role-play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "역할놀이를 하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s role-play.",
      "Scrambled": "Let’s / role-play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "케이크를 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "케이크를 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s make a cake.",
      "Scrambled": "make a cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "케이크를 만들자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s make a cake.",
      "Scrambled": "cake / make / a / Let’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 사자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 사자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s buy a gift.",
      "Scrambled": "buy a gift"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "선물을 사자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s buy a gift.",
      "Scrambled": "gift / buy / a / Let’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "샌드위치를 좀 주문하자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "샌드위치를 좀 주문하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s order some sandwiches.",
      "Scrambled": "order some sandwiches"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "샌드위치를 좀 주문하자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s order some sandwiches.",
      "Scrambled": "sandwiches / Let’s / some / order"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "2시에 만나자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "2시에 만나자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s meet at two.",
      "Scrambled": "meet at two"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "2시에 만나자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s meet at two.",
      "Scrambled": "Let’s / at / meet / two"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "핫도그를 먹자.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "핫도그를 먹자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s eat hot dogs.",
      "Scrambled": "eat hot dogs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "Let's ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "핫도그를 먹자.",
      "English/Answer": "Let’s eat hot dogs.",
      "Scrambled": "dogs / hot / eat / Let’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 학교에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to school.",
      "Scrambled": "school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 학교에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to school.",
      "Scrambled": "went / I / school / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 체육관에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the gym.",
      "Scrambled": "the gym"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 체육관에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the gym.",
      "Scrambled": "went / gym / the / I / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 병원에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the hospital.",
      "Scrambled": "the hospital"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 병원에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the hospital.",
      "Scrambled": "hospital / the / went / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 샘의 집에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to Sam’s house.",
      "Scrambled": "Sam’s house"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 샘의 집에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to Sam’s house.",
      "Scrambled": "Sam’s / went / I / to / house"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 공항에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the airport.",
      "Scrambled": "the airport"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 공항에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the airport.",
      "Scrambled": "to / went / the / airport / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 극장에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the movie theater.",
      "Scrambled": "the movie theater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 극장에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the movie theater.",
      "Scrambled": "movie / the / theater / I / to / went"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미용실에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the hair salon.",
      "Scrambled": "the hair salon"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미용실에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the hair salon.",
      "Scrambled": "the / to / went / salon / I / hair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 백화점에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the department store.",
      "Scrambled": "the department store"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 백화점에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the department store.",
      "Scrambled": "department / I / went / to / store / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미국에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to America.",
      "Scrambled": "America"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 미국에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to America.",
      "Scrambled": "went / America / I / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "Where did you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 서점에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the bookstore.",
      "Scrambled": "the bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "I went to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 서점에 갔어.",
      "English/Answer": "I went to the bookstore.",
      "Scrambled": "I / went / the / bookstore / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 쇼핑을 할 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will shop.",
      "Scrambled": "shop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 쇼핑을 할 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will shop.",
      "Scrambled": "shop / will / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 앤을 만날 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will meet Ann.",
      "Scrambled": "meet Ann"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 앤을 만날 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will meet Ann.",
      "Scrambled": "Ann / will / meet / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스키를 타러 갈 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will go skiing.",
      "Scrambled": "go skiing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스키를 타러 갈 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will go skiing.",
      "Scrambled": "skiing / go / will / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 프렌치토스트를 먹을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will eat French toast.",
      "Scrambled": "eat French toast"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 프렌치토스트를 먹을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will eat French toast.",
      "Scrambled": "eat / will / French / toast / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 교실을 청소할 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will clean the classroom.",
      "Scrambled": "clean the classroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 교실을 청소할 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will clean the classroom.",
      "Scrambled": "will / clean / classroom / the / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나의 선생님을 도울 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will help my teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "help my teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나의 선생님을 도울 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will help my teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "teacher / help / I / my / will"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우표들을 모을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will collect stamps.",
      "Scrambled": "collect stamps"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우표들을 모을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will collect stamps.",
      "Scrambled": "stamps / will / I / collect"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 전등을 끌 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will turn off the light.",
      "Scrambled": "turn off the light"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 전등을 끌 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will turn off the light.",
      "Scrambled": "I / the / will / off / light / turn"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스파게티를 먹을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will have spaghetti.",
      "Scrambled": "have spaghetti"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스파게티를 먹을 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I will have spaghetti.",
      "Scrambled": "will / I / spaghetti / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What will you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 무용수가 될 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I’ll be a dancer.",
      "Scrambled": "be a dancer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I will ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 무용수가 될 거야.",
      "English/Answer": "I’ll be a dancer.",
      "Scrambled": "I’ll / be / a / dancer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 TV를 보고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watching TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 TV를 보고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "I’m / TV / watching"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What is he doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 책을 읽고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m reading a book.",
      "Scrambled": "reading a book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 책을 읽고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m reading a book.",
      "Scrambled": "reading / a / book / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is your mom doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나의 엄마를 돕고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m helping my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "helping my mom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나의 엄마를 돕고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m helping my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "mom / my / helping / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 너에게 이야기하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m talking to you.",
      "Scrambled": "talking to you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 너에게 이야기하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m talking to you.",
      "Scrambled": "you / I’m / to / talking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What is your dad doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 영어를 공부하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m studying English.",
      "Scrambled": "studying English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 영어를 공부하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m studying English.",
      "Scrambled": "English / studying / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 설거지를 하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m doing the dishes.",
      "Scrambled": "doing the dishes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 설거지를 하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m doing the dishes.",
      "Scrambled": "doing / dishes / the / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 산책하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m taking a walk.",
      "Scrambled": "taking a walk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 산책하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m taking a walk.",
      "Scrambled": "walk / I’m / taking / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 방을 청소하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m cleaning the room.",
      "Scrambled": "cleaning the room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 방을 청소하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m cleaning the room.",
      "Scrambled": "room / cleaning / the / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 가고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m going.",
      "Scrambled": "going"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 가고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m going.",
      "Scrambled": "I’m / going"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 저녁을 먹고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m having dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "having dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 저녁을 먹고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m having dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "having / dinner / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you listening?",
      "Scrambled": "listening"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you listening?",
      "Scrambled": "you / listening / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 내 컴퓨터를 고치고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you fixing my computer?",
      "Scrambled": "fixing my computer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 내 컴퓨터를 고치고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you fixing my computer?",
      "Scrambled": "computer / you / fixing / my / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 이메일을 지우고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you deleting the email?",
      "Scrambled": "deleting the email"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 이메일을 지우고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you deleting the email?",
      "Scrambled": "email / you / the / deleting / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 네 시험공부를 하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you studying for your exam?",
      "Scrambled": "studying for your exam"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 네 시험공부를 하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you studying for your exam?",
      "Scrambled": "studying / you / your / exam / for / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 울고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you crying?",
      "Scrambled": "crying"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 울고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you crying?",
      "Scrambled": "crying / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 재미있게 놀고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you having fun?",
      "Scrambled": "having fun"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 재미있게 놀고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you having fun?",
      "Scrambled": "having / you / fun / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 신문을 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you reading a newspaper?",
      "Scrambled": "reading a newspaper"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 신문을 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you reading a newspaper?",
      "Scrambled": "newspaper / reading / a / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 축구 경기를 보고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you watching a soccer game?",
      "Scrambled": "watching a soccer game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 축구 경기를 보고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you watching a soccer game?",
      "Scrambled": "game / Are / soccer / a / you / watching"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you sleeping?",
      "Scrambled": "sleeping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you sleeping?",
      "Scrambled": "sleeping / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "Are you doing it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 음악을 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you listening to music?",
      "Scrambled": "listening to music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 음악을 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you listening to music?",
      "Scrambled": "to / you / listening / music / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What is there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "펜이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a pen.",
      "Scrambled": "a pen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "펜이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a pen.",
      "Scrambled": "There / a / is / pen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What is there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "사과가 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is an apple.",
      "Scrambled": "an apple"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "사과가 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is an apple.",
      "Scrambled": "There / apple / an / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "아이스크림이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "ice cream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "아이스크림이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "cream / ice / is / There"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What is there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "강 속에 개구리가 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a frog in the river.",
      "Scrambled": "a frog in the river"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "강 속에 개구리가 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a frog in the river.",
      "Scrambled": "in / a / is / river / There / frog / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What are there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "의자들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are chairs.",
      "Scrambled": "chairs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "의자들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are chairs.",
      "Scrambled": "chairs / are / There"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "일곱 개의 샌드위치들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are seven sandwiches.",
      "Scrambled": "seven sandwiches"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "일곱 개의 샌드위치들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are seven sandwiches.",
      "Scrambled": "seven / are / There / sandwiches"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "약간의 딸기들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are some strawberries.",
      "Scrambled": "some strawberries"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "약간의 딸기들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are some strawberries.",
      "Scrambled": "strawberries / are / some / There"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "도로 위에 많은 차들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are many cars on the street.",
      "Scrambled": "many cars on the street"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "도로 위에 많은 차들이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are many cars on the street.",
      "Scrambled": "the / are / There / cars / street / on / many"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What is there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "박물관이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a museum.",
      "Scrambled": "a museum"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "박물관이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There is a museum.",
      "Scrambled": "museum / There / is / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are there?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "사계절이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are four seasons.",
      "Scrambled": "four seasons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "There is/are ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "사계절이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "There are four seasons.",
      "Scrambled": "There / four / seasons / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 컵들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 컵들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cups are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cups"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 컵들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cups are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cups / How / are / there / many"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 동물들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 동물들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many animals are there?",
      "Scrambled": "animals"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 동물들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many animals are there?",
      "Scrambled": "many / there / animals / How / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 쿠키들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 쿠키들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cookies are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cookies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 쿠키들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cookies are there?",
      "Scrambled": "are / How / there / cookies / many"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 학생들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 학생들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many students are there?",
      "Scrambled": "students"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 학생들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many students are there?",
      "Scrambled": "students / are / How / many / there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 케이크들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 케이크들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cakes are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cakes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 케이크들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cakes are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cakes / How / many / are / there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 접시들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 접시들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many plates are there?",
      "Scrambled": "plates"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 접시들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many plates are there?",
      "Scrambled": "there / How / many / plates / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 탄산음료들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 탄산음료들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many sodas are there?",
      "Scrambled": "sodas"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 탄산음료들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many sodas are there?",
      "Scrambled": "sodas / many / How / are / there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 풍선들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 풍선들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many balloons are there?",
      "Scrambled": "balloons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 풍선들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many balloons are there?",
      "Scrambled": "How / balloons / there / are / many"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 고양이들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 고양이들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cats are there?",
      "Scrambled": "cats"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 고양이들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many cats are there?",
      "Scrambled": "How / are / cats / many / there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 사람들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 사람들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many people are there?",
      "Scrambled": "people"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "How many ... are there?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "얼마나 많은 사람들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How many people are there?",
      "Scrambled": "there / people / How / many / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is it?",
      "Scrambled": "it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is it?",
      "Scrambled": "How / much / is / it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "티켓은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "티켓은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is a ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "a ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "티켓은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is a ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "ticket / How / much / is / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그 연필은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그 연필은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is the pencil?",
      "Scrambled": "the pencil"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그 연필은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is the pencil?",
      "Scrambled": "How / much / the / pencil / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this book?",
      "Scrambled": "this book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this book?",
      "Scrambled": "this / How / book / much / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저 시계는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저 시계는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that watch?",
      "Scrambled": "that watch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저 시계는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that watch?",
      "Scrambled": "that / watch / much / How / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 모자는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 모자는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this cap?",
      "Scrambled": "this cap"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 모자는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this cap?",
      "Scrambled": "How / much / cap / this / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 필통은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 필통은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is the pencil case?",
      "Scrambled": "the pencil case"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 필통은 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is the pencil case?",
      "Scrambled": "the / is / much / pencil / How / case"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 셔츠는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 셔츠는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that shirt?",
      "Scrambled": "that shirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 셔츠는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that shirt?",
      "Scrambled": "shirt / much / that / is / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 차는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 차는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this car?",
      "Scrambled": "this car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 차는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is this car?",
      "Scrambled": "is / this / How / much / car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저 케이크는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저 케이크는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that cake?",
      "Scrambled": "that cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "How much is ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저 케이크는 얼마니?",
      "English/Answer": "How much is that cake?",
      "Scrambled": "cake / much / that / How / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s this?",
      "Scrambled": "this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s this?",
      "Scrambled": "this / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 이름은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 이름은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your name?",
      "Scrambled": "your name"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네 이름은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your name?",
      "Scrambled": "What’s / name / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 취미는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 취미는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your hobby?",
      "Scrambled": "your hobby"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네 취미는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your hobby?",
      "Scrambled": "your / What’s / hobby"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날짜는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날짜는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the date today?",
      "Scrambled": "the date today"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날짜는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the date today?",
      "Scrambled": "today / What’s / the / date"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s that?",
      "Scrambled": "that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s that?",
      "Scrambled": "that / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "문제가 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "문제가 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the problem?",
      "Scrambled": "the problem"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "문제가 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the problem?",
      "Scrambled": "the / problem / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장기는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장기는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your talent?",
      "Scrambled": "your talent"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 장기는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your talent?",
      "Scrambled": "your / talent / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 꿈은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 꿈은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your dream?",
      "Scrambled": "your dream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 꿈은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your dream?",
      "Scrambled": "dream / your / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "정답이 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "정답이 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the answer?",
      "Scrambled": "the answer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "정답이 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s the answer?",
      "Scrambled": "the / What’s / answer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 직업은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 직업은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your job?",
      "Scrambled": "your job"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "What's ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 직업은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your job?",
      "Scrambled": "your / What’s / job"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 동물은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 동물은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite animal?",
      "Scrambled": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 동물은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite animal?",
      "Scrambled": "What’s / favorite / your / animal"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 운동은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 운동은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite sport?",
      "Scrambled": "sport"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 운동은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite sport?",
      "Scrambled": "your / What’s / sport / favorite"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 색깔은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 색깔은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite color?",
      "Scrambled": "color"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 색깔은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite color?",
      "Scrambled": "color / favorite / your / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과목은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과목은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite subject?",
      "Scrambled": "subject"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과목은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite subject?",
      "Scrambled": "subject / your / favorite / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 후식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 후식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "dessert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 후식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "What’s / favorite / dessert / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 도시는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 도시는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite city?",
      "Scrambled": "city"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 도시는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite city?",
      "Scrambled": "city / favorite / your / What’s"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 계절은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 계절은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite season?",
      "Scrambled": "season"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 계절은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite season?",
      "Scrambled": "What’s / your / season / favorite"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과일은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과일은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite fruit?",
      "Scrambled": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 과일은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite fruit?",
      "Scrambled": "favorite / fruit / What’s / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 음식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 음식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite food?",
      "Scrambled": "food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 음식은 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite food?",
      "Scrambled": "What’s / food / your / favorite"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 노래는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 노래는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite song?",
      "Scrambled": "song"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "What's your favorite ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 가장 좋아하는 노래는 뭐니?",
      "English/Answer": "What’s your favorite song?",
      "Scrambled": "song / What’s / your / favorite"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 달릴 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can run.",
      "Scrambled": "run"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 달릴 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can run.",
      "Scrambled": "run / I / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 노래할 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can sing.",
      "Scrambled": "sing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 노래할 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can sing.",
      "Scrambled": "can / sing / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 TV를 볼 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can watch TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watch TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 TV를 볼 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can watch TV.",
      "Scrambled": "I / can / TV / watch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 많이 먹을 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can eat a lot.",
      "Scrambled": "eat a lot"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 많이 먹을 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can eat a lot.",
      "Scrambled": "eat / I / a / lot / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 걸을 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can walk.",
      "Scrambled": "walk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 걸을 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can walk.",
      "Scrambled": "walk / I / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 그릴 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can draw.",
      "Scrambled": "draw"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 그릴 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can draw.",
      "Scrambled": "draw / I / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우유를 마실 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can drink milk.",
      "Scrambled": "drink milk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 우유를 마실 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can drink milk.",
      "Scrambled": "drink / I / can / milk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 수영을 아주 잘할 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can swim very well.",
      "Scrambled": "swim very well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 수영을 아주 잘할 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can swim very well.",
      "Scrambled": "well / very / I / swim / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나갈 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can go out.",
      "Scrambled": "go out"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 나갈 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can go out.",
      "Scrambled": "go / out / I / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What can you do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스키를 잘 탈 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can ski well.",
      "Scrambled": "ski well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "I can ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 스키를 잘 탈 수 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can ski well.",
      "Scrambled": "ski / I / can / well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 수영할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 수영할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you swim?",
      "Scrambled": "swim"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 수영할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you swim?",
      "Scrambled": "Can / you / swim"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 요리할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 요리할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you cook?",
      "Scrambled": "cook"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 요리할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you cook?",
      "Scrambled": "cook / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 춤출 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 춤출 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you dance?",
      "Scrambled": "dance"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 춤출 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you dance?",
      "Scrambled": "you / dance / Can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 영어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 영어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you speak English?",
      "Scrambled": "speak English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 영어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you speak English?",
      "Scrambled": "speak / you / Can / English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 노래할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 노래할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you sing?",
      "Scrambled": "sing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 노래할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you sing?",
      "Scrambled": "you / sing / Can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 피자를 만들 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 피자를 만들 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you make pizza?",
      "Scrambled": "make pizza"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 피자를 만들 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you make pizza?",
      "Scrambled": "pizza / make / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자전거를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자전거를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you ride a bike?",
      "Scrambled": "ride a bike"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 자전거를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you ride a bike?",
      "Scrambled": "ride / bike / a / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 기타를 칠 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 기타를 칠 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you play the guitar?",
      "Scrambled": "play the guitar"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 기타를 칠 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you play the guitar?",
      "Scrambled": "guitar / the / Can / you / play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 스케이트를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 스케이트를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you skate?",
      "Scrambled": "skate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 스케이트를 탈 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you skate?",
      "Scrambled": "you / skate / Can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 중국어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 중국어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you speak Chinese?",
      "Scrambled": "speak Chinese"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너는 중국어를 말할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you speak Chinese?",
      "Scrambled": "speak / Can / you / Chinese"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 낮잠을 자도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 낮잠을 자도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I take a nap?",
      "Scrambled": "take a nap"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 낮잠을 자도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I take a nap?",
      "Scrambled": "nap / take / I / Can / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 탁자를 치워도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 탁자를 치워도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I clear the table?",
      "Scrambled": "clear the table"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 탁자를 치워도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I clear the table?",
      "Scrambled": "Can / clear / the / table / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 케이크를 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 케이크를 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I have some cake?",
      "Scrambled": "have some cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 케이크를 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I have some cake?",
      "Scrambled": "some / cake / have / I / Can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 창문을 닫아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 창문을 닫아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I close the window?",
      "Scrambled": "close the window"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 창문을 닫아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I close the window?",
      "Scrambled": "window / Can / close / the / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 설거지를 해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 설거지를 해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I do the dishes?",
      "Scrambled": "do the dishes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 설거지를 해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I do the dishes?",
      "Scrambled": "dishes / Can / the / I / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 전등을 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 전등을 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I turn on the light?",
      "Scrambled": "turn on the light"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 전등을 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I turn on the light?",
      "Scrambled": "I / turn / Can / on / light / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 뭐 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 뭐 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I eat something?",
      "Scrambled": "eat something"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 뭐 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I eat something?",
      "Scrambled": "something / Can / I / eat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그걸 만져도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그걸 만져도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I touch it?",
      "Scrambled": "touch it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그걸 만져도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I touch it?",
      "Scrambled": "it / I / Can / touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 집에 가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 집에 가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I go home?",
      "Scrambled": "go home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 집에 가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I go home?",
      "Scrambled": "Can / home / I / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "sit here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Can I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Can I sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "here / I / sit / Can"
    }
  ],
  "Level B Book 1": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for him.",
      "Scrambled": "him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for him.",
      "Scrambled": "for / I'm / looking / him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 게임을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a game.",
      "Scrambled": "a game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 게임을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a game.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / a / I'm / for / game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바지를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for pants.",
      "Scrambled": "pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바지를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for pants.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / pants / I'm / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 지갑을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for my wallet.",
      "Scrambled": "my wallet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 지갑을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for my wallet.",
      "Scrambled": "wallet / I'm / my / looking / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 야채를 좀 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for some vegetables.",
      "Scrambled": "some vegetables"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 야채를 좀 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for some vegetables.",
      "Scrambled": "vegetables / I'm / some / looking / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 버스 정류장을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a bus stop.",
      "Scrambled": "a bus stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 버스 정류장을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a bus stop.",
      "Scrambled": "for / bus / looking / stop / I'm / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여자 화장실을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for the ladies' room.",
      "Scrambled": "the ladies' room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여자 화장실을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for the ladies' room.",
      "Scrambled": "ladies' / looking / room / I'm / for / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아빠를 위한 선물을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a present for my dad.",
      "Scrambled": "a present for my dad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아빠를 위한 선물을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a present for my dad.",
      "Scrambled": "dad / looking / present / for / my / a / I'm / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for her.",
      "Scrambled": "her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀를 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for her.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / her / for / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you looking for?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수영복을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a swimsuit.",
      "Scrambled": "a swimsuit"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking for ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수영복을 찾고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking for a swimsuit.",
      "Scrambled": "swimsuit / looking / I'm / a / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 농구를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 농구를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "basketball / good / I'm / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수학을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at math.",
      "Scrambled": "math"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수학을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at math.",
      "Scrambled": "at / math / good / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤을 잘 춰.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at dancing.",
      "Scrambled": "dancing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤을 잘 춰.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at dancing.",
      "Scrambled": "dancing / I'm / good / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 말하기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at speaking English.",
      "Scrambled": "speaking English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 말하기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at speaking English.",
      "Scrambled": "at / good / English / speaking / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 악기 연주를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at playing instruments.",
      "Scrambled": "playing instruments"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 악기 연주를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at playing instruments.",
      "Scrambled": "at / playing / good / instruments / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 운동을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at exercising.",
      "Scrambled": "exercising"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 운동을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at exercising.",
      "Scrambled": "exercising / I'm / good / at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 높이 뛰기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at jumping high.",
      "Scrambled": "jumping high"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 높이 뛰기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at jumping high.",
      "Scrambled": "at / jumping / high / good / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 일을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at doing my job.",
      "Scrambled": "doing my job"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 일을 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at doing my job.",
      "Scrambled": "good / I'm / doing / at / job / my"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 달리기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at running.",
      "Scrambled": "running"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 달리기를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at running.",
      "Scrambled": "good / running / at / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you good at?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 일본어를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at Japanese.",
      "Scrambled": "Japanese"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm good at ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 일본어를 잘해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm good at Japanese.",
      "Scrambled": "good / I'm / at / Japanese"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너에게 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in you.",
      "Scrambled": "you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너에게 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in you.",
      "Scrambled": "interested / you / in / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음악에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in music.",
      "Scrambled": "music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음악에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in music.",
      "Scrambled": "in / interested / music / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 글쓰기에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in writing.",
      "Scrambled": "writing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 글쓰기에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in writing.",
      "Scrambled": "writing / in / I’m / interested"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국 역사에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in Korean history.",
      "Scrambled": "Korean history"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국 역사에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in Korean history.",
      "Scrambled": "Korean / in / interested / I’m / history"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 컴퓨터 게임 하는 것에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in playing computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "playing computer games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 컴퓨터 게임 하는 것에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in playing computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "computer / interested / playing / games / in / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 패션에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in fashion.",
      "Scrambled": "fashion"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 패션에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in fashion.",
      "Scrambled": "in / I’m / interested / fashion"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 액션 영화에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in action movies.",
      "Scrambled": "action movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 액션 영화에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in action movies.",
      "Scrambled": "interested / action / movies / in / I’m"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언어 배우는 것에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in learning languages.",
      "Scrambled": "learning languages"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언어 배우는 것에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in learning languages.",
      "Scrambled": "learning / in / interested / I’m / languages"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in art.",
      "Scrambled": "art"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in art.",
      "Scrambled": "I’m / in / art / interested"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What are you interested in?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 요리에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in cooking.",
      "Scrambled": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I’m interested in ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 요리에 관심이 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I’m interested in cooking.",
      "Scrambled": "cooking / interested / I’m / in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 재킷을 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "a jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 재킷을 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a jacket.",
      "Scrambled": "She / jacket / a / wearing / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 안경을 쓰고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "glasses"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 안경을 쓰고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / She / glasses / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 목걸이를 하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a necklace.",
      "Scrambled": "a necklace"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 목걸이를 하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a necklace.",
      "Scrambled": "She / necklace / is / wearing / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 갈색 신발을 신고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing brown shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "brown shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 갈색 신발을 신고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing brown shoes.",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / shoes / She / brown / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 긴 드레스를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a long dress.",
      "Scrambled": "a long dress"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 긴 드레스를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing a long dress.",
      "Scrambled": "She / dress / wearing / is / a / long"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What is he wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 파란색 넥타이를 매고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing a blue tie.",
      "Scrambled": "a blue tie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 파란색 넥타이를 매고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing a blue tie.",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / a / He / tie / is / blue"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What is he wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 노란 장갑을 끼고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing yellow gloves.",
      "Scrambled": "yellow gloves"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 노란 장갑을 끼고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing yellow gloves.",
      "Scrambled": "yellow / He / wearing / gloves / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What is he wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 더러운 바지를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing dirty pants.",
      "Scrambled": "dirty pants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 더러운 바지를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing dirty pants.",
      "Scrambled": "pants / wearing / He / is / dirty"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What is he wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 티셔츠를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing a T-shirt.",
      "Scrambled": "a T-shirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그는 티셔츠를 입고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "He is wearing a T-shirt.",
      "Scrambled": "is / wearing / a / He / T-shirt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What is she wearing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 검은 양말을 신고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing black socks.",
      "Scrambled": "black socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "She is wearing ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀는 검은 양말을 신고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "She is wearing black socks.",
      "Scrambled": "socks / wearing / She / is / black"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 갈 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 갈 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to go?",
      "Scrambled": "go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 갈 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to go?",
      "Scrambled": "to / Are / go / you / ready"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 달릴 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 달릴 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to run?",
      "Scrambled": "run"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 달릴 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to run?",
      "Scrambled": "run / ready / Are / you / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 주문할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 주문할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to order?",
      "Scrambled": "order"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 주문할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to order?",
      "Scrambled": "order / Are / you / to / ready"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밖에서 놀 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밖에서 놀 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to play outside?",
      "Scrambled": "play outside"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밖에서 놀 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to play outside?",
      "Scrambled": "ready / play / to / Are / you / outside"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시험 볼 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시험 볼 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to take the test?",
      "Scrambled": "take the test"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시험 볼 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to take the test?",
      "Scrambled": "test / to / take / ready / the / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 출발할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 출발할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to start?",
      "Scrambled": "start"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 출발할 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to start?",
      "Scrambled": "to / start / Are / you / ready"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠자리에 들 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠자리에 들 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to go to bed?",
      "Scrambled": "go to bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠자리에 들 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to go to bed?",
      "Scrambled": "go / Are / ready / you / to / to / bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 즐길 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 즐길 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to have fun?",
      "Scrambled": "have fun"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 즐길 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to have fun?",
      "Scrambled": "have / ready / fun / Are / you / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 떠날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 떠날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to leave?",
      "Scrambled": "leave"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 떠날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to leave?",
      "Scrambled": "to / ready / leave / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 만날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 만날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to meet him?",
      "Scrambled": "meet him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you ready to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 만날 준비됐니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you ready to meet him?",
      "Scrambled": "you / meet / ready / him / Are / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 야구를 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 야구를 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to play baseball?",
      "Scrambled": "play baseball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 야구를 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to play baseball?",
      "Scrambled": "you / play / Are / baseball / going / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하러 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하러 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to go swimming?",
      "Scrambled": "go swimming"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하러 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to go swimming?",
      "Scrambled": "you / Are / to / going / go / swimming"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to stay home?",
      "Scrambled": "stay home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to stay home?",
      "Scrambled": "you / home / going / Are / to / stay"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 머리카락을 자를 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 머리카락을 자를 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "get a haircut"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 머리카락을 자를 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "get / a / going / Are / haircut / you / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 의사의 진찰을 받을 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 의사의 진찰을 받을 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to see a doctor?",
      "Scrambled": "see a doctor"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 의사의 진찰을 받을 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to see a doctor?",
      "Scrambled": "a / Are / you / to / doctor / going / see"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 책을 읽을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 책을 읽을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to read books?",
      "Scrambled": "read books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 책을 읽을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to read books?",
      "Scrambled": "read / books / Are / you / going / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제주도에 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제주도에 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to go to Jeju-do?",
      "Scrambled": "go to Jeju-do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제주도에 갈 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to go to Jeju-do?",
      "Scrambled": "to / go / Are / going / you / Jeju-do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 삼촌을 방문할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 삼촌을 방문할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to visit your uncle?",
      "Scrambled": "visit your uncle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 삼촌을 방문할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to visit your uncle?",
      "Scrambled": "uncle / Are / to / visit / your / going / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to sleep?",
      "Scrambled": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to sleep?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / going / you / sleep / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 전화할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 전화할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to call her?",
      "Scrambled": "call her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 전화할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you going to call her?",
      "Scrambled": "her / Are / you / call / going / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이 개는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이 개는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this dog yours?",
      "Scrambled": "dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이 개는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this dog yours?",
      "Scrambled": "dog / yours / this / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자리는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자리는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this seat yours?",
      "Scrambled": "seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자리는 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this seat yours?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / yours / seat / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 집은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 집은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this house yours?",
      "Scrambled": "house"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 집은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this house yours?",
      "Scrambled": "yours / house / this / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 무거운 가방은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 무거운 가방은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this heavy bag yours?",
      "Scrambled": "heavy bag"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 무거운 가방은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this heavy bag yours?",
      "Scrambled": "this / heavy / Is / bag / yours"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 새 우산은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 새 우산은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this new umbrella yours?",
      "Scrambled": "new umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이 새 우산은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this new umbrella yours?",
      "Scrambled": "new / Is / umbrella / this / yours"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these books yours?",
      "Scrambled": "books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이 책들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these books yours?",
      "Scrambled": "these / yours / books / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 새들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 새들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these pretty birds yours?",
      "Scrambled": "pretty birds"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 새들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these pretty birds yours?",
      "Scrambled": "these / Are / birds / pretty / yours"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이 더러운 양말들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이 더러운 양말들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these dirty socks yours?",
      "Scrambled": "dirty socks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이 더러운 양말들은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are these dirty socks yours?",
      "Scrambled": "socks / dirty / yours / Are / these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this ticket yours?",
      "Scrambled": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this ticket yours?",
      "Scrambled": "yours / this / Is / ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 재킷은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 재킷은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this pretty jacket yours?",
      "Scrambled": "pretty jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this … yours?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이 예쁜 재킷은 너의 것이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this pretty jacket yours?",
      "Scrambled": "pretty / jacket / Is / this / yours"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 긴장된 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel nervous.",
      "Scrambled": "nervous"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 긴장된 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel nervous.",
      "Scrambled": "I / feel / nervous"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 흥분된 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel excited.",
      "Scrambled": "excited"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 흥분된 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel excited.",
      "Scrambled": "I / feel / excited"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아주 자신 있는 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel very confident.",
      "Scrambled": "very confident"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아주 자신 있는 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel very confident.",
      "Scrambled": "feel / confident / very / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너무 준비가 안 된 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel so unprepared.",
      "Scrambled": "so unprepared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너무 준비가 안 된 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel so unprepared.",
      "Scrambled": "so / feel / I / unprepared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 안쓰러운 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel sorry for her.",
      "Scrambled": "sorry for her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 안쓰러운 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel sorry for her.",
      "Scrambled": "her / for / feel / sorry / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 나아진 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel better.",
      "Scrambled": "better"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 나아진 느낌이 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel better.",
      "Scrambled": "feel / better / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 정말 좋은 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel really good.",
      "Scrambled": "really good"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 정말 좋은 기분이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel really good.",
      "Scrambled": "really / feel / good / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너무 피곤한 상태야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel so tired.",
      "Scrambled": "so tired"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너무 피곤한 상태야.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel so tired.",
      "Scrambled": "feel / so / tired / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아파.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel sick.",
      "Scrambled": "sick"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아파.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel sick.",
      "Scrambled": "feel / sick / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you feel?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 꽤 지루해.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel pretty bored.",
      "Scrambled": "pretty bored"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I feel ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 꽤 지루해.",
      "English/Answer": "I feel pretty bored.",
      "Scrambled": "pretty / bored / feel / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 버스를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by bus.",
      "Scrambled": "bus"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 버스를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by bus.",
      "Scrambled": "I / by / go / bus"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자전거를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by bike.",
      "Scrambled": "bike"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자전거를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by bike.",
      "Scrambled": "by / bike / I / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 보트를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by boat.",
      "Scrambled": "boat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 보트를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by boat.",
      "Scrambled": "I / go / boat / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지하철을 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by subway.",
      "Scrambled": "subway"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지하철을 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by subway.",
      "Scrambled": "subway / I / go / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 기차나 비행기를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by train or plane.",
      "Scrambled": "train or plane"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 기차나 비행기를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by train or plane.",
      "Scrambled": "by / I / plane / or / go / train"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 택시를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by taxi.",
      "Scrambled": "taxi"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 택시를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by taxi.",
      "Scrambled": "go / I / by / taxi"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고속버스를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by express bus.",
      "Scrambled": "express bus"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고속버스를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by express bus.",
      "Scrambled": "I / express / bus / go / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자동차와 배를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by car and ship.",
      "Scrambled": "car and ship"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자동차와 배 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by car and ship.",
      "Scrambled": "ship / and / I / car / go / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자동차를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by car.",
      "Scrambled": "car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자동차를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by car.",
      "Scrambled": "go / by / car / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "How do you go?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오토바이를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by motorcycle.",
      "Scrambled": "motorcycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I go by ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오토바이를 타고 가.",
      "English/Answer": "I go by motorcycle.",
      "Scrambled": "motorcycle / go / I / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 먹는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like eating.",
      "Scrambled": "eating"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 먹는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like eating.",
      "Scrambled": "eating / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 축구 하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like playing soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "playing soccer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 축구 하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like playing soccer.",
      "Scrambled": "playing / soccer / I / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 책 읽는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like reading books.",
      "Scrambled": "reading books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 책 읽는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like reading books.",
      "Scrambled": "reading / I / like / books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음악 듣는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like listening to music.",
      "Scrambled": "listening to music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음악 듣는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like listening to music.",
      "Scrambled": "music / I / listening / to / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 해변에서 수영하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like swimming at the beach.",
      "Scrambled": "swimming at the beach"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 해변에서 수영하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like swimming at the beach.",
      "Scrambled": "beach / swimming / at / I / like / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you not like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑 가는 것을 좋아하지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I don't like going camping.",
      "Scrambled": "going camping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑 가는 것을 좋아하지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I don't like going camping.",
      "Scrambled": "going / camping / like / I / don't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 공부하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like studying English.",
      "Scrambled": "studying English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 공부하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like studying English.",
      "Scrambled": "studying / like / I / English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you not like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 것들을 시도하는 것을 좋아하지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I don't like trying new things.",
      "Scrambled": "trying new things"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 것들을 시도하는 것을 좋아하지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I don't like trying new things.",
      "Scrambled": "like / I / things / trying / new / don't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 요리하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like cooking.",
      "Scrambled": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 요리하는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like cooking.",
      "Scrambled": "cooking / like / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you like doing?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 TV 보는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watching TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "I like -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 TV 보는 것을 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I like watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watching / like / TV / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to be in the future?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 가수가 되고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to be a singer.",
      "Scrambled": "be a singer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 가수가 되고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to be a singer.",
      "Scrambled": "want / to / a / singer / I / be"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밖에서 놀고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to play outside.",
      "Scrambled": "play outside"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밖에서 놀고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to play outside.",
      "Scrambled": "I / play / outside / to / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피자를 먹고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to eat pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "eat pizza"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피자를 먹고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to eat pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "to / eat / I / want / pizza"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자전거를 타고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to ride a bike.",
      "Scrambled": "ride a bike"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 자전거를 타고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to ride a bike.",
      "Scrambled": "bike / to / a / ride / I / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 TV를 더 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to watch more TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watch more TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 TV를 더 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to watch more TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watch / TV / more / want / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to go home.",
      "Scrambled": "go home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to go home.",
      "Scrambled": "want / to / home / I / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 파티를 열고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to have a party.",
      "Scrambled": "have a party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 파티를 열고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to have a party.",
      "Scrambled": "to / have / party / a / I / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새 헤드폰을 사고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to buy new headphones.",
      "Scrambled": "buy new headphones"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새 헤드폰을 사고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to buy new headphones.",
      "Scrambled": "to / buy / headphones / new / I / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 산책을 하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to take a walk.",
      "Scrambled": "take a walk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 산책을 하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to take a walk.",
      "Scrambled": "take / walk / a / to / I / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you want to do?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영화를 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to see a movie.",
      "Scrambled": "see a movie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "I want to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영화를 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I want to see a movie.",
      "Scrambled": "movie / a / see / want / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 재미있다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's fun.",
      "Scrambled": "fun"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 재미있다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's fun.",
      "Scrambled": "it's / fun / think / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 어렵다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it is difficult.",
      "Scrambled": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 어렵다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it is difficult.",
      "Scrambled": "it / difficult / is / I / think"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 용감하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think he is brave.",
      "Scrambled": "brave"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 용감하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think he is brave.",
      "Scrambled": "I / he / brave / think / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 책이 흥미롭다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think this book is interesting.",
      "Scrambled": "interesting"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 책이 흥미롭다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think this book is interesting.",
      "Scrambled": "interesting / book / think / is / this / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저것이 지루할 거라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think that would be boring.",
      "Scrambled": "boring"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저것이 지루할 거라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think that would be boring.",
      "Scrambled": "think / boring / be / I / would / that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 옳다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you're right.",
      "Scrambled": "right"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 옳다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you're right.",
      "Scrambled": "think / right / I / you're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 좋은 생각이라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's a good idea.",
      "Scrambled": "good idea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 좋은 생각이라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's a good idea.",
      "Scrambled": "idea / I / think / a / good / it's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 그림이 환상적이라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think the painting is fantastic.",
      "Scrambled": "fantastic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 그림이 환상적이라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think the painting is fantastic.",
      "Scrambled": "think / painting / is / I / the / fantastic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 놀랍다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's amazing.",
      "Scrambled": "amazing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그것이 놀랍다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think it's amazing.",
      "Scrambled": "amazing / I / think / it's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 매우 똑똑하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think she is very smart.",
      "Scrambled": "very smart"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 매우 똑똑하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think she is very smart.",
      "Scrambled": "think / is / very / smart / she / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저것이 무서울 거라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think that would be scary.",
      "Scrambled": "scary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저것이 무서울 거라고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think that would be scary.",
      "Scrambled": "I / scary / be / that / think / would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "What do you think?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 배우들이 훌륭하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think the actors are great.",
      "Scrambled": "great"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "I think ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 배우들이 훌륭하다고 생각해.",
      "English/Answer": "I think the actors are great.",
      "Scrambled": "great / actors / are / I / the / think"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 성처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a castle.",
      "Scrambled": "a castle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 성처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a castle.",
      "Scrambled": "like / a / It / castle / looks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 꽃 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like flowers.",
      "Scrambled": "flowers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 꽃 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like flowers.",
      "Scrambled": "smells / flowers / It / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 오렌지 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like oranges.",
      "Scrambled": "oranges"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 오렌지 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like oranges.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes / oranges / like / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 바다 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "the sea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 바다 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "sounds / sea / It / like / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 별처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a star.",
      "Scrambled": "a star"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 별처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a star.",
      "Scrambled": "star / looks / a / It / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 생선 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like fish.",
      "Scrambled": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 생선 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like fish.",
      "Scrambled": "smells / fish / It / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 초콜릿 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "chocolate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 초콜릿 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "tastes / chocolate / like / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 천둥 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like thunder.",
      "Scrambled": "thunder"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 천둥 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like thunder.",
      "Scrambled": "sounds / like / It / thunder"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 돛단배처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a sailboat.",
      "Scrambled": "a sailboat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 돛단배처럼 보여.",
      "English/Answer": "It looks like a sailboat.",
      "Scrambled": "looks / a / It / sailboat / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 폭우 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like heavy rain.",
      "Scrambled": "heavy rain"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 폭우 같은 소리가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It sounds like heavy rain.",
      "Scrambled": "heavy / like / sounds / rain / It"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 레몬 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like lemons.",
      "Scrambled": "lemons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 레몬 같은 맛이 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It tastes like lemons.",
      "Scrambled": "lemons / It / like / tastes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "What is it like?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 향수 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like perfume.",
      "Scrambled": "perfume"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It looks [smells, tastes, sounds] like ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "그것은 향수 같은 냄새가 나.",
      "English/Answer": "It smells like perfume.",
      "Scrambled": "perfume / It / like / smells"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요리하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요리하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요리하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "cooking / Do / like / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 농구 하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 농구 하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like playing basketball?",
      "Scrambled": "playing basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 농구 하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like playing basketball?",
      "Scrambled": "basketball / like / playing / Do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 노래 부르는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 노래 부르는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like singing songs?",
      "Scrambled": "singing songs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 노래 부르는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like singing songs?",
      "Scrambled": "songs / singing / you / like / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 개 산책시키는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 개 산책시키는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like walking dogs?",
      "Scrambled": "walking dogs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 개 산책시키는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like walking dogs?",
      "Scrambled": "walking / like / dogs / you / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 인터넷 검색하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 인터넷 검색하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like surfing the internet?",
      "Scrambled": "surfing the internet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 인터넷 검색하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like surfing the internet?",
      "Scrambled": "internet / the / surfing / like / you / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이야기 쓰는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이야기 쓰는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like writing stories?",
      "Scrambled": "writing stories"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이야기 쓰는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like writing stories?",
      "Scrambled": "like / stories / writing / you / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 바이올린 연주하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 바이올린 연주하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like playing the violin?",
      "Scrambled": "playing the violin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 바이올린 연주하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like playing the violin?",
      "Scrambled": "the / Do / violin / like / playing / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 사진 찍는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 사진 찍는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like taking pictures?",
      "Scrambled": "taking pictures"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 사진 찍는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like taking pictures?",
      "Scrambled": "like / you / pictures / taking / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like skateboarding?",
      "Scrambled": "skateboarding"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like skateboarding?",
      "Scrambled": "like / you / skateboarding / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 외식하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 외식하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like eating out?",
      "Scrambled": "eating out"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 외식하는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like eating out?",
      "Scrambled": "out / eating / you / like / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그림 그리는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그림 그리는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like drawing pictures?",
      "Scrambled": "drawing pictures"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그림 그리는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like drawing pictures?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / drawing / like / you / pictures"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 만화책 읽는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 만화책 읽는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like reading comic books?",
      "Scrambled": "reading comic books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you like -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 만화책 읽는 것을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you like reading comic books?",
      "Scrambled": "reading / books / you / Do / like / comic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤추고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤추고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to dance?",
      "Scrambled": "dance"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤추고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to dance?",
      "Scrambled": "you / Do / dance / to / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기에 앉고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기에 앉고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "sit here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기에 앉고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "want / sit / here / Do / to / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 동아리에 가입하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 동아리에 가입하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to join the club?",
      "Scrambled": "join the club"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 동아리에 가입하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to join the club?",
      "Scrambled": "you / club / join / to / the / want / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 걸어가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 걸어가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to walk to school?",
      "Scrambled": "walk to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 걸어가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to walk to school?",
      "Scrambled": "walk / want / Do / school / you / to / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 소풍 가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 소풍 가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to go on a picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "go on a picnic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 소풍 가고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to go on a picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "you / picnic / go / want / a / on / to / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다른 사람들을 돕고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다른 사람들을 돕고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to help others?",
      "Scrambled": "help others"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다른 사람들을 돕고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to help others?",
      "Scrambled": "help / others / want / to / you / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 공연을 보고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 공연을 보고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to see the show?",
      "Scrambled": "see the show"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 공연을 보고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to see the show?",
      "Scrambled": "you / the / Do / want / show / see / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 더 자고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 더 자고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to sleep more?",
      "Scrambled": "sleep more"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 더 자고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to sleep more?",
      "Scrambled": "want / to / Do / sleep / you / more"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to come?",
      "Scrambled": "come"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to come?",
      "Scrambled": "come / want / to / you / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 반납하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 반납하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to return this book?",
      "Scrambled": "return this book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 반납하고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to return this book?",
      "Scrambled": "book / this / to / return / Do / you / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국수를 먹고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국수를 먹고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to have noodles?",
      "Scrambled": "have noodles"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국수를 먹고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to have noodles?",
      "Scrambled": "you / have / noodles / to / Do / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악을 듣고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악을 듣고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to listen to music?",
      "Scrambled": "listen to music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you want to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악을 듣고 싶니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you want to listen to music?",
      "Scrambled": "to / music / you / want / listen / to / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물렀니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물렀니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you stay home?",
      "Scrambled": "stay home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 머물렀니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you stay home?",
      "Scrambled": "stay / home / you / Did"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뭔가를 샀니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뭔가를 샀니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you buy anything?",
      "Scrambled": "buy anything"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뭔가를 샀니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you buy anything?",
      "Scrambled": "you / Did / anything / buy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 경기에서 이겼니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 경기에서 이겼니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you win the game?",
      "Scrambled": "win the game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 경기에서 이겼니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you win the game?",
      "Scrambled": "win / Did / the / game / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you go to the park?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the park"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you go to the park?",
      "Scrambled": "park / the / Did / go / to / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 숙제를 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 숙제를 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you do your homework?",
      "Scrambled": "do your homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 숙제를 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you do your homework?",
      "Scrambled": "homework / do / Did / your / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 잤니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 잤니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you sleep well?",
      "Scrambled": "sleep well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잘 잤니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you sleep well?",
      "Scrambled": "sleep / Did / you / well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 퍼레이드를 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 퍼레이드를 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you watch the parade?",
      "Scrambled": "watch the parade"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 퍼레이드를 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you watch the parade?",
      "Scrambled": "parade / watch / you / Did / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 쿠키를 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 쿠키를 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you eat my cookies?",
      "Scrambled": "eat my cookies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 쿠키를 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you eat my cookies?",
      "Scrambled": "my / eat / you / cookies / Did"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아침을 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아침을 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you have breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "have breakfast"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아침을 먹었니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you have breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "you / breakfast / Did / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 문을 잠갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 문을 잠갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you lock the door?",
      "Scrambled": "lock the door"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 문을 잠갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you lock the door?",
      "Scrambled": "Did / door / the / lock / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 병원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 병원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you go to the hospital?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the hospital"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 병원에 갔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you go to the hospital?",
      "Scrambled": "Did / the / hospital / you / go / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가족과 게임을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가족과 게임을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you play games with your family?",
      "Scrambled": "play games with your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Did you…?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가족과 게임을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "Did you play games with your family?",
      "Scrambled": "your / with / play / Did / games / family / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you doing?",
      "Scrambled": "doing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you doing?",
      "Scrambled": "are / you / doing / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 만들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 만들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you making?",
      "Scrambled": "making"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 만들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you making?",
      "Scrambled": "What / you / making / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you reading?",
      "Scrambled": "reading"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you reading?",
      "Scrambled": "are / you / What / reading"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you wearing?",
      "Scrambled": "wearing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you wearing?",
      "Scrambled": "you / wearing / are / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 찾고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 찾고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you looking for?",
      "Scrambled": "looking for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 찾고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you looking for?",
      "Scrambled": "What / looking / for / you / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you eating?",
      "Scrambled": "eating"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you eating?",
      "Scrambled": "eating / you / are / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 그리고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 그리고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you drawing?",
      "Scrambled": "drawing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 그리고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you drawing?",
      "Scrambled": "What / you / drawing / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you listening to?",
      "Scrambled": "listening to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 듣고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you listening to?",
      "Scrambled": "are / you / listening / to / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "you / What / cooking / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓰고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓰고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you writing?",
      "Scrambled": "writing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓰고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you writing?",
      "Scrambled": "writing / are / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 보고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 보고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you looking at?",
      "Scrambled": "looking at"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 보고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you looking at?",
      "Scrambled": "at / you / What / are / looking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇에 대해 이야기하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇에 대해 이야기하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you talking about?",
      "Scrambled": "talking about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇에 대해 이야기하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you talking about?",
      "Scrambled": "are / What / about / talking / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to eat?",
      "Scrambled": "eat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to eat?",
      "Scrambled": "are / to / What / you / going / eat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to buy?",
      "Scrambled": "buy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to buy?",
      "Scrambled": "to / going / What / buy / are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓸 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓸 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to write?",
      "Scrambled": "write"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 쓸 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to write?",
      "Scrambled": "What / write / are / you / going / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내일 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내일 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to do tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "do tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내일 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to do tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "you / going / to / tomorrow / do / What / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 저녁으로 무엇을 요리할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 저녁으로 무엇을 요리할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to cook for dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "cook for dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 저녁으로 무엇을 요리할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to cook for dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "cook / What / going / you / dinner / to / for / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 볼 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 볼 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to watch?",
      "Scrambled": "watch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 볼 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to watch?",
      "Scrambled": "to / are / watch / you / going / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 무엇을 줄 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 무엇을 줄 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to give to her?",
      "Scrambled": "give to her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그녀에게 무엇을 줄 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to give to her?",
      "Scrambled": "give / you / to / are / What / going / to / her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 파티에 무엇을 가져올 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 파티에 무엇을 가져올 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to bring to the party?",
      "Scrambled": "bring to the party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 파티에 무엇을 가져올 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to bring to the party?",
      "Scrambled": "to / you / bring / going / to / What / are / the / party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 공부할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 공부할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to study?",
      "Scrambled": "study"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 무엇을 공부할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to study?",
      "Scrambled": "What / are / to / going / you / study"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이번 주말에 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이번 주말에 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to do this weekend?",
      "Scrambled": "do this weekend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이번 주말에 무엇을 할 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to do this weekend?",
      "Scrambled": "going / you / weekend / are / What / this / do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 점심으로 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 점심으로 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to have for lunch?",
      "Scrambled": "have for lunch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 점심으로 무엇을 먹을 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to have for lunch?",
      "Scrambled": "are / for / to / lunch / What / going / have / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가게에서 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가게에서 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to get at the store?",
      "Scrambled": "get at the store"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "What are you going to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 가게에서 무엇을 살 거니?",
      "English/Answer": "What are you going to get at the store?",
      "Scrambled": "store / What / at / you / the / get / are / going / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with you?",
      "Scrambled": "you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with you?",
      "Scrambled": "wrong / you / What's / with"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "리사에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with Lisa?",
      "Scrambled": "Lisa"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "리사에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with Lisa?",
      "Scrambled": "with / What's / Lisa / wrong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그 차에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with the car?",
      "Scrambled": "the car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "그 차에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with the car?",
      "Scrambled": "the / wrong / with / What's / car"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 눈에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your eye?",
      "Scrambled": "your eye"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 눈에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your eye?",
      "Scrambled": "your / eye / What's / with / wrong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 아빠의 손에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your dad's hand?",
      "Scrambled": "your dad's hand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 아빠의 손에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your dad's hand?",
      "Scrambled": "your / dad's / hand / with / What's / wrong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "톰의 팔들에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with Tom's arms?",
      "Scrambled": "Tom's arms"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "톰의 팔들에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with Tom's arms?",
      "Scrambled": "What's / Tom's / wrong / arms / with"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀의 다리들에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with her legs?",
      "Scrambled": "her legs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀의 다리들에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with her legs?",
      "Scrambled": "with / her / legs / wrong / What's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 개에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your dog?",
      "Scrambled": "your dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 개에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your dog?",
      "Scrambled": "wrong / dog / What's / your / with"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with him?",
      "Scrambled": "him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그에게 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with him?",
      "Scrambled": "wrong / him / with / What's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 발가락에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your toe?",
      "Scrambled": "your toe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "네 발가락에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your toe?",
      "Scrambled": "What's / toe / your / with / wrong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "문에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with the door?",
      "Scrambled": "the door"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "문에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with the door?",
      "Scrambled": "with / the / What's / wrong / door"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "What's wrong?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "네 엄마의 머리에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your mom's head?",
      "Scrambled": "your mom's head"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "What's wrong with …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "네 엄마의 머리에 무슨 문제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's wrong with your mom's head?",
      "Scrambled": "wrong / with / What's / mom's / your / head"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "봄에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "봄에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the spring?",
      "Scrambled": "in the spring"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "봄에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the spring?",
      "Scrambled": "the / in / like / weather / the / spring / What's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "여름에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "여름에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the summer?",
      "Scrambled": "in the summer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "여름에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the summer?",
      "Scrambled": "like / in / What's / summer / the / weather / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "가을에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "가을에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the fall?",
      "Scrambled": "in the fall"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "가을에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the fall?",
      "Scrambled": "What's / in / weather / the / like / the / fall"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "겨울에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "겨울에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the winter?",
      "Scrambled": "in the winter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "겨울에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in the winter?",
      "Scrambled": "What's / the / winter / in / weather / the / like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "하와이의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "하와이의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Hawaii?",
      "Scrambled": "in Hawaii"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "하와이의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Hawaii?",
      "Scrambled": "in / like / weather / What's / the / Hawaii"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like today?",
      "Scrambled": "today"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like today?",
      "Scrambled": "weather / today / like / What's / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "12월에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "12월에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in December?",
      "Scrambled": "in December"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "12월에 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in December?",
      "Scrambled": "weather / like / What's / the / December / in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "한국의 여름 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "한국의 여름 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Korea in the summer?",
      "Scrambled": "in Korea in the summer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "한국의 여름 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Korea in the summer?",
      "Scrambled": "the / summer / weather / Korea / in / like / What's / the / in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "요즘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "요즘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like these days?",
      "Scrambled": "these days"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "요즘 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like these days?",
      "Scrambled": "What's / the / like / these / days / weather"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "뉴욕의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "뉴욕의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in New York?",
      "Scrambled": "in New York"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "뉴욕의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in New York?",
      "Scrambled": "in / What's / like / weather / the / York / New"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "한국 서울의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "한국 서울의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Seoul, Korea?",
      "Scrambled": "in Seoul, Korea?"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "한국 서울의 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Seoul, Korea?",
      "Scrambled": "like / Seoul, / What's / in / Korea / the / weather"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "일본의 봄 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "일본의 봄 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Japan in the spring?",
      "Scrambled": "in Japan in the spring"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "What's the weather like …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "일본의 봄 날씨는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "What's the weather like in Japan in the spring?",
      "Scrambled": "weather / like / the / spring / Japan / the / in / What's / in"
    }
  ],
  "Level B Book 2": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 일어나니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 일어나니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get up?",
      "Scrambled": "get up"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 일어나니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get up?",
      "Scrambled": "up / get / you / do / time / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you go to school?",
      "Scrambled": "go to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you go to school?",
      "Scrambled": "to / go / you / school / What / time / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 네 숙제를 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 네 숙제를 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you do your homework?",
      "Scrambled": "do your homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 네 숙제를 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you do your homework?",
      "Scrambled": "do / your / What / time / do / homework / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 저녁을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 저녁을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "have dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 저녁을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "time / dinner / have / do / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 자러 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 자러 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you go to bed?",
      "Scrambled": "go to bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 자러 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you go to bed?",
      "Scrambled": "bed / to / go / do / you / time / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 피아노 수업이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 피아노 수업이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have a piano lesson?",
      "Scrambled": "have a piano lesson"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 피아노 수업이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have a piano lesson?",
      "Scrambled": "a / piano / you / do / time / lesson / What / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 집에 도착하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 집에 도착하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get home?",
      "Scrambled": "get home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 집에 도착하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get home?",
      "Scrambled": "do / time / get / home / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 영어 프로그램을 시청하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 영어 프로그램을 시청하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you watch English programs?",
      "Scrambled": "watch English programs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 영어 프로그램을 시청하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you watch English programs?",
      "Scrambled": "What / time / watch / English / you / do / programs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 아침을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 아침을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "have breakfast"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 아침을 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you have breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "time / What / breakfast / do / you / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에서 나오니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에서 나오니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get out of school?",
      "Scrambled": "get out of school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "What time do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 몇 시에 학교에서 나오니?",
      "English/Answer": "What time do you get out of school?",
      "Scrambled": "you / out / get / do / time / What / school / of"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 애완동물을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 애완동물을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of pet do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "pet do you have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 애완동물을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of pet do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "kind / have / What / of / you / pet / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 주스를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 주스를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of juice do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "juice do you want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 주스를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of juice do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "juice / want / kind / of / What / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음악을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음악을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of music do you like?",
      "Scrambled": "music do you like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음악을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of music do you like?",
      "Scrambled": "you / music / do / like / kind / of / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 일을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 일을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of work do you do?",
      "Scrambled": "work do you do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 일을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of work do you do?",
      "Scrambled": "do / of / you / What / kind / work / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 후식을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 후식을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of dessert do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "dessert do you have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 후식을 갖고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of dessert do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "have / kind / of / do / dessert / What / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 선물을 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 선물을 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of gift do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "gift do you want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 선물을 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of gift do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "you / kind / of / What / gift / do / want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음식을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음식을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of food do you like?",
      "Scrambled": "food do you like"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 음식을 좋아하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of food do you like?",
      "Scrambled": "like / do / of / food / you / kind / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 운동을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 운동을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of exercise do you do?",
      "Scrambled": "exercise do you do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 운동을 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of exercise do you do?",
      "Scrambled": "do / kind / you / of / do / What / exercise"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 취미를 가지고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 취미를 가지고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of hobby do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "hobby do you have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 취미를 가지고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of hobby do you have?",
      "Scrambled": "do / hobby / have / kind / What / of / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 차를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 차를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of car do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "car do you want"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "What kind of ~ do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어떤 종류의 차를 원하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What kind of car do you want?",
      "Scrambled": "What / do / kind / want / of / car / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "민지와 준호 중에서 누가 더 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "민지와 준호 중에서 누가 더 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is older, Minji or Junho?",
      "Scrambled": "older, Minji or Junho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "민지와 준호 중에서 누가 더 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is older, Minji or Junho?",
      "Scrambled": "older, / is / Who / Minji / Junho / or"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해리와 테드 중에서 누가 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해리와 테드 중에서 누가 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is faster, Harry or Ted?",
      "Scrambled": "faster, Harry or Ted"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해리와 테드 중에서 누가 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is faster, Harry or Ted?",
      "Scrambled": "faster, / is / or / Who / Harry / Ted"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너와 너의 남동생 중에서 누가 더 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너와 너의 남동생 중에서 누가 더 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is taller, you or your brother?",
      "Scrambled": "taller, you or your brother"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너와 너의 남동생 중에서 누가 더 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is taller, you or your brother?",
      "Scrambled": "your / brother / or / taller, / Who / is / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "제이와 그의 친구 중에서 누가 더 체격이 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "제이와 그의 친구 중에서 누가 더 체격이 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is smaller, Jay or his friend?",
      "Scrambled": "smaller, Jay or his friend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "제이와 그의 친구 중에서 누가 더 체격이 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is smaller, Jay or his friend?",
      "Scrambled": "is / Who / friend / or / his / smaller, / Jay"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "루시와 그녀의 여동생 중에서 누가 더 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "루시와 그녀의 여동생 중에서 누가 더 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is prettier, Lucy or her sister?",
      "Scrambled": "prettier, Lucy or her sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "루시와 그녀의 여동생 중에서 누가 더 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is prettier, Lucy or her sister?",
      "Scrambled": "sister / her / or / prettier, / is / Who / Lucy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "토끼와 거북이 중에서 어느 것이 더 느리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "토끼와 거북이 중에서 어느 것이 더 느리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is slower, a rabbit or a turtle?",
      "Scrambled": "slower, a rabbit or a turtle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "토끼와 거북이 중에서 어느 것이 더 느리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is slower, a rabbit or a turtle?",
      "Scrambled": "turtle / is / Which / a / rabbit / or / slower, / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "고래와 여우 중에서 어느 것이 더 몸집이 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "고래와 여우 중에서 어느 것이 더 몸집이 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is bigger, a whale or a fox?",
      "Scrambled": "bigger, a whale or a fox"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "고래와 여우 중에서 어느 것이 더 몸집이 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is bigger, a whale or a fox?",
      "Scrambled": "bigger, / a / Which / is / fox / or / whale / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "버스와 기차 중에서 어느 것이 더 기니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "버스와 기차 중에서 어느 것이 더 기니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is longer, a bus or a train?",
      "Scrambled": "longer, a bus or a train"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "버스와 기차 중에서 어느 것이 더 기니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is longer, a bus or a train?",
      "Scrambled": "or / a / train / bus / a / Which / is / longer,"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "로이와 캐시 중에서 누가 더 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "로이와 캐시 중에서 누가 더 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is younger, Roy or Cathy?",
      "Scrambled": "younger, Roy or Cathy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "로이와 캐시 중에서 누가 더 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is younger, Roy or Cathy?",
      "Scrambled": "Roy / younger, / or / Who / is / Cathy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자동차와 비행기 중에서 어느 것이 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자동차와 비행기 중에서 어느 것이 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is faster, a car or a plane?",
      "Scrambled": "faster, a car or a plane"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is -er, A or B?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자동차와 비행기 중에서 어느 것이 더 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Which is faster, a car or a plane?",
      "Scrambled": "a / plane / or / Which / faster, / a / car / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the tallest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "tallest in your class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 키가 크니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the tallest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "class / your / Who / the / tallest / in / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 힘이 세니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 힘이 세니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the strongest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "strongest in your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 힘이 세니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the strongest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "Who / the / is / strongest / family / in / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the fastest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "fastest in your class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 빠르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the fastest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "is / in / your / class / fastest / Who / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 약하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 약하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the weakest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "weakest in your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 약하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the weakest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "family / weakest / is / your / Who / in / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 똑똑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 똑똑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the smartest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "smartest in your class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 똑똑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the smartest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "in / is / class / Who / the / smartest / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the prettiest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "prettiest in your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 예쁘니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the prettiest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "family / prettiest / Who / in / your / is / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the smallest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "smallest in your class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 작니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the smallest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "Who / in / the / your / smallest / is / class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the youngest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "youngest in your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 어리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the youngest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "in / family / is / youngest / Who / your / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the oldest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "oldest in your family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 가족 중에서 누가 가장 나이가 많니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the oldest in your family?",
      "Scrambled": "is / Who / family / in / your / the / oldest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 웃기니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 웃기니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the funniest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "funniest in your class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "Who is the -est in ~?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "너희 반에서 누가 가장 웃기니?",
      "English/Answer": "Who is the funniest in your class?",
      "Scrambled": "the / class / is / Who / in / your / funniest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 가방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 가방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose bag is this?",
      "Scrambled": "bag is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 가방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose bag is this?",
      "Scrambled": "bag / is / Whose / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 컵이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 컵이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose cup is this?",
      "Scrambled": "cup is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 컵이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose cup is this?",
      "Scrambled": "Whose / cup / is / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 자이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 자이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose ruler is this?",
      "Scrambled": "ruler is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 자이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose ruler is this?",
      "Scrambled": "is / Whose / ruler / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 집이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 집이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose house is this?",
      "Scrambled": "house is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 집이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose house is this?",
      "Scrambled": "house / this / Whose / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 햄스터니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 햄스터니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose hamster is this?",
      "Scrambled": "hamster is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 햄스터니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose hamster is this?",
      "Scrambled": "hamster / Whose / is / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 신발이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 신발이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose shoes are these?",
      "Scrambled": "shoes are these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 신발이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose shoes are these?",
      "Scrambled": "these / shoes / are / Whose"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 장갑이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 장갑이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose gloves are these?",
      "Scrambled": "gloves are these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 장갑이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose gloves are these?",
      "Scrambled": "gloves / are / Whose / these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 그림들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 그림들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose pictures are these?",
      "Scrambled": "pictures are these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "이것들은 누구의 그림들이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose pictures are these?",
      "Scrambled": "Whose / are / pictures / these"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 차니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 차니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose car is this?",
      "Scrambled": "car is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 차니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose car is this?",
      "Scrambled": "Whose / is / car / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 풀이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 풀이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose glue is this?",
      "Scrambled": "glue is this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "Whose … is this?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 누구의 풀이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Whose glue is this?",
      "Scrambled": "glue / Whose / is / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "시험은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "시험은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the test?",
      "Scrambled": "the test"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "시험은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the test?",
      "Scrambled": "test / is / When / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "콘서트는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "콘서트는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the concert?",
      "Scrambled": "the concert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "콘서트는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the concert?",
      "Scrambled": "concert / the / is / When"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 소풍은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 소풍은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is our picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "our picnic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 소풍은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is our picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "is / picnic / our / When"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 생일은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 생일은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is your birthday?",
      "Scrambled": "your birthday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 생일은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is your birthday?",
      "Scrambled": "birthday / When / is / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "어린이날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "어린이날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is Children's Day?",
      "Scrambled": "Children's Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "어린이날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is Children's Day?",
      "Scrambled": "is / When / Children's / Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "파티는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "파티는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the party?",
      "Scrambled": "the party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "파티는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the party?",
      "Scrambled": "party / is / the / When"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "다음 수업은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "다음 수업은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the next class?",
      "Scrambled": "the next class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "다음 수업은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the next class?",
      "Scrambled": "is / next / class / the / When"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "지구의 날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "지구의 날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is Earth Day?",
      "Scrambled": "Earth Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "지구의 날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is Earth Day?",
      "Scrambled": "Earth / When / is / Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "새해 첫날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "새해 첫날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is New Year's Day?",
      "Scrambled": "New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "새해 첫날은 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is New Year's Day?",
      "Scrambled": "When / New / is / Year's / Day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "말하기 대회는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "말하기 대회는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the speech contest?",
      "Scrambled": "the speech contest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "When is …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "말하기 대회는 언제니?",
      "English/Answer": "When is the speech contest?",
      "Scrambled": "is / speech / the / When / contest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 공부하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 공부하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you study?",
      "Scrambled": "study"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 공부하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you study?",
      "Scrambled": "Where / study / you / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 쇼핑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 쇼핑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you shop?",
      "Scrambled": "shop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 쇼핑하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you shop?",
      "Scrambled": "you / do / Where / shop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 왔니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 왔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you come from?",
      "Scrambled": "come from"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 왔니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you come from?",
      "Scrambled": "from / you / come / Where / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "get a haircut"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "do / you / get / a / Where / haircut"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토요일마다 어디에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토요일마다 어디에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you go on Saturdays?",
      "Scrambled": "go on Saturdays"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토요일마다 어디에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you go on Saturdays?",
      "Scrambled": "Where / go / on / do / you / Saturdays"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 일하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 일하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you work?",
      "Scrambled": "work"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 일하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you work?",
      "Scrambled": "work / do / you / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 내리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 내리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you get off?",
      "Scrambled": "get off"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 내리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you get off?",
      "Scrambled": "get / do / you / off / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 그녀를 만나니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 그녀를 만나니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you meet her?",
      "Scrambled": "meet her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 그녀를 만나니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you meet her?",
      "Scrambled": "do / you / meet / her / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에 사니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에 사니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you live?",
      "Scrambled": "live"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에 사니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you live?",
      "Scrambled": "live / you / do / Where"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you work out?",
      "Scrambled": "work out"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "Where do you …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 어디에서 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Where do you work out?",
      "Scrambled": "Where / do / out / work / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to school?",
      "Scrambled": "to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 학교에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to school?",
      "Scrambled": "do / you / get / school / to / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시장에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시장에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the market?",
      "Scrambled": "to the market"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시장에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the market?",
      "Scrambled": "market / to / the / get / How / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도서관에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도서관에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "to the library"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도서관에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "to / get / you / do / library / How / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 식당에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 식당에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the restaurant?",
      "Scrambled": "to the restaurant"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 식당에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the restaurant?",
      "Scrambled": "the / you / to / How / get / restaurant / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 워터 파크에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 워터 파크에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the water park?",
      "Scrambled": "to the water park"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 워터 파크에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the water park?",
      "Scrambled": "you / to / the / How / get / park / water / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 쇼핑몰에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 쇼핑몰에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the mall?",
      "Scrambled": "to the mall"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 쇼핑몰에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the mall?",
      "Scrambled": "mall / get / you / the / to / do / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이발소에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이발소에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the barbershop?",
      "Scrambled": "to the barbershop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이발소에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the barbershop?",
      "Scrambled": "barbershop / get / do / you / to / How / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뉴욕에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뉴욕에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to New York?",
      "Scrambled": "to New York"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뉴욕에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to New York?",
      "Scrambled": "New / How / do / you / get / to / York"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 대구에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 대구에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to Daegu?",
      "Scrambled": "to Daegu"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 대구에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to Daegu?",
      "Scrambled": "to / get / How / do / you / Daegu"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 서점에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 서점에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the bookstore?",
      "Scrambled": "to the bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 서점에 어떻게 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you get to the bookstore?",
      "Scrambled": "bookstore / to / How / the / do / get / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "공원까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "공원까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the park?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the park"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "공원까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the park?",
      "Scrambled": "the / to / How / does / park / get / long / it / take / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해변까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해변까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the beach?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the beach"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "해변까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the beach?",
      "Scrambled": "get / does / take / How / to / beach / to / it / long / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "터미널까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "터미널까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the terminal?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the terminal"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "터미널까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the terminal?",
      "Scrambled": "to / terminal / get / the / long / it / take / to / does / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "경기장까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "경기장까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the stadium?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the stadium"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "경기장까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the stadium?",
      "Scrambled": "long / take / to / stadium / get / How / the / it / does / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "식료품점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "식료품점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the grocery store?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the grocery store"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "식료품점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the grocery store?",
      "Scrambled": "grocery / How / take / to / get / does / to / long / it / the / store"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "기차역까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "기차역까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the train station?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the train station"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "기차역까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the train station?",
      "Scrambled": "take / train / it / the / station / to / long / to / get / How / does"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "부두까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "부두까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the pier?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the pier"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "부두까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the pier?",
      "Scrambled": "it / to / take / the / long / pier / get / to / does / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "서점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "서점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the bookstore?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "서점까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the bookstore?",
      "Scrambled": "bookstore / How / get / does / the / to / long / it / take / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "학교까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "학교까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to school?",
      "Scrambled": "get to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "학교까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to school?",
      "Scrambled": "to / to / long / it / How / get / does / take / school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "공항까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "공항까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the airport?",
      "Scrambled": "get to the airport"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "How long does it take to get to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "공항까지 가는 데 얼마나 걸리니?",
      "English/Answer": "How long does it take to get to the airport?",
      "Scrambled": "get / airport / the / to / does / How / it / take / long / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우유는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우유는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about milk?",
      "Scrambled": "milk"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우유는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about milk?",
      "Scrambled": "milk / How / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "약간의 간식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "약간의 간식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about some snacks?",
      "Scrambled": "some snacks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "약간의 간식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about some snacks?",
      "Scrambled": "How / some / snacks / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "지하철을 타는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "지하철을 타는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about taking the subway?",
      "Scrambled": "taking the subway"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "지하철을 타는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about taking the subway?",
      "Scrambled": "the / How / taking / subway / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about going to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "going to the library"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about going to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "going / to / How / about / library / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "점심으로 피자를 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "점심으로 피자를 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about having pizza for lunch?",
      "Scrambled": "having pizza for lunch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "점심으로 피자를 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about having pizza for lunch?",
      "Scrambled": "about / pizza / lunch / for / How / having"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "후식으로 아이스크림은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "후식으로 아이스크림은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about ice cream for dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "ice cream for dessert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "후식으로 아이스크림은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about ice cream for dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "ice / cream / How / for / about / dessert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마시는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마시는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about drinking water?",
      "Scrambled": "drinking water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마시는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about drinking water?",
      "Scrambled": "about / How / water / drinking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀를 데리고 나가서 저녁을 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀를 데리고 나가서 저녁을 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about taking her out to dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "taking her out to dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "그녀를 데리고 나가서 저녁을 먹는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about taking her out to dinner?",
      "Scrambled": "dinner / to / taking / out / about / her / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내일은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내일은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내일은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "tomorrow / How / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "소풍 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "소풍 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about going on a picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "going on a picnic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "How about ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "소풍 가는 것은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How about going on a picnic?",
      "Scrambled": "on / about / How / going / a / picnic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 요리하고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you cooking?",
      "Scrambled": "cooking / Why / are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 줄을 서고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 줄을 서고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you standing in line?",
      "Scrambled": "standing in line"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 줄을 서고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you standing in line?",
      "Scrambled": "standing / in / you / line / Why / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 네 귀를 막고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 네 귀를 막고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you covering your ears?",
      "Scrambled": "covering your ears"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 네 귀를 막고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you covering your ears?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Why / ears / you / are / covering"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 교과서를 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 교과서를 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you reading the textbook?",
      "Scrambled": "reading the textbook"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 교과서를 읽고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you reading the textbook?",
      "Scrambled": "textbook / reading / Why / the / you / are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 그렇게 일찍 잠자리에 들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 그렇게 일찍 잠자리에 들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you going to bed so early?",
      "Scrambled": "going to bed so early"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 그렇게 일찍 잠자리에 들고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you going to bed so early?",
      "Scrambled": "early / you / so / going / are / bed / Why / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 울고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 울고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you crying?",
      "Scrambled": "crying"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 울고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you crying?",
      "Scrambled": "crying / are / you / Why"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 파티를 열고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 파티를 열고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you throwing a party?",
      "Scrambled": "throwing a party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 파티를 열고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you throwing a party?",
      "Scrambled": "are / party / Why / throwing / a / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 음악을 줄이고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 음악을 줄이고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you turning down the music?",
      "Scrambled": "turning down the music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 음악을 줄이고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you turning down the music?",
      "Scrambled": "the / turning / Why / music / down / are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 큰 소리로 웃고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 큰 소리로 웃고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you laughing loud?",
      "Scrambled": "laughing loud"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 큰 소리로 웃고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you laughing loud?",
      "Scrambled": "laughing / you / are / Why / loud"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 스웨터를 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 스웨터를 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you wearing a sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "wearing a sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "Why are you -ing?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 왜 스웨터를 입고 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Why are you wearing a sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / Why / are / sweater / a / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 탄산음료를 마시는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 탄산음료를 마시는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we drink soda?",
      "Scrambled": "drink soda"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 탄산음료를 마시는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we drink soda?",
      "Scrambled": "Why / don't / we / soda / drink"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 열쇠고리를 사는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 열쇠고리를 사는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we buy a keychain?",
      "Scrambled": "buy a keychain"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 열쇠고리를 사는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we buy a keychain?",
      "Scrambled": "buy / a / Why / don't / keychain / we"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 공포 영화를 보는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 공포 영화를 보는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we watch a horror movie?",
      "Scrambled": "watch a horror movie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 공포 영화를 보는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we watch a horror movie?",
      "Scrambled": "movie / we / watch / don't / Why / horror / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 대신 콘서트에 가는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 대신 콘서트에 가는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we go to a concert instead?",
      "Scrambled": "go to a concert instead"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 대신 콘서트에 가는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we go to a concert instead?",
      "Scrambled": "to / instead / concert / don't / go / a / we / Why"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 다음 주에 만나는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 다음 주에 만나는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we get together next week?",
      "Scrambled": "get together next week"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 다음 주에 만나는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we get together next week?",
      "Scrambled": "next / don't / we / week / together / get / Why"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 후식을 좀 먹는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 후식을 좀 먹는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we have some dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "have some dessert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 후식을 좀 먹는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we have some dessert?",
      "Scrambled": "we / Why / have / dessert / some / don't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그를 위해 요리하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그를 위해 요리하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we cook for him?",
      "Scrambled": "cook for him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그를 위해 요리하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we cook for him?",
      "Scrambled": "cook / Why / for / don't / we / him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 과학 박물관을 방문하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 과학 박물관을 방문하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we visit the science museum?",
      "Scrambled": "visit the science museum"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 과학 박물관을 방문하는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we visit the science museum?",
      "Scrambled": "museum / the / we / visit / Why / science / don't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그녀를 돕는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그녀를 돕는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we help her?",
      "Scrambled": "help her"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "우리가 그녀를 돕는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we help her?",
      "Scrambled": "help / Why / her / we / don't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 좀 쉬는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 좀 쉬는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we take some rest?",
      "Scrambled": "take some rest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Why don't we …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "우리 좀 쉬는 게 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "Why don't we take some rest?",
      "Scrambled": "take / we / don't / Why / rest / some"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to stay home.",
      "Scrambled": "stay home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to stay home.",
      "Scrambled": "to / home / have / I / stay"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마를 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마를 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to help my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "help my mom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마를 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to help my mom.",
      "Scrambled": "help / have / my / to / mom / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 공부해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 공부해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to study English.",
      "Scrambled": "study English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 공부해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to study English.",
      "Scrambled": "study / I / English / to / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 숙제를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 숙제를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to do my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "do my homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 숙제를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to do my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "I / my / have / homework / do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 남동생을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 남동생을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to babysit my brother.",
      "Scrambled": "babysit my brother"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 남동생을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to babysit my brother.",
      "Scrambled": "to / I / brother / babysit / my / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지하철을 타야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지하철을 타야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to take the subway.",
      "Scrambled": "take the subway"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지하철을 타야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to take the subway.",
      "Scrambled": "I / to / take / have / subway / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to clean my room.",
      "Scrambled": "clean my room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to clean my room.",
      "Scrambled": "room / clean / my / to / have / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피아노를 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피아노를 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to practice the piano.",
      "Scrambled": "practice the piano"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피아노를 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to practice the piano.",
      "Scrambled": "piano / have / practice / the / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지금 떠나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지금 떠나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to leave now.",
      "Scrambled": "leave now"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 지금 떠나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to leave now.",
      "Scrambled": "now / leave / I / have / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to go to the bathroom.",
      "Scrambled": "go to the bathroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "I have to ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I have to go to the bathroom.",
      "Scrambled": "bathroom / I / the / have / to / go / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 일찍 일어나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 일찍 일어나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should get up early.",
      "Scrambled": "get up early"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 일찍 일어나야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should get up early.",
      "Scrambled": "should / You / up / get / early"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 치과에 가 봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 치과에 가 봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should see a dentist.",
      "Scrambled": "see a dentist"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 치과에 가 봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should see a dentist.",
      "Scrambled": "dentist / You / a / should / see"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠을 좀 자야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠을 좀 자야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should get some sleep.",
      "Scrambled": "get some sleep"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잠을 좀 자야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should get some sleep.",
      "Scrambled": "get / should / some / sleep / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 물을 더 많이 마셔야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 물을 더 많이 마셔야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should drink more water.",
      "Scrambled": "drink more water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 물을 더 많이 마셔야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should drink more water.",
      "Scrambled": "drink / should / more / water / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should practice every day.",
      "Scrambled": "practice every day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 연습해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should practice every day.",
      "Scrambled": "practice / You / should / every / day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 돈을 저축해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 돈을 저축해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should save money.",
      "Scrambled": "save money"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 돈을 저축해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should save money.",
      "Scrambled": "save / money / You / should"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아스피린을 먹어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아스피린을 먹어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should take an aspirin.",
      "Scrambled": "take an aspirin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 아스피린을 먹어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should take an aspirin.",
      "Scrambled": "should / You / take / an / aspirin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 가서 쉬어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 가서 쉬어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should go home and rest.",
      "Scrambled": "go home and rest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 집에 가서 쉬어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should go home and rest.",
      "Scrambled": "should / home / go / rest / and / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 마스크를 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 마스크를 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should wear a mask.",
      "Scrambled": "wear a mask"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 마스크를 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should wear a mask.",
      "Scrambled": "mask / a / should / wear / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should exercise every day.",
      "Scrambled": "exercise every day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "You should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You should exercise every day.",
      "Scrambled": "day / exercise / every / You / should"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나가 놀아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나가 놀아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I play outside?",
      "Scrambled": "play outside"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나가 놀아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I play outside?",
      "Scrambled": "play / I / outside / May"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I go to the movies?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 영화 보러 가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I go to the movies?",
      "Scrambled": "May / I / go / to / movies / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I have some cookies?",
      "Scrambled": "have some cookies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 쿠키를 좀 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I have some cookies?",
      "Scrambled": "have / I / some / May / cookies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I play video games?",
      "Scrambled": "play video games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 비디오 게임을 해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I play video games?",
      "Scrambled": "video / play / May / I / games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I watch my favorite TV show?",
      "Scrambled": "watch my favorite TV show"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 좋아하는 TV 쇼를 봐도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I watch my favorite TV show?",
      "Scrambled": "favorite / TV / watch / show / I / my / May"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I help you?",
      "Scrambled": "help you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 도와줘도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I help you?",
      "Scrambled": "you / I / May / help"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 준호와 통화해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 준호와 통화해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I speak to Junho?",
      "Scrambled": "speak to Junho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 준호와 통화해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I speak to Junho?",
      "Scrambled": "Junho / to / speak / May / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 뭐 좀 물어봐도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 뭐 좀 물어봐도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I ask you something?",
      "Scrambled": "ask you something"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 뭐 좀 물어봐도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I ask you something?",
      "Scrambled": "ask / something / May / you / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 써도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 써도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I use your phone?",
      "Scrambled": "use your phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 써도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I use your phone?",
      "Scrambled": "phone / use / your / May / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 의자를 가져가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 의자를 가져가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I take this chair?",
      "Scrambled": "take this chair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "May I …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 의자를 가져가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "May I take this chair?",
      "Scrambled": "chair / May / this / take / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전등을 켜 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전등을 켜 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please turn on the light?",
      "Scrambled": "turn on the light"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전등을 켜 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please turn on the light?",
      "Scrambled": "please / turn / light / the / on / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "침대를 정리해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "침대를 정리해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please make the bed?",
      "Scrambled": "make the bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "침대를 정리해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please make the bed?",
      "Scrambled": "bed / make / please / Will / the / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "책들을 치워 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "책들을 치워 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please put the books away?",
      "Scrambled": "put the books away"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "책들을 치워 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please put the books away?",
      "Scrambled": "put / away / books / please / Will / you / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "쓰레기를 내다 버려 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "쓰레기를 내다 버려 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please take out the trash?",
      "Scrambled": "take out the trash"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "쓰레기를 내다 버려 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please take out the trash?",
      "Scrambled": "trash / out / please / take / the / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 신발을 벗어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 신발을 벗어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please take off your shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "take off your shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 신발을 벗어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please take off your shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "your / off / please / take / shoes / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "냉장고를 청소해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "냉장고를 청소해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please clean the fridge?",
      "Scrambled": "clean the fridge"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "냉장고를 청소해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please clean the fridge?",
      "Scrambled": "please / clean / fridge / the / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 옷을 입어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 옷을 입어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please put on your clothes?",
      "Scrambled": "put on your clothes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네 옷을 입어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please put on your clothes?",
      "Scrambled": "please / clothes / put / on / your / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내 코트를 걸어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내 코트를 걸어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please hang up my coat?",
      "Scrambled": "hang up my coat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내 코트를 걸어 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please hang up my coat?",
      "Scrambled": "up / my / coat / please / hang / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전화를 받아 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전화를 받아 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please get the phone?",
      "Scrambled": "get the phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전화를 받아 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please get the phone?",
      "Scrambled": "get / please / the / phone / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자전거를 고쳐 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자전거를 고쳐 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please fix the bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "fix the bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Will you please …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "자전거를 고쳐 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Will you please fix the bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "bicycle / please / fix / the / Will / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to go to the restroom.",
      "Scrambled": "go to the restroom"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 화장실에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to go to the restroom.",
      "Scrambled": "go / restroom / like / to / to / the / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 박물관을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 박물관을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to visit a museum.",
      "Scrambled": "visit a museum"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 박물관을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to visit a museum.",
      "Scrambled": "visit / a / like / museum / to / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 숲에서 하이킹하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 숲에서 하이킹하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to hike in the forest.",
      "Scrambled": "hike in the forest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 숲에서 하이킹하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to hike in the forest.",
      "Scrambled": "forest / to / in / like / hike / the / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 롤러코스터를 타고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 롤러코스터를 타고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to ride a roller coaster.",
      "Scrambled": "ride a roller coaster"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 롤러코스터를 타고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to ride a roller coaster.",
      "Scrambled": "roller / like / to / a / ride / coaster / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이것을 입어보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이것을 입어보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to try this on.",
      "Scrambled": "try this on"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이것을 입어보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to try this on.",
      "Scrambled": "try / on / like / to / this / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "지호와 통화하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "지호와 통화하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to speak to Jiho.",
      "Scrambled": "speak to Jiho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "지호와 통화하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to speak to Jiho.",
      "Scrambled": "speak / Jiho / like / to / to / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아이스크림을 좀 먹고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아이스크림을 좀 먹고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to have some ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "have some ice cream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 아이스크림을 좀 먹고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to have some ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "ice / some / have / to / like / cream / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 모험적인 무언가를 하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 모험적인 무언가를 하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to do something adventurous.",
      "Scrambled": "do something adventurous"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 모험적인 무언가를 하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to do something adventurous.",
      "Scrambled": "adventurous / like / do / to / something / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 중국에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 중국에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to go to China.",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 중국에 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to go to China.",
      "Scrambled": "to / China / go / to / like / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨을 좀 주문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨을 좀 주문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to order some chicken.",
      "Scrambled": "order some chicken"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I'd like to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨을 좀 주문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'd like to order some chicken.",
      "Scrambled": "order / chicken / to / like / some / I'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마실래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마실래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to drink water?",
      "Scrambled": "drink water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물을 마실래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to drink water?",
      "Scrambled": "water / to / you / drink / like / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "뮤지컬을 보러 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "뮤지컬을 보러 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to go to a musical?",
      "Scrambled": "go to a musical"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "뮤지컬을 보러 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to go to a musical?",
      "Scrambled": "a / go / musical / to / like / you / Would / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "빵 좀 먹을래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "빵 좀 먹을래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to have some bread?",
      "Scrambled": "have some bread"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "빵 좀 먹을래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to have some bread?",
      "Scrambled": "bread / have / some / to / like / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "테니스 경기를 볼래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "테니스 경기를 볼래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to watch a tennis match?",
      "Scrambled": "watch a tennis match"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "테니스 경기를 볼래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to watch a tennis match?",
      "Scrambled": "tennis / match / a / watch / to / like / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 위한 선물을 살래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 위한 선물을 살래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to buy a gift for him?",
      "Scrambled": "buy a gift for him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그를 위해 선물을 살래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to buy a gift for him?",
      "Scrambled": "buy / him / for / a / to / gift / like / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리와 함께 할래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리와 함께 할래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to join us?",
      "Scrambled": "join us"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "우리와 함께 할래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to join us?",
      "Scrambled": "like / us / join / to / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "집에서 쉴래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "집에서 쉴래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to rest at home?",
      "Scrambled": "rest at home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "집에서 쉴래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to rest at home?",
      "Scrambled": "rest / at / like / home / to / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "벤치에 앉을래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "벤치에 앉을래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to sit on a bench?",
      "Scrambled": "sit on a bench"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "벤치에 앉을래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to sit on a bench?",
      "Scrambled": "on / sit / to / like / you / Would / a / bench"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to go to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the library"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "도서관에 갈래?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to go to the library?",
      "Scrambled": "library / to / go / to / the / like / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "메시지를 남기시겠어요?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "메시지를 남기시겠어요?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to leave a message?",
      "Scrambled": "leave a message"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Would you like to …?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "메시지를 남기시겠어요?",
      "English/Answer": "Would you like to leave a message?",
      "Scrambled": "message / a / leave / to / like / you / Would"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 일곱 시 정각에 일어나.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 일곱 시 정각에 일어나.",
      "English/Answer": "I usually get up at seven o'clock.",
      "Scrambled": "get up at seven o'clock"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 일곱 시 정각에 일어나.",
      "English/Answer": "I usually get up at seven o'clock.",
      "Scrambled": "up / o'clock / get / usually / at / seven / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 아침을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 아침을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "I always eat breakfast.",
      "Scrambled": "eat breakfast"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 아침을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "I always eat breakfast.",
      "Scrambled": "eat / always / breakfast / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 시리얼을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 시리얼을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "I often have cereal.",
      "Scrambled": "have cereal"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 시리얼을 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "I often have cereal.",
      "Scrambled": "cereal / have / often / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 때때로 버스를 타.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 때때로 버스를 타.",
      "English/Answer": "I sometimes take the bus.",
      "Scrambled": "take the bus"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 때때로 버스를 타.",
      "English/Answer": "I sometimes take the bus.",
      "Scrambled": "sometimes / the / take / bus / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 결코 학교에 걸어가지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 결코 학교에 걸어가지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I never walk to school.",
      "Scrambled": "walk to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 결코 학교에 걸어가지 않아.",
      "English/Answer": "I never walk to school.",
      "Scrambled": "walk / school / to / never / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 밤에 TV를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 밤에 TV를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "I usually watch TV at night.",
      "Scrambled": "watch TV at night"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 보통 밤에 TV를 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "I usually watch TV at night.",
      "Scrambled": "night / at / TV / watch / usually / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 내 숙제를 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 내 숙제를 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I always do my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "do my homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 내 숙제를 해.",
      "English/Answer": "I always do my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "my / do / always / I / homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 인터넷을 검색해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 인터넷을 검색해.",
      "English/Answer": "I often surf the internet.",
      "Scrambled": "surf the internet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 인터넷을 검색해.",
      "English/Answer": "I often surf the internet.",
      "Scrambled": "often / internet / the / surf / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 일기를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 일기를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "I always write in my diary.",
      "Scrambled": "write in my diary"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 항상 일기를 써.",
      "English/Answer": "I always write in my diary.",
      "Scrambled": "diary / in / write / always / my / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 록 음악을 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 록 음악을 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I often listen to rock music.",
      "Scrambled": "listen to rock music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "I usually [always, often, sometimes, never] ….",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "나는 종종 록 음악을 들어.",
      "English/Answer": "I often listen to rock music.",
      "Scrambled": "rock / to / listen / often / music / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그만 말해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그만 말해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop talking.",
      "Scrambled": "talking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그만 말해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop talking.",
      "Scrambled": "talking / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "손뼉 그만 쳐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "손뼉 그만 쳐.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop clapping.",
      "Scrambled": "clapping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "손뼉 그만 쳐.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop clapping.",
      "Scrambled": "clapping / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "TV 그만 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "TV 그만 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watching TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "TV 그만 봐.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop watching TV.",
      "Scrambled": "watching / TV / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "컴퓨터 게임 그만 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "컴퓨터 게임 그만 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop playing computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "playing computer games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "컴퓨터 게임 그만 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop playing computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "games / playing / computer / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스쿠터 운전하는 것을 멈춰.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스쿠터 운전하는 것을 멈춰.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop driving your scooter.",
      "Scrambled": "driving your scooter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "네 스쿠터 운전하는 것을 멈춰.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop driving your scooter.",
      "Scrambled": "scooter / your / driving / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "노래 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "노래 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop singing.",
      "Scrambled": "singing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "노래 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop singing.",
      "Scrambled": "singing / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "농구 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "농구 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop playing basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "playing basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "농구 그만해.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop playing basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "playing / basketball / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "종이컵 그만 써.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "종이컵 그만 써.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop using paper cups.",
      "Scrambled": "using paper cups"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "종이컵 그만 써.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop using paper cups.",
      "Scrambled": "using / paper / cups / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "초콜릿 그만 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "초콜릿 그만 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop eating chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "eating chocolate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "초콜릿 그만 먹어.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop eating chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "chocolate / eating / Stop"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "복도에서 그만 뛰어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "복도에서 그만 뛰어.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop running in the hallway.",
      "Scrambled": "running in the hallway"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Stop –ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "복도에서 그만 뛰어.",
      "English/Answer": "Stop running in the hallway.",
      "Scrambled": "in / hallway / the / running / Stop"
    }
  ],
  "Level C Book 1": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to hear that.",
      "Scrambled": "to hear that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to hear that.",
      "Scrambled": "hear / glad / I'm / that / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그를 다시 봐서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그를 다시 봐서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to see him again.",
      "Scrambled": "to see him again"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그를 다시 봐서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to see him again.",
      "Scrambled": "see / glad / him / to / again / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 돌아와서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 돌아와서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to be back home.",
      "Scrambled": "to be back home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 돌아와서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to be back home.",
      "Scrambled": "back / be / to / home / glad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 이제 몸이 좋아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 이제 몸이 좋아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you are well now.",
      "Scrambled": "you are well now"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 이제 몸이 좋아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you are well now.",
      "Scrambled": "well / are / you / now / glad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 비행기를 놓치지 않아서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 비행기를 놓치지 않아서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad she didn't miss the flight.",
      "Scrambled": "she didn't miss the flight"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 비행기를 놓치지 않아서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad she didn't miss the flight.",
      "Scrambled": "flight / didn't / miss / glad / she / I'm / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너와 함께 가서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너와 함께 가서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to go with you.",
      "Scrambled": "to go with you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너와 함께 가서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to go with you.",
      "Scrambled": "to / you / glad / I'm / with / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 너를 도울 수 있어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 너를 도울 수 있어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad I can help you.",
      "Scrambled": "I can help you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 너를 도울 수 있어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad I can help you.",
      "Scrambled": "can / help / I'm / glad / you / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 그게 마음이 든다니 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 그게 마음이 든다니 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you like it.",
      "Scrambled": "you like it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 그게 마음이 든다니 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you like it.",
      "Scrambled": "it / you / like / glad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 만나서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 만나서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to meet you.",
      "Scrambled": "to meet you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 만나서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to meet you.",
      "Scrambled": "meet / to / you / glad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to hear the news.",
      "Scrambled": "to hear the news"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 소식을 들어서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad to hear the news.",
      "Scrambled": "hear / news / to / the / glad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 표를 구해서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 표를 구해서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad we got tickets.",
      "Scrambled": "we got tickets"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 표를 구해서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad we got tickets.",
      "Scrambled": "got / we / tickets / I'm / glad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 기분이 더 나아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 기분이 더 나아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you're feeling better.",
      "Scrambled": "you're feeling better"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 1,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm glad ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 기분이 더 나아져서 기뻐.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm glad you're feeling better.",
      "Scrambled": "better / you're / feeling / I'm / glad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그건 틀린 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그건 틀린 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid that's wrong.",
      "Scrambled": "that's wrong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그건 틀린 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid that's wrong.",
      "Scrambled": "wrong / that's / I'm / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 널 도울 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 널 도울 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I can’t help you.",
      "Scrambled": "I can’t help you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 널 도울 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I can’t help you.",
      "Scrambled": "help / I / afraid / I'm / can’t / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 늦을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 늦을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we will be late.",
      "Scrambled": "we will be late"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 늦을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we will be late.",
      "Scrambled": "we / be / late / will / I'm / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그가 여기에 오지 않을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그가 여기에 오지 않을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid he isn't coming here.",
      "Scrambled": "he isn't coming here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그가 여기에 오지 않을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid he isn't coming here.",
      "Scrambled": "isn't / here / he / coming / afraid / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 실수한 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 실수한 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid you made a mistake.",
      "Scrambled": "you made a mistake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 실수한 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid you made a mistake.",
      "Scrambled": "mistake / you / made / a / I'm / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 내가 시간이 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 내가 시간이 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I don't have time.",
      "Scrambled": "I don't have time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 내가 시간이 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I don't have time.",
      "Scrambled": "have / don't / time / I / afraid / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 길을 잃은 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 길을 잃은 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we're lost.",
      "Scrambled": "we're lost"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 길을 잃은 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we're lost.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / lost / we're / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리 팀이 질 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리 팀이 질 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid our team will lose.",
      "Scrambled": "our team will lose"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리 팀이 질 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid our team will lose.",
      "Scrambled": "team / will / lose / our / I'm / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 이해가 되지 않는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 이해가 되지 않는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I don't understand.",
      "Scrambled": "I don't understand"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 이해가 되지 않는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I don't understand.",
      "Scrambled": "don't / understand / I / afraid / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그걸 할 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그걸 할 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I can't do that.",
      "Scrambled": "I can't do that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 그걸 할 수 없을 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid I can't do that.",
      "Scrambled": "I / do / that / afraid / can't / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 선택의 여지가 없는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 선택의 여지가 없는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we have no choice.",
      "Scrambled": "we have no choice"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 우리가 선택의 여지가 없는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid we have no choice.",
      "Scrambled": "choice / no / have / we / afraid / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 내 자리에 앉아 있는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 내 자리에 앉아 있는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid you're sitting in my seat.",
      "Scrambled": "you're sitting in my seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 2,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm afraid ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "유감이지만 난 네가 내 자리에 앉아 있는 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm afraid you're sitting in my seat.",
      "Scrambled": "seat / you're / sitting / in / I'm / my / afraid"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 말을 들으니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 말을 들으니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to hear that.",
      "Scrambled": "to hear that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 말을 들으니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to hear that.",
      "Scrambled": "to / hear / that / sorry / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너를 방해해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너를 방해해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to bother you.",
      "Scrambled": "to bother you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "너를 방해해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to bother you.",
      "Scrambled": "sorry / bother / you / I'm / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 늦어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 늦어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I'm late.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm late"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 늦어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I'm late.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / late / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 엄마가 편찮으시다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 엄마가 편찮으시다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry your mom is sick.",
      "Scrambled": "your mom is sick"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 엄마가 편찮으시다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry your mom is sick.",
      "Scrambled": "sick / your / mom / is / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 콘서트를 놓치다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 콘서트를 놓치다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I missed your concert.",
      "Scrambled": "I missed your concert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 콘서트를 놓치다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I missed your concert.",
      "Scrambled": "concert / missed / I / sorry / I'm / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 떠들어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 떠들어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I made noise.",
      "Scrambled": "I made noise"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 떠들어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I made noise.",
      "Scrambled": "noise / made / I / sorry / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 네 전화기를 잃어버렸다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 네 전화기를 잃어버렸다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry you lost your phone.",
      "Scrambled": "you lost your phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "네가 네 전화기를 잃어버렸다니 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry you lost your phone.",
      "Scrambled": "sorry / lost / you / I'm / phone / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 발을 밟아서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 발을 밟아서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I stepped on your foot.",
      "Scrambled": "I stepped on your foot"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 발을 밟아서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I stepped on your foot.",
      "Scrambled": "stepped / on / foot / I / your / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "널 방해하게 되어 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "널 방해하게 되어 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to interrupt you.",
      "Scrambled": "to interrupt you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "널 방해하게 되어 유감이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to interrupt you.",
      "Scrambled": "interrupt / to / you / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 널 기다리게 해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 널 기다리게 해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to keep you waiting.",
      "Scrambled": "to keep you waiting"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 널 기다리게 해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry to keep you waiting.",
      "Scrambled": "you / waiting / to / keep / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 갈 수 없어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 갈 수 없어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I broke your cup.",
      "Scrambled": "I broke your cup"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 갈 수 없어서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I broke your cup.",
      "Scrambled": "I / broke / your / cup / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 약속을 어겨서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 약속을 어겨서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I left you alone.",
      "Scrambled": "I left you alone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 약속을 어겨서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I left you alone.",
      "Scrambled": "you / I / left / alone / I'm / sorry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 13,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 이어폰을 찾지 못해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 13,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 이어폰을 찾지 못해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I can't find your earphones.",
      "Scrambled": "I can't find your earphones"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 3,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm sorry ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 13,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 이어폰을 찾지 못해서 미안해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm sorry I can't find your earphones.",
      "Scrambled": "can't / your / earphones / I / I'm / sorry / find"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 케이트가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 케이트가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about Kate.",
      "Scrambled": "Kate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 케이트가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about Kate.",
      "Scrambled": "worried / Kate / about / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 개가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 개가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my dog.",
      "Scrambled": "my dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 개가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my dog.",
      "Scrambled": "dog / my / about / I'm / worried"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수학 시험이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수학 시험이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the math test.",
      "Scrambled": "the math test"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 수학 시험이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the math test.",
      "Scrambled": "the / math / test / worried / I'm / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 체중이 느는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 체중이 느는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about gaining weight.",
      "Scrambled": "gaining weight"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 체중이 느는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about gaining weight.",
      "Scrambled": "weight / I'm / worried / about / gaining"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사람들 앞에서 말하는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사람들 앞에서 말하는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about speaking in front of people.",
      "Scrambled": "speaking in front of people"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사람들 앞에서 말하는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about speaking in front of people.",
      "Scrambled": "people / of / in / speaking / front / about / I'm / worried"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 외모가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 외모가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my looks.",
      "Scrambled": "my looks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 외모가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my looks.",
      "Scrambled": "my / looks / worried / I'm / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 날씨가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 날씨가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the weather.",
      "Scrambled": "the weather"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 날씨가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the weather.",
      "Scrambled": "weather / about / the / worried / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마의 건강이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마의 건강이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my mom's health.",
      "Scrambled": "my mom's health"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 엄마의 건강이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my mom's health.",
      "Scrambled": "mom's / about / worried / I'm / my / health"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 성적이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 성적이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my grade.",
      "Scrambled": "my grade"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 성적이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about my grade.",
      "Scrambled": "my / grade / about / worried / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 말하기 대회가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 말하기 대회가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the speech contest.",
      "Scrambled": "the speech contest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 말하기 대회가 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about the speech contest.",
      "Scrambled": "contest / speech / the / about / I'm / worried"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 길을 잃는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 길을 잃는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about getting lost.",
      "Scrambled": "getting lost"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 길을 잃는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about getting lost.",
      "Scrambled": "getting / worried / about / I'm / lost"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새 친구들을 사귀는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새 친구들을 사귀는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about making new friends.",
      "Scrambled": "making new friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 4,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm worried about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새 친구들을 사귀는 것이 걱정돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm worried about making new friends.",
      "Scrambled": "friends / making / new / about / I'm / worried"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우주에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우주에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the universe.",
      "Scrambled": "the universe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우주에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the universe.",
      "Scrambled": "universe / curious / the / I'm / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 발명품들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 발명품들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about his inventions.",
      "Scrambled": "his inventions"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 발명품들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about his inventions.",
      "Scrambled": "inventions / curious / his / about / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피자의 기원에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피자의 기원에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the origin of pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "the origin of pizza"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 피자의 기원에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the origin of pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "pizza / origin / the / about / of / I'm / curious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 작문 주제에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 작문 주제에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your writing topic.",
      "Scrambled": "your writing topic"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 작문 주제에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your writing topic.",
      "Scrambled": "writing / curious / your / topic / I'm / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 축구 규칙들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 축구 규칙들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the rules for football.",
      "Scrambled": "the rules for football"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 축구 규칙들에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about the rules for football.",
      "Scrambled": "rules / for / football / the / about / I'm / curious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 셰익스피어에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 셰익스피어에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about Shakespeare.",
      "Scrambled": "Shakespeare"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 셰익스피어에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about Shakespeare.",
      "Scrambled": "about / Shakespeare / curious / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 클래식 음악에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 클래식 음악에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about classical music.",
      "Scrambled": "classical music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고전 음악에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about classical music.",
      "Scrambled": "curious / classical / music / about / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 부산 여행에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 부산 여행에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your trip to Busan.",
      "Scrambled": "your trip to Busan"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너의 부산 여행에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your trip to Busan.",
      "Scrambled": "Busan / trip / your / to / about / curious / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 삶에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 삶에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about his life.",
      "Scrambled": "his life"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 삶에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about his life.",
      "Scrambled": "life / his / about / I'm / curious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 게임에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 게임에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about this game.",
      "Scrambled": "this game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 게임에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about this game.",
      "Scrambled": "game / this / curious / I'm / about"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국 역사에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국 역사에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about Korean history.",
      "Scrambled": "Korean history"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국 역사에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about Korean history.",
      "Scrambled": "Korean / history / about / I'm / curious"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 새 친구에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 새 친구에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your new friend.",
      "Scrambled": "your new friend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 5,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm curious about ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네 새 친구에 대해 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm curious about your new friend.",
      "Scrambled": "friend / your / new / about / curious / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 놀이 기구가 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 놀이 기구가 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of rides.",
      "Scrambled": "rides"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 놀이 기구가 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of rides.",
      "Scrambled": "rides / of / I'm / scared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 뱀이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 뱀이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of snakes.",
      "Scrambled": "snakes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 뱀이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of snakes.",
      "Scrambled": "scared / of / I'm / snakes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트 타는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트 타는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of skating.",
      "Scrambled": "skating"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트 타는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of skating.",
      "Scrambled": "of / skating / scared / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험에 떨어지는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험에 떨어지는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of failing the test.",
      "Scrambled": "failing the test"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험에 떨어지는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of failing the test.",
      "Scrambled": "the / failing / of / scared / test / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치과에 가는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치과에 가는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of going to the dentist.",
      "Scrambled": "going to the dentist"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치과에 가는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of going to the dentist.",
      "Scrambled": "the / going / dentist / to / of / I'm / scared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 야생 동물이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 야생 동물이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of wild animals.",
      "Scrambled": "wild animals"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 야생 동물이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of wild animals.",
      "Scrambled": "animals / wild / of / scared / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of swimming in the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "swimming in the sea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of swimming in the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "in / sea / swimming / the / of / I'm / scared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 사람들을 만나는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 사람들을 만나는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of meeting new people.",
      "Scrambled": "meeting new people"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 사람들을 만나는 것이 두려워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of meeting new people.",
      "Scrambled": "new / people / meeting / of / scared / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 번지 점프하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 번지 점프하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of bungee jumping.",
      "Scrambled": "bungee jumping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 번지 점프하는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of bungee jumping.",
      "Scrambled": "jumping / bungee / of / scared / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 높이 오르는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 높이 오르는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of climbing high.",
      "Scrambled": "climbing high"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 높이 오르는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of climbing high.",
      "Scrambled": "climbing / of / scared / high / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공포 영화를 보는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공포 영화를 보는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of watching horror movies.",
      "Scrambled": "watching horror movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공포 영화를 보는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of watching horror movies.",
      "Scrambled": "horror / movies / watching / of / I'm / scared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밤에 혼자 걷는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밤에 혼자 걷는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of walking alone at night.",
      "Scrambled": "walking alone at night"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 6,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm scared of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밤에 혼자 걷는 것이 무서워.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm scared of walking alone at night.",
      "Scrambled": "walking / at / night / of / alone / I'm / scared"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음식을 요리하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음식을 요리하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to cook food.",
      "Scrambled": "cook food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 음식을 요리하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to cook food.",
      "Scrambled": "supposed / food / cook / to / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to clean my room.",
      "Scrambled": "clean my room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 방을 청소하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to clean my room.",
      "Scrambled": "clean / supposed / room / my / to / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밴드에서 연주하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밴드에서 연주하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to play in a band.",
      "Scrambled": "play in a band"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밴드에서 연주하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to play in a band.",
      "Scrambled": "in / play / to / supposed / I'm / a / band"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 마술 묘기를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 마술 묘기를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to do magic tricks.",
      "Scrambled": "do magic tricks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 마술 묘기를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to do magic tricks.",
      "Scrambled": "do / magic / to / I'm / tricks / supposed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저녁 외식하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저녁 외식하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to go out for dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "go out for dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 저녁 외식하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to go out for dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "go / out / I'm / supposed / dinner / for / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소피아를 만나기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소피아를 만나기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to meet Sophia.",
      "Scrambled": "meet Sophia"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소피아를 만나기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to meet Sophia.",
      "Scrambled": "Sophia / meet / to / supposed / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 7시까지 집에 가기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 7시까지 집에 가기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to go home by seven.",
      "Scrambled": "go home by seven"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 7시까지 집에 가기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to go home by seven.",
      "Scrambled": "to / seven / go / supposed / I'm / home / by"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그에게 3시에 전화하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그에게 3시에 전화하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to call him at three.",
      "Scrambled": "call him at three"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그에게 3시에 전화하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to call him at three.",
      "Scrambled": "him / at / call / to / three / supposed / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험공부를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험공부를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to study for the exam.",
      "Scrambled": "study for the exam"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 시험공부를 하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to study for the exam.",
      "Scrambled": "study / supposed / the / for / I'm / to / exam"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 이메일을 보내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 이메일을 보내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to send this email.",
      "Scrambled": "send this email"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이 이메일을 보내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to send this email.",
      "Scrambled": "this / send / supposed / I'm / email / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 할머니를 방문하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 할머니를 방문하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to visit my grandmother.",
      "Scrambled": "visit my grandmother"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 할머니를 방문하기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to visit my grandmother.",
      "Scrambled": "visit / grandmother / supposed / I'm / my / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오늘 그것을 끝내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오늘 그것을 끝내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to finish it today.",
      "Scrambled": "finish it today"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 7,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm supposed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오늘 그것을 끝내기로 되어 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm supposed to finish it today.",
      "Scrambled": "today / to / it / finish / supposed / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 샐러드를 먹을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 샐러드를 먹을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of having salad.",
      "Scrambled": "having salad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 샐러드를 먹을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of having salad.",
      "Scrambled": "thinking / having / of / salad / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화책을 읽을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화책을 읽을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of reading comic books.",
      "Scrambled": "reading comic books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화책을 읽을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of reading comic books.",
      "Scrambled": "of / comic / reading / thinking / books / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤 동아리에 가입할 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤 동아리에 가입할 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of joining a dance club.",
      "Scrambled": "joining a dance club"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤 동아리에 가입할 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of joining a dance club.",
      "Scrambled": "of / club / a / dance / I'm / joining / thinking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 가장 좋아하는 원피스를 입을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 가장 좋아하는 원피스를 입을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of wearing my favorite dress.",
      "Scrambled": "wearing my favorite dress"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 가장 좋아하는 원피스를 입을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of wearing my favorite dress.",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / of / thinking / dress / my / favorite / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 드럼 연주하는 걸 배울 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 드럼 연주하는 걸 배울 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of learning to play the drums.",
      "Scrambled": "learning to play the drums"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 드럼 연주하는 걸 배울 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of learning to play the drums.",
      "Scrambled": "the / learning / of / drums / thinking / play / to / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 스케이트보드를 탈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 스케이트보드를 탈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of riding my skateboard.",
      "Scrambled": "riding my skateboard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 스케이트보드를 탈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of riding my skateboard.",
      "Scrambled": "thinking / riding / I'm / my / of / skateboard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 서점에 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 서점에 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of going to the bookstore.",
      "Scrambled": "going to the bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 서점에 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of going to the bookstore.",
      "Scrambled": "thinking / the / bookstore / going / to / of / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 영화를 볼 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 영화를 볼 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of watching a movie this weekend.",
      "Scrambled": "watching a movie this weekend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 영화를 볼 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of watching a movie this weekend.",
      "Scrambled": "weekend / this / watching / movie / thinking / a / of / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑을 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑을 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of going camping.",
      "Scrambled": "going camping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑을 갈 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of going camping.",
      "Scrambled": "of / camping / I'm / going / thinking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업을 들을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업을 들을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of taking the art class.",
      "Scrambled": "taking the art class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업을 들을 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of taking the art class.",
      "Scrambled": "art / class / the / taking / of / thinking / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 놀 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 놀 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of hanging out with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "hanging out with friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 놀 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of hanging out with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "friends / out / hanging / of / with / I'm / thinking"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 옷을 살 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 옷을 살 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of buying clothes this weekend.",
      "Scrambled": "buying clothes this weekend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 8,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm thinking of ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이번 주말에 옷을 살 생각이야.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm thinking of buying clothes this weekend.",
      "Scrambled": "buying / this / thinking / weekend / clothes / of / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 올해를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 올해를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to this year.",
      "Scrambled": "this year"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 올해를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to this year.",
      "Scrambled": "to / forward / year / I'm / looking / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 콘서트를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 콘서트를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the concert.",
      "Scrambled": "the concert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 콘서트를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the concert.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / I'm / to / the / forward / concert"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리의 현장 학습을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리의 현장 학습을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to our field trip.",
      "Scrambled": "our field trip"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리의 현장 학습을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to our field trip.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / field / forward / our / trip / to / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 다시 보는 것을 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 다시 보는 것을 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to seeing you again.",
      "Scrambled": "seeing you again"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 다시 보는 것을 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to seeing you again.",
      "Scrambled": "you / seeing / looking / again / forward / to / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 반 친구들을 만나는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 반 친구들을 만나는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to meeting new classmates.",
      "Scrambled": "meeting new classmates"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 새로운 반 친구들을 만나는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to meeting new classmates.",
      "Scrambled": "I'm / looking / forward / to / new / classmates / meeting"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 학교 축제를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 학교 축제를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the school festival.",
      "Scrambled": "the school festival"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 학교 축제를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the school festival.",
      "Scrambled": "forward / looking / to / school / I'm / festival / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 다음 주 토요일을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 다음 주 토요일을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to next Saturday.",
      "Scrambled": "next Saturday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 다음 주 토요일을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to next Saturday.",
      "Scrambled": "Saturday / next / to / looking / I'm / forward"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여행 가는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여행 가는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to going on a trip.",
      "Scrambled": "going on a trip"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여행 가는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to going on a trip.",
      "Scrambled": "trip / going / a / looking / forward / to / on / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울 방학을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울 방학을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to winter vacation.",
      "Scrambled": "winter vacation"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울 방학을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to winter vacation.",
      "Scrambled": "vacation / looking / forward / to / I'm / winter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전시회를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전시회를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the exhibition.",
      "Scrambled": "the exhibition"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전시회를 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to the exhibition.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / exhibition / I'm / the / to / forward"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to swimming in the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "swimming in the sea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 바다에서 수영하는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to swimming in the sea.",
      "Scrambled": "looking / sea / the / swimming / to / forward / I'm / in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너에게 소식을 듣는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너에게 소식을 듣는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to hearing from you.",
      "Scrambled": "hearing from you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 9,
      "Pattern Name": "I'm looking forward to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너에게 소식을 듣는 것을 기대하고 있어.",
      "English/Answer": "I'm looking forward to hearing from you.",
      "Scrambled": "hearing / from / looking / forward / to / you / I'm"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제시간에 와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제시간에 와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to be on time.",
      "Scrambled": "be on time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 제시간에 와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to be on time.",
      "Scrambled": "You're / time / be / expected / on / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 종이를 절약해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 종이를 절약해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to save paper.",
      "Scrambled": "save paper"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 종이를 절약해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to save paper.",
      "Scrambled": "paper / to / expected / You're / save"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업에 참여해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업에 참여해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to participate in class.",
      "Scrambled": "participate in class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업에 참여해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to participate in class.",
      "Scrambled": "class / participate / expected / in / to / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 발표를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 발표를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to give a presentation.",
      "Scrambled": "give a presentation"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 발표를 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to give a presentation.",
      "Scrambled": "expected / a / to / give / presentation / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 친구들과 잘 지내야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 친구들과 잘 지내야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to get along with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "get along with friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 친구들과 잘 지내야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to get along with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "expected / friends / get / with / You're / along / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공부를 열심히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공부를 열심히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to study hard.",
      "Scrambled": "study hard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 공부를 열심히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to study hard.",
      "Scrambled": "expected / study / hard / to / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 부모님께 말씀드려야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 부모님께 말씀드려야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to tell your parents.",
      "Scrambled": "tell your parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 부모님께 말씀드려야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to tell your parents.",
      "Scrambled": "expected / parents / your / to / tell / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 식물들을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 식물들을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to take care of your plants.",
      "Scrambled": "take care of your plants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 식물들을 돌봐야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to take care of your plants.",
      "Scrambled": "plants / of / care / take / your / to / expected / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "wear a helmet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "expected / helmet / a / You're / to / wear"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 정오까지 돌아와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 정오까지 돌아와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to be back by noon.",
      "Scrambled": "be back by noon"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 정오까지 돌아와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to be back by noon.",
      "Scrambled": "noon / be / back / by / You're / to / expected"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도움이 필요한 사람들을 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도움이 필요한 사람들을 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to help people in need.",
      "Scrambled": "help people in need"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 도움이 필요한 사람들을 도와야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to help people in need.",
      "Scrambled": "need / expected / in / people / to / You're / help"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교통 법규를 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교통 법규를 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to follow traffic rules.",
      "Scrambled": "follow traffic rules"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 10,
      "Pattern Name": "You're expected to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교통 법규를 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You're expected to follow traffic rules.",
      "Scrambled": "rules / to / follow / You're / traffic / expected"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 만지면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 만지면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to touch it.",
      "Scrambled": "touch it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 만지면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to touch it.",
      "Scrambled": "it / allowed / You're / to / not / touch"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물을 데려오면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물을 데려오면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to bring pets.",
      "Scrambled": "bring pets"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물을 데려오면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to bring pets.",
      "Scrambled": "allowed / bring / pets / to / You're / not"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시끄럽게 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시끄럽게 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to make noise.",
      "Scrambled": "make noise"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 시끄럽게 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to make noise.",
      "Scrambled": "make / allowed / not / to / You're / noise"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 설탕을 너무 많이 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 설탕을 너무 많이 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to eat too much sugar.",
      "Scrambled": "eat too much sugar"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 설탕을 너무 많이 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to eat too much sugar.",
      "Scrambled": "much / allowed / eat / not / too / sugar / to / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기서 휴대 전화를 사용하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기서 휴대 전화를 사용하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to use a cell phone here.",
      "Scrambled": "use a cell phone here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 여기서 휴대 전화를 사용하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to use a cell phone here.",
      "Scrambled": "phone / allowed / here / cell / not / use / a / to / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화를 보면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화를 보면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to watch the movie.",
      "Scrambled": "watch the movie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화를 보면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to watch the movie.",
      "Scrambled": "movie / the / watch / not / allowed / You're / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 박물관에서 사진을 찍으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 박물관에서 사진을 찍으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to take pictures in the museum.",
      "Scrambled": "take pictures in the museum"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 박물관에서 사진을 찍으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to take pictures in the museum.",
      "Scrambled": "take / pictures / in / museum / the / not / allowed / to / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 9시 이후에 피아노를 연습하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 9시 이후에 피아노를 연습하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to practice the piano after 9 p.m.",
      "Scrambled": "practice the piano after 9 p.m."
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 9시 이후에 피아노를 연습하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to practice the piano after 9 p.m.",
      "Scrambled": "the / after / 9 p.m. / practice / piano / not / You're / allowed / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 하루 종일 게임을 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 하루 종일 게임을 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to play games all day.",
      "Scrambled": "play games all day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 하루 종일 게임을 하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to play games all day.",
      "Scrambled": "all / games / to / day / play / allowed / not / You're"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교실에서 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교실에서 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to eat in class.",
      "Scrambled": "eat in class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교실에서 먹으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to eat in class.",
      "Scrambled": "eat / not / allowed / class / in / You're / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 대출하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 대출하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to check out this book.",
      "Scrambled": "check out this book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책을 대출하면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to check out this book.",
      "Scrambled": "out / check / this / book / not / allowed / You're / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잔디 위를 걸으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잔디 위를 걸으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to walk on the grass.",
      "Scrambled": "walk on the grass"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 11,
      "Pattern Name": "You're not allowed to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 잔디 위를 걸으면 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You're not allowed to walk on the grass.",
      "Scrambled": "on / grass / the / walk / allowed / You're / not / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 소식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 소식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the news?",
      "Scrambled": "the news"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 소식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the news?",
      "Scrambled": "happy / you / Are / with / news / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 스웨터에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 스웨터에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "your sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 스웨터에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Are / with / sweater / happy / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 제안에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 제안에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with my proposal?",
      "Scrambled": "my proposal"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 제안에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with my proposal?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / proposal / you / my / with / happy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 결정에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 결정에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with our decision?",
      "Scrambled": "our decision"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 결정에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with our decision?",
      "Scrambled": "decision / with / our / happy / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 새 집에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 새 집에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your new house?",
      "Scrambled": "your new house"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 새 집에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your new house?",
      "Scrambled": "house / with / your / Are / new / you / happy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그의 대답에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그의 대답에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with his answer?",
      "Scrambled": "his answer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그의 대답에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with his answer?",
      "Scrambled": "answer / happy / his / with / you / Are"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 시험 결과에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 시험 결과에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the test result?",
      "Scrambled": "the test result"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 시험 결과에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the test result?",
      "Scrambled": "with / test / result / Are / happy / you / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 교복에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 교복에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your school uniform?",
      "Scrambled": "your school uniform"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 교복에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your school uniform?",
      "Scrambled": "uniform / you / happy / school / your / Are / with"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 음식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 음식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the food?",
      "Scrambled": "the food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 음식에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with the food?",
      "Scrambled": "the / with / food / happy / Are / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 수업들에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 수업들에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your classes?",
      "Scrambled": "your classes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 수업들에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your classes?",
      "Scrambled": "with / classes / your / Are / happy / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리의 서비스에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리의 서비스에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with our service?",
      "Scrambled": "our service"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리의 서비스에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with our service?",
      "Scrambled": "you / happy / with / Are / service / our"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 자리에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 자리에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your seat?",
      "Scrambled": "your seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 12,
      "Pattern Name": "Are you happy with ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 자리에 만족하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are you happy with your seat?",
      "Scrambled": "you / Are / with / seat / your / happy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "헬멧을 쓰는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "헬멧을 쓰는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "wear a helmet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "헬멧을 쓰는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "helmet / a / to / important / wear / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "책을 많이 읽는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "책을 많이 읽는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to read many books.",
      "Scrambled": "read many books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "책을 많이 읽는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to read many books.",
      "Scrambled": "read / many / important / to / It's / books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "서로를 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "서로를 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to trust each other.",
      "Scrambled": "trust each other"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "서로를 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to trust each other.",
      "Scrambled": "trust / other / important / to / each / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "건강에 좋은 음식을 먹는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "건강에 좋은 음식을 먹는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to eat healthy food.",
      "Scrambled": "eat healthy food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "건강에 좋은 음식을 먹는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to eat healthy food.",
      "Scrambled": "important / eat / healthy / to / food / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "수업 시간에 참여하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "수업 시간에 참여하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to participate in class.",
      "Scrambled": "participate in class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "수업 시간에 참여하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to participate in class.",
      "Scrambled": "in / participate / class / to / important / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "돈을 절약하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "돈을 절약하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to save money.",
      "Scrambled": "save money"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "돈을 절약하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to save money.",
      "Scrambled": "important / save / money / to / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "최선을 다하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "최선을 다하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to do your best.",
      "Scrambled": "do your best"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "최선을 다하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to do your best.",
      "Scrambled": "do / your / to / best / important / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "매일 영어를 공부하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "매일 영어를 공부하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to study English every day.",
      "Scrambled": "study English every day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "매일 영어를 공부하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to study English every day.",
      "Scrambled": "day / study / English / important / to / every / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꿈을 갖는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꿈을 갖는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to have a dream.",
      "Scrambled": "have a dream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꿈을 갖는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to have a dream.",
      "Scrambled": "dream / have / to / a / important / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "규칙적으로 운동하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "규칙적으로 운동하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to exercise regularly.",
      "Scrambled": "exercise regularly"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "규칙적으로 운동하는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to exercise regularly.",
      "Scrambled": "to / regularly / exercise / important / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "제시간에 오는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "제시간에 오는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to be on time.",
      "Scrambled": "be on time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "제시간에 오는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to be on time.",
      "Scrambled": "on / time / to / important / be / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "너 자신을 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "너 자신을 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to believe in yourself.",
      "Scrambled": "believe in yourself"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 13,
      "Pattern Name": "It's important to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "너 자신을 믿는 것이 중요해.",
      "English/Answer": "It's important to believe in yourself.",
      "Scrambled": "believe / in / to / yourself / important / It's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 자니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 자니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your ruler?",
      "Scrambled": "ruler"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 자니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your ruler?",
      "Scrambled": "your / ruler / this / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 우산이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 우산이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your umbrella?",
      "Scrambled": "umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 우산이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your umbrella?",
      "Scrambled": "this / your / umbrella / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "여기가 네 자리니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "여기가 네 자리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your seat?",
      "Scrambled": "seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "여기가 네 자리니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your seat?",
      "Scrambled": "seat / Is / your / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람이 네 여동생이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람이 네 여동생이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your sister?",
      "Scrambled": "sister"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "이 사람이 네 여동생이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your sister?",
      "Scrambled": "this / sister / Is / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 처음이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 처음이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your first time?",
      "Scrambled": "first time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 처음이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your first time?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Is / time / this / first"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 배낭이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 배낭이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your backpack?",
      "Scrambled": "backpack"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 배낭이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your backpack?",
      "Scrambled": "backpack / Is / that / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 아파트니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 아파트니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your apartment?",
      "Scrambled": "apartment"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "저기가 네 아파트니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your apartment?",
      "Scrambled": "apartment / your / Is / that"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람은 네 반 친구니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람은 네 반 친구니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your classmate?",
      "Scrambled": "classmate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저 사람이 네 반 친구니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your classmate?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Is / that / classmate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 전화번호니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 전화번호니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your phone number?",
      "Scrambled": "phone number"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "이것은 네 전화번호니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your phone number?",
      "Scrambled": "this / your / phone / number / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your room?",
      "Scrambled": "room"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 방이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your room?",
      "Scrambled": "your / that / room / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 기차표니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 기차표니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your train ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "train ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "저것은 네 기차표니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is that your train ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "train / Is / that / ticket / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 첫 방문이니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 첫 방문이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your first visit?",
      "Scrambled": "first visit"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 14,
      "Pattern Name": "Is this your ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이번이 네 첫 방문이니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is this your first visit?",
      "Scrambled": "first / Is / visit / this / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기에 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기에 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "sit here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기에 앉아도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I sit here?",
      "Scrambled": "sit / okay / here / Is / it / if / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 케이크를 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 케이크를 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I eat the cake?",
      "Scrambled": "eat the cake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 케이크를 먹어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I eat the cake?",
      "Scrambled": "I / okay / cake / if / eat / the / it / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 자전거를 타도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 자전거를 타도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I ride this bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "ride this bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 자전거를 타도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I ride this bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "bicycle / this / ride / if / okay / I / it / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 사용해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 사용해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I use your phone?",
      "Scrambled": "use your phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화기를 사용해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I use your phone?",
      "Scrambled": "your / Is / phone / I / it / if / okay / use"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 선풍기를 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 선풍기를 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I turn on the fan?",
      "Scrambled": "turn on the fan"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 선풍기를 켜도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I turn on the fan?",
      "Scrambled": "turn / fan / if / on / the / okay / it / Is / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 충전기를 빌려도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 충전기를 빌려도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I borrow your charger?",
      "Scrambled": "borrow your charger"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 충전기를 빌려도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I borrow your charger?",
      "Scrambled": "borrow / your / if / charger / it / Is / I / okay"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 오늘 네 셔츠를 입어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 오늘 네 셔츠를 입어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I wear your shirt today?",
      "Scrambled": "wear your shirt today"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 오늘 네 셔츠를 입어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I wear your shirt today?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / today / shirt / wear / it / your / okay / I / if"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "제가 9시까지 집에 와도 될까요?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "제가 9시까지 집에 와도 될까요?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I come home by nine?",
      "Scrambled": "come home by nine"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "제가 9시까지 집에 와도 될까요?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I come home by nine?",
      "Scrambled": "if / come / nine / it / home / okay / I / by / Is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 들어가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 들어가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I come in?",
      "Scrambled": "come in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 들어가도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I come in?",
      "Scrambled": "I / if / it / come / okay / Is / in"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 TV를 꺼도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 TV를 꺼도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I turn off the TV?",
      "Scrambled": "turn off the TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 TV를 꺼도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I turn off the TV?",
      "Scrambled": "TV / Is / off / I / it / turn / okay / if / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나중에 내 방을 청소해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나중에 내 방을 청소해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I clean my room later?",
      "Scrambled": "clean my room later"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 나중에 내 방을 청소해도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I clean my room later?",
      "Scrambled": "my / room / it / clean / if / I / okay / Is / later"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기서 사진을 찍어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기서 사진을 찍어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I take photos here?",
      "Scrambled": "take photos here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 15,
      "Pattern Name": "Is it okay if I ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 여기서 사진을 찍어도 될까?",
      "English/Answer": "Is it okay if I take photos here?",
      "Scrambled": "okay / if / Is / here / it / photos / take / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any water?",
      "Scrambled": "water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "물이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any water?",
      "Scrambled": "water / there / Is / any"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "남은 음식이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "남은 음식이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any food left?",
      "Scrambled": "food left"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "남은 음식이 좀 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any food left?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / any / food / left / there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "특별한 이유가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "특별한 이유가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any special reason?",
      "Scrambled": "special reason"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "특별한 이유가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any special reason?",
      "Scrambled": "any / special / there / Is / reason"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "해야 할 숙제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "해야 할 숙제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any homework to do?",
      "Scrambled": "homework to do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "해야 할 숙제가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any homework to do?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / do / any / there / to / homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "질문들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "질문들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any questions?",
      "Scrambled": "questions"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "질문들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any questions?",
      "Scrambled": "questions / Are / there / any"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "근처에 식당들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "근처에 식당들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any restaurants nearby?",
      "Scrambled": "restaurants nearby"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "근처에 식당들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any restaurants nearby?",
      "Scrambled": "nearby / there / any / Are / restaurants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내일 계획들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내일 계획들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any plans for tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "plans for tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내일 계획들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any plans for tomorrow?",
      "Scrambled": "plans / there / Are / any / tomorrow / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "새로운 아이디어들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "새로운 아이디어들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any new ideas?",
      "Scrambled": "new ideas"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "새로운 아이디어들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any new ideas?",
      "Scrambled": "there / new / ideas / Are / any"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "좋은 소식들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "좋은 소식들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any good news?",
      "Scrambled": "good news"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "좋은 소식들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any good news?",
      "Scrambled": "news / there / good / Is / any"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "세일 중인 품목들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "세일 중인 품목들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any items on sale?",
      "Scrambled": "items on sale"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "세일 중인 품목들이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any items on sale?",
      "Scrambled": "Are / items / any / sale / there / on"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "다른 방법이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "다른 방법이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any other way?",
      "Scrambled": "other way"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "다른 방법이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Is there any other way?",
      "Scrambled": "Is / there / other / way / any"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "나에게 온 메시지가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "나에게 온 메시지가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any messages for me?",
      "Scrambled": "messages for me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 16,
      "Pattern Name": "Is/Are there any ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "나에게 온 메시지가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Are there any messages for me?",
      "Scrambled": "messages / there / any / Are / me / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 노래 부르는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 노래 부르는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy singing.",
      "Scrambled": "singing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 노래 부르는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy singing.",
      "Scrambled": "I / singing / enjoy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빵 굽는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빵 굽는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy baking bread.",
      "Scrambled": "baking bread"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빵 굽는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy baking bread.",
      "Scrambled": "baking / I / enjoy / bread"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사진 찍는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사진 찍는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy taking pictures.",
      "Scrambled": "taking pictures"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사진 찍는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy taking pictures.",
      "Scrambled": "taking / enjoy / pictures / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화 그리는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화 그리는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy drawing cartoons.",
      "Scrambled": "drawing cartoons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 만화 그리는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy drawing cartoons.",
      "Scrambled": "drawing / cartoons / enjoy / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공상 과학 영화 보는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공상 과학 영화 보는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy watching sci-fi movies.",
      "Scrambled": "watching sci-fi movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 공상 과학 영화 보는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy watching sci-fi movies.",
      "Scrambled": "movies / sci-fi / enjoy / I / watching"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이야기 쓰는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이야기 쓰는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy writing stories.",
      "Scrambled": "writing stories"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 이야기 쓰는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy writing stories.",
      "Scrambled": "stories / writing / enjoy / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 웹 서핑하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 웹 서핑하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy surfing the web.",
      "Scrambled": "surfing the web"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 웹 검색하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy surfing the web.",
      "Scrambled": "web / enjoy / the / I / surfing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 축구 하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 축구 하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy playing soccer with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "playing soccer with friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 친구들과 축구 하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy playing soccer with friends.",
      "Scrambled": "friends / with / soccer / enjoy / playing / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식물 키우는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식물 키우는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy growing plants.",
      "Scrambled": "growing plants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식물 키우는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy growing plants.",
      "Scrambled": "growing / enjoy / I / plants"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤추는 것을 매우 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤추는 것을 매우 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy dancing very much.",
      "Scrambled": "dancing very much"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤추는 것을 매우 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy dancing very much.",
      "Scrambled": "enjoy / much / very / I / dancing"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매운 음식 먹는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매운 음식 먹는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy eating spicy food.",
      "Scrambled": "eating spicy food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매운 음식 먹는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy eating spicy food.",
      "Scrambled": "enjoy / food / I / spicy / eating"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 주말마다 등산하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 주말마다 등산하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy climbing the mountains on weekends.",
      "Scrambled": "climbing the mountains on weekends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 17,
      "Pattern Name": "I enjoy -ing.",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 주말마다 등산하는 것을 즐겨.",
      "English/Answer": "I enjoy climbing the mountains on weekends.",
      "Scrambled": "weekends / mountains / climbing / on / enjoy / the / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 곧 볼 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 곧 볼 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to see you soon.",
      "Scrambled": "to see you soon"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 너를 곧 볼 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to see you soon.",
      "Scrambled": "to / hope / see / I / soon / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 반장이 되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 반장이 되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to be a class leader.",
      "Scrambled": "to be a class leader"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 반장이 되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to be a class leader.",
      "Scrambled": "to / class / a / be / leader / I / hope"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트보드 타는 걸 배우기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트보드 타는 걸 배우기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to learn to skateboard.",
      "Scrambled": "to learn to skateboard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 스케이트보드 타는 걸 배우기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to learn to skateboard.",
      "Scrambled": "learn / I / hope / to / skateboard / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 올 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 올 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope he can come.",
      "Scrambled": "he can come"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 올 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope he can come.",
      "Scrambled": "hope / come / can / I / he"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 다음번에 더 잘하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 다음번에 더 잘하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you do better next time.",
      "Scrambled": "you do better next time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 다음번에 더 잘하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you do better next time.",
      "Scrambled": "do / better / next / hope / time / you / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 많은 친구들을 사귀기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 많은 친구들을 사귀기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to make many friends.",
      "Scrambled": "to make many friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 많은 친구들을 사귀기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to make many friends.",
      "Scrambled": "friends / I / many / make / to / hope"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 곧 낫기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 곧 낫기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope he gets well soon.",
      "Scrambled": "he gets well soon"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 곧 낫기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope he gets well soon.",
      "Scrambled": "soon / he / hope / I / gets / well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 기타를 칠 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 기타를 칠 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope I can play the guitar someday.",
      "Scrambled": "I can play the guitar someday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 기타를 칠 수 있기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope I can play the guitar someday.",
      "Scrambled": "play / can / I / hope / guitar / the / I / someday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 영어 실력이 향상되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 영어 실력이 향상되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to improve my English.",
      "Scrambled": "to improve my English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 영어 실력이 향상되기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to improve my English.",
      "Scrambled": "to / I / English / improve / my / hope"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 지갑을 찾기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 지갑을 찾기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you find your wallet.",
      "Scrambled": "you find your wallet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 지갑을 찾기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you find your wallet.",
      "Scrambled": "wallet / you / find / I / your / hope"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국의 많은 곳을 여행하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국의 많은 곳을 여행하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to travel to many places in Korea.",
      "Scrambled": "to travel to many places in Korea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한국의 많은 곳을 여행하기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope to travel to many places in Korea.",
      "Scrambled": "in / many / hope / I / Korea / travel / places / to / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 숙제를 제시간에 끝내기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 숙제를 제시간에 끝내기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you finish your homework on time.",
      "Scrambled": "you finish your homework on time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 18,
      "Pattern Name": "I hope ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 숙제를 제시간에 끝내기를 바라.",
      "English/Answer": "I hope you finish your homework on time.",
      "Scrambled": "homework / finish / your / time / you / I / hope / on"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 개보다 고양이를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 개보다 고양이를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer cats to dogs.",
      "Scrambled": "cats to dogs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 개보다 고양이를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer cats to dogs.",
      "Scrambled": "prefer / I / cats / to / dogs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어보다 수학을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어보다 수학을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer math to English.",
      "Scrambled": "math to English"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어보다 수학을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer math to English.",
      "Scrambled": "English / I / to / math / prefer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨보다 피자를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨보다 피자를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer pizza to chicken.",
      "Scrambled": "pizza to chicken"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 치킨보다 피자를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer pizza to chicken.",
      "Scrambled": "to / pizza / I / prefer / chicken"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울보다 여름을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울보다 여름을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer summer to winter.",
      "Scrambled": "summer to winter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 겨울보다 여름을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer summer to winter.",
      "Scrambled": "summer / winter / prefer / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 농구보다 야구를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 농구보다 야구를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer baseball to basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "baseball to basketball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 농구보다 야구를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer baseball to basketball.",
      "Scrambled": "to / basketball / I / prefer / baseball"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소설보다 만화책을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소설보다 만화책을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer comic books to novels.",
      "Scrambled": "comic books to novels"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 소설보다 만화책을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer comic books to novels.",
      "Scrambled": "prefer / to / novels / books / comic / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 록 음악보다 클래식 음악을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 록 음악보다 클래식 음악을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer classical music to rock music.",
      "Scrambled": "classical music to rock music"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 록 음악보다 클래식 음악을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer classical music to rock music.",
      "Scrambled": "prefer / to / classical / music / rock / music / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 책 읽는 것보다 영화 보는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 책 읽는 것보다 영화 보는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer watching movies to reading books.",
      "Scrambled": "watching movies to reading books"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 책 읽는 것보다 영화 보는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer watching movies to reading books.",
      "Scrambled": "to / reading / movies / books / I / watching / prefer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사탕보다 초콜릿을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사탕보다 초콜릿을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer chocolate to candy.",
      "Scrambled": "chocolate to candy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 사탕보다 초콜릿을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer chocolate to candy.",
      "Scrambled": "to / prefer / candy / I / chocolate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 산보다 바다를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 산보다 바다를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer oceans to mountains.",
      "Scrambled": "oceans to mountains"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 산보다 바다를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer oceans to mountains.",
      "Scrambled": "prefer / I / mountains / oceans / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 생머리보다 곱슬머리를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 생머리보다 곱슬머리를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer curly hair to straight hair.",
      "Scrambled": "curly hair to straight hair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 생머리보다 곱슬머리를 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer curly hair to straight hair.",
      "Scrambled": "hair / curly / hair / straight / prefer / to / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밖에서 노는 것보다 집에 있는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밖에서 노는 것보다 집에 있는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer staying at home to playing outside.",
      "Scrambled": "staying at home to playing outside"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 19,
      "Pattern Name": "I prefer ~ to ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 밖에서 노는 것보다 집에 있는 것을 더 좋아해.",
      "English/Answer": "I prefer staying at home to playing outside.",
      "Scrambled": "staying / to / prefer / at / playing / outside / home / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 올 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 올 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if you can come.",
      "Scrambled": "if you can come"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 올 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if you can come.",
      "Scrambled": "can / you / wonder / if / I / come"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀의 직업이 무엇인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀의 직업이 무엇인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder what her job is.",
      "Scrambled": "what her job is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀의 직업이 무엇인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder what her job is.",
      "Scrambled": "is / wonder / job / her / what / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 왜 결석했는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 왜 결석했는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder why he's absent.",
      "Scrambled": "why he's absent"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 왜 결석했는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder why he's absent.",
      "Scrambled": "wonder / why / I / absent / he's"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 건물이 얼마나 높은지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 건물이 얼마나 높은지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder how tall the building is.",
      "Scrambled": "how tall the building is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 건물이 얼마나 높은지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder how tall the building is.",
      "Scrambled": "how / building / wonder / tall / I / is / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 서점이 언제 문을 닫았는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 서점이 언제 문을 닫았는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder when the bookstore closed.",
      "Scrambled": "when the bookstore closed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 서점이 언제 문을 닫았는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder when the bookstore closed.",
      "Scrambled": "the / closed / bookstore / wonder / I / when"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 할인을 받을 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 할인을 받을 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if I can get a discount.",
      "Scrambled": "if I can get a discount"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내가 할인을 받을 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if I can get a discount.",
      "Scrambled": "get / wonder / I / can / discount / I / if / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 상자 안에 무엇이 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 상자 안에 무엇이 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder what’s in the box.",
      "Scrambled": "what’s in the box"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 상자 안에 무엇이 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder what’s in the box.",
      "Scrambled": "what’s / box / in / wonder / I / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 지금 어디에 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 지금 어디에 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder where we are now.",
      "Scrambled": "where we are now"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 우리가 지금 어디에 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder where we are now.",
      "Scrambled": "we / I / where / now / are / wonder"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 누구인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 누구인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder who she is.",
      "Scrambled": "who she is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 누구인지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder who she is.",
      "Scrambled": "she / is / who / wonder / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 키가 얼마나 큰지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 키가 얼마나 큰지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder how tall he is.",
      "Scrambled": "how tall he is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그가 키가 얼마나 큰지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder how tall he is.",
      "Scrambled": "wonder / is / he / tall / how / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 날 도와줄 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 날 도와줄 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if you can help me.",
      "Scrambled": "if you can help me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 네가 날 도와줄 수 있는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder if you can help me.",
      "Scrambled": "if / me / wonder / can / I / help / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 왜 그렇게 화가 났는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 왜 그렇게 화가 났는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder why she was so upset.",
      "Scrambled": "why she was so upset"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 20,
      "Pattern Name": "I wonder ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그녀가 왜 그렇게 화가 났는지 궁금해.",
      "English/Answer": "I wonder why she was so upset.",
      "Scrambled": "she / wonder / upset / was / why / so / I"
    }
  ],
  "Level C Book 2": [
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to skateboard?",
      "Scrambled": "skateboard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 스케이트보드 타는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to skateboard?",
      "Scrambled": "know / Do / to / you / skateboard / how"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 고치는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 고치는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to fix a computer?",
      "Scrambled": "fix a computer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 고치는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to fix a computer?",
      "Scrambled": "how / computer / fix / know / Do / you / to / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요구르트 만드는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요구르트 만드는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to make yogurt?",
      "Scrambled": "make yogurt"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요구르트 만드는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to make yogurt?",
      "Scrambled": "make / how / yogurt / Do / you / know / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 전자 메일 보내는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 전자 메일 보내는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to send emails?",
      "Scrambled": "send emails"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 전자 메일 보내는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to send emails?",
      "Scrambled": "to / emails / send / Do / how / you / know"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 세탁기 사용하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 세탁기 사용하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to use a washing machine?",
      "Scrambled": "use a washing machine"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 세탁기 사용하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to use a washing machine?",
      "Scrambled": "washing / use / machine / know / to / you / a / Do / how"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뜨개질하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뜨개질하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to knit?",
      "Scrambled": "knit"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 뜨개질 하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to knit?",
      "Scrambled": "know / knit / how / you / to / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 씨앗 키우는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 씨앗 키우는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to grow seeds?",
      "Scrambled": "grow seeds"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 씨앗 키우는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to grow seeds?",
      "Scrambled": "how / Do / grow / to / you / seeds / know"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국제 전화 거는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국제 전화 거는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to make an international call?",
      "Scrambled": "make an international call"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 국제 전화 거는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to make an international call?",
      "Scrambled": "how / an / know / call / you / make / Do / to / international"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to swim?",
      "Scrambled": "swim"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수영하는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to swim?",
      "Scrambled": "know / to / how / swim / Do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 체스 두는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 체스 두는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to play chess?",
      "Scrambled": "play chess"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 체스 두는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to play chess?",
      "Scrambled": "how / play / you / to / know / chess / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 문제 푸는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 문제 푸는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to solve this problem?",
      "Scrambled": "solve this problem"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 문제 푸는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to solve this problem?",
      "Scrambled": "solve / problem / how / you / know / to / this / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거기에 가는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거기에 가는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to get there?",
      "Scrambled": "get there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 21,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you know how to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거기에 가는 방법을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you know how to get there?",
      "Scrambled": "get / there / how / know / you / Do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember him?",
      "Scrambled": "him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember him?",
      "Scrambled": "him / Do / remember / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 스웨터를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 스웨터를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember this sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "this sweater"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 스웨터를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember this sweater?",
      "Scrambled": "remember / sweater / you / this / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속초 가족 여행을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속초 가족 여행을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember the family trip to Sokcho?",
      "Scrambled": "the family trip to Sokcho"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속초 가족 여행을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember the family trip to Sokcho?",
      "Scrambled": "Do / Sokcho / you / remember / to / trip / the / family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 6학년 때 선생님을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 6학년 때 선생님을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember our 6th grade teacher?",
      "Scrambled": "our 6th grade teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리 6학년 때 선생님을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember our 6th grade teacher?",
      "Scrambled": "6th / remember / you / teacher / Do / grade / our"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에게 서울대공원에 대해 이야기했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에게 서울대공원에 대해 이야기했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember telling me about the Seoul Grand Park?",
      "Scrambled": "telling me about the Seoul Grand Park"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에게 서울대공원에 대해 이야기했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember telling me about the Seoul Grand Park?",
      "Scrambled": "Grand / Seoul / me / you / telling / Do / remember / about / the / Park"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 노래를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 노래를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember this song?",
      "Scrambled": "this song"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 노래를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember this song?",
      "Scrambled": "remember / this / you / Do / song"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 장난감의 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 장난감의 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember the name of this toy?",
      "Scrambled": "the name of this toy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 장난감의 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember the name of this toy?",
      "Scrambled": "the / remember / Do / name / this / of / toy / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 작년 축구 경기를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 작년 축구 경기를 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember last year's soccer match?",
      "Scrambled": "last year's soccer match"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 작년 축구 시합을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember last year's soccer match?",
      "Scrambled": "remember / Do / year's / you / soccer / last / match"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember my name?",
      "Scrambled": "my name"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 이름을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember my name?",
      "Scrambled": "my / remember / Do / name / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 엄마의 생신을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 엄마의 생신을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember Mom's birthday?",
      "Scrambled": "Mom's birthday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 엄마의 생신을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember Mom's birthday?",
      "Scrambled": "remember / birthday / Do / Mom's / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너의 지난 여름 방학을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너의 지난 여름 방학을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember your last summer vacation?",
      "Scrambled": "your last summer vacation"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너의 지난 여름 방학을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember your last summer vacation?",
      "Scrambled": "vacation / summer / remember / your / last / Do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리가 한옥 마을에 방문했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리가 한옥 마을에 방문했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember our visit to the Hanok Village?",
      "Scrambled": "our visit to the Hanok Village"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 22,
      "Pattern Name": "Do you remember ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우리가 한옥 마을에 방문했던 것을 기억하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do you remember our visit to the Hanok Village?",
      "Scrambled": "Village / visit / the / remember / to / our / you / Do / Hanok"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 머리 모양에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 머리 모양에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of my hair?",
      "Scrambled": "my hair"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 머리 모양에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of my hair?",
      "Scrambled": "hair / my / of / think / you / do / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of the movie?",
      "Scrambled": "the movie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 영화에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of the movie?",
      "Scrambled": "movie / the / of / think / What / you / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 계획에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 계획에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of this plan?",
      "Scrambled": "this plan"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 계획에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of this plan?",
      "Scrambled": "plan / this / of / think / do / What / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물 기르는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물 기르는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of raising a pet?",
      "Scrambled": "raising a pet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 애완동물 기르는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of raising a pet?",
      "Scrambled": "you / a / pet / think / do / What / raising / of"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교복 입는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교복 입는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of wearing school uniforms?",
      "Scrambled": "wearing school uniforms"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 교복 입는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of wearing school uniforms?",
      "Scrambled": "wearing / uniforms / school / of / think / you / do / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 새 책가방에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 새 책가방에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of my new backpack?",
      "Scrambled": "my new backpack"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 내 새 책가방에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of my new backpack?",
      "Scrambled": "backpack / my / think / of / new / do / What / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of computer games?",
      "Scrambled": "computer games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of computer games?",
      "Scrambled": "think / games / What / of / you / computer / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 영어 캠프에 참여하는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 영어 캠프에 참여하는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of joining an English camp?",
      "Scrambled": "joining an English camp"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 영어 캠프에 참여하는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of joining an English camp?",
      "Scrambled": "joining / an / camp / think / English / you / of / do / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of me?",
      "Scrambled": "me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 나에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of me?",
      "Scrambled": "of / you / What / me / do / think"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of this book?",
      "Scrambled": "this book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 이 책에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of this book?",
      "Scrambled": "do / book / of / this / you / think / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악 수업에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악 수업에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of music class?",
      "Scrambled": "music class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음악 수업에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of music class?",
      "Scrambled": "class / you / music / of / think / do / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해외 여행에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해외 여행에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of traveling abroad?",
      "Scrambled": "traveling abroad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 23,
      "Pattern Name": "What do you think of ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해외 여행에 대해 어떻게 생각하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What do you think of traveling abroad?",
      "Scrambled": "traveling / of / think / abroad / do / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is there?",
      "Scrambled": "is there"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is there?",
      "Scrambled": "else / What / there / is"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 밖에 무엇이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 밖에 무엇이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do I need?",
      "Scrambled": "do I need"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 밖에 무엇이 필요하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do I need?",
      "Scrambled": "What / need / I / else / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에 대해 그 밖에 무엇을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에 대해 그 밖에 무엇을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do you know about him?",
      "Scrambled": "do you know about him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에 대해 그 밖에 무엇을 아니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do you know about him?",
      "Scrambled": "him / else / about / do / know / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 오늘 그 밖에 무엇을 할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 오늘 그 밖에 무엇을 할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else can we do today?",
      "Scrambled": "can we do today"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 오늘 그 밖에 무엇을 할 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else can we do today?",
      "Scrambled": "else / do / we / What / today / can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 런던에서 그 밖에 무엇을 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 런던에서 그 밖에 무엇을 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you see in London?",
      "Scrambled": "did you see in London"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 런던에서 그 밖에 무엇을 보았니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you see in London?",
      "Scrambled": "did / in / you / else / London / What / see"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 새롭니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 새롭니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is new?",
      "Scrambled": "is new"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 무엇이 새롭니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is new?",
      "Scrambled": "else / new / is / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 그 밖에 무엇을 살 필요가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 그 밖에 무엇을 살 필요가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do we need to buy?",
      "Scrambled": "do we need to buy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우린 그 밖에 무엇을 살 필요가 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do we need to buy?",
      "Scrambled": "do / What / else / buy / need / to / we"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 밖에 무엇을 찾았니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 밖에 무엇을 찾았니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you find?",
      "Scrambled": "did you find"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 밖에 무엇을 찾았니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you find?",
      "Scrambled": "did / find / else / What / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 할 일이 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 할 일이 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is there to do?",
      "Scrambled": "is there to do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 할 일이 무엇이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else is there to do?",
      "Scrambled": "do / is / there / What / to / else"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 내가 너를 위해 무엇을 해 줄 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 내가 너를 위해 무엇을 해 줄 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else can I do for you?",
      "Scrambled": "can I do for you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그 밖에 내가 너를 위해 무엇을 해 줄 수 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else can I do for you?",
      "Scrambled": "can / I / What / else / you / for / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "그에게 그 밖에 무슨 말을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "그에게 그 밖에 무슨 말을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you say to him?",
      "Scrambled": "did you say to him"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "그에게 그 밖에 무슨 말을 했니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else did you say to him?",
      "Scrambled": "did / say / him / else / to / you / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 밖에 무엇을 챙겨야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 밖에 무엇을 챙겨야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do I need to pack?",
      "Scrambled": "do I need to pack"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 24,
      "Pattern Name": "What else ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 그 밖에 무엇을 챙겨야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "What else do I need to pack?",
      "Scrambled": "pack / do / to / I / need / else / What"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 팔찌는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 팔찌는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the bracelet?",
      "Scrambled": "the bracelet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "그 팔찌는 어떠니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the bracelet?",
      "Scrambled": "the / like / do / bracelet / How / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그 브로콜리 수프는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그 브로콜리 수프는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the broccoli soup?",
      "Scrambled": "the broccoli soup"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "그 브로콜리 수프는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the broccoli soup?",
      "Scrambled": "the / like / How / do / broccoli / soup / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자전거는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자전거는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like this bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "this bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "이 자전거는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like this bicycle?",
      "Scrambled": "How / like / bicycle / do / this / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your jacket?",
      "Scrambled": "your jacket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "네 재킷이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your jacket?",
      "Scrambled": "do / like / your / jacket / How / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새 컴퓨터 게임이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새 컴퓨터 게임이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the new computer game?",
      "Scrambled": "the new computer game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "그 새 컴퓨터 게임이 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the new computer game?",
      "Scrambled": "like / the / computer / new / game / How / you / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 담임 선생님은 어떠시니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 담임 선생님은 어떠시니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your homeroom teacher?",
      "Scrambled": "your homeroom teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "네 담임 선생님은 어떠시니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your homeroom teacher?",
      "Scrambled": "like / teacher / your / homeroom / How / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 사진 전시회는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 사진 전시회는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the photo exhibition?",
      "Scrambled": "the photo exhibition"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "그 사진 전시회는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the photo exhibition?",
      "Scrambled": "How / like / photo / the / exhibition / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 새 휴대 전화가 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 새 휴대 전화가 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your new cell phone?",
      "Scrambled": "your new cell phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "네 새 휴대 전화가 마음에 드니?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your new cell phone?",
      "Scrambled": "like / phone / your / new / cell / How / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 음식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 음식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the food?",
      "Scrambled": "the food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "그 음식은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like the food?",
      "Scrambled": "do / you / food / like / How / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 아이디어는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 아이디어는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like my idea?",
      "Scrambled": "my idea"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내 아이디어는 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like my idea?",
      "Scrambled": "you / do / idea / like / my / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 기타 수업은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 기타 수업은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your guitar lessons?",
      "Scrambled": "your guitar lessons"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 기타 수업은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like your guitar lessons?",
      "Scrambled": "do / guitar / your / lessons / like / How / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like these shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "these shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 25,
      "Pattern Name": "How do you like ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 신발은 어때?",
      "English/Answer": "How do you like these shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "like / shoes / these / How / do / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you exercise?",
      "Scrambled": "exercise"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 운동하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you exercise?",
      "Scrambled": "do / How / exercise / you / often"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 책을 읽니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 책을 읽니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you read a book?",
      "Scrambled": "read a book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 책을 읽니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you read a book?",
      "Scrambled": "book / you / read / often / a / How / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 햄버거를 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 햄버거를 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you eat hamburgers?",
      "Scrambled": "eat hamburgers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 햄버거를 먹니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you eat hamburgers?",
      "Scrambled": "hamburgers / do / eat / How / often / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 학교에 걸어가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 학교에 걸어가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you walk to school?",
      "Scrambled": "walk to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 학교에 걸어가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you walk to school?",
      "Scrambled": "walk / often / How / school / do / to / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 개에게 먹이를 주니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 개에게 먹이를 주니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you feed your dog?",
      "Scrambled": "feed your dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 개에게 먹이를 주니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you feed your dog?",
      "Scrambled": "your / often / How / feed / you / do / dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "get a haircut"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 머리카락을 자르니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you get a haircut?",
      "Scrambled": "How / a / haircut / often / get / you / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 체육관에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 체육관에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you go to the gym?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the gym"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 체육관에 가니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you go to the gym?",
      "Scrambled": "How / often / go / gym / to / do / you / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 조부모님을 방문하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 조부모님을 방문하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you visit your grandparents?",
      "Scrambled": "visit your grandparents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 네 조부모님을 방문하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you visit your grandparents?",
      "Scrambled": "your / often / How / visit / grandparents / you / do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 외식하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 외식하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you eat out?",
      "Scrambled": "eat out"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 외식하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you eat out?",
      "Scrambled": "do / often / out / eat / you / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 인터넷을 사용하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 인터넷을 사용하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you use the internet?",
      "Scrambled": "use the internet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 인터넷을 사용하니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you use the internet?",
      "Scrambled": "use / internet / often / the / you / do / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 늦게까지 깨어 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 늦게까지 깨어 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you stay up late?",
      "Scrambled": "stay up late"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 늦게까지 깨어 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you stay up late?",
      "Scrambled": "up / late / often / stay / do / you / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 아침을 거르니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 아침을 거르니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you skip breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "skip breakfast"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 26,
      "Pattern Name": "How often do you ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 얼마나 자주 아침을 거르니?",
      "English/Answer": "How often do you skip breakfast?",
      "Scrambled": "do / breakfast / often / you / skip / How"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치킨샐러드로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치킨샐러드로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a chicken salad.",
      "Scrambled": "a chicken salad"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치킨샐러드로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a chicken salad.",
      "Scrambled": "have / chicken / I'll / salad / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오렌지주스로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오렌지주스로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have an orange juice.",
      "Scrambled": "an orange juice"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오렌지주스로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have an orange juice.",
      "Scrambled": "I'll / juice / have / orange / an"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "전 딸기아이스크림으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "전 딸기아이스크림으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have strawberry ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "strawberry ice cream"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "전 딸기아이스크림으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have strawberry ice cream.",
      "Scrambled": "strawberry / ice / I'll / cream / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "전 햄버거 두 개로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "전 햄버거 두 개로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have two hamburgers.",
      "Scrambled": "two hamburgers"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "전 햄버거 두 개로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have two hamburgers.",
      "Scrambled": "hamburgers / two / I'll / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "전 중간 크기의 피자로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "전 중간 크기의 피자로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a medium pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "a medium pizza"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "전 중간 크기의 피자로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a medium pizza.",
      "Scrambled": "medium / pizza / I'll / a / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "전 콜라로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "전 콜라로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a cola.",
      "Scrambled": "a cola"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "전 콜라로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a cola.",
      "Scrambled": "have / I'll / cola / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "전 애플파이로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "전 애플파이로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have an apple pie.",
      "Scrambled": "an apple pie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "전 애플파이로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have an apple pie.",
      "Scrambled": "have / I'll / pie / apple / an"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "전 버터가 든 팝콘으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "전 버터가 든 팝콘으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have popcorn with butter.",
      "Scrambled": "popcorn with butter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "전 버터가 든 팝콘으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have popcorn with butter.",
      "Scrambled": "I'll / with / have / popcorn / butter"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전 팬케이크로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전 팬케이크로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have pancakes.",
      "Scrambled": "pancakes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "전 팬케이크로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have pancakes.",
      "Scrambled": "I'll / pancakes / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "전 핫초코로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "전 핫초코로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a hot chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "a hot chocolate"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "전 핫초코로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a hot chocolate.",
      "Scrambled": "hot / chocolate / I'll / a / have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오늘의 수프로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오늘의 수프로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have the soup of the day.",
      "Scrambled": "the soup of the day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "전 오늘의 수프로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have the soup of the day.",
      "Scrambled": "of / day / soup / have / I'll / the / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치즈버거와 감자튀김으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치즈버거와 감자튀김으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a cheeseburger and French fries.",
      "Scrambled": "a cheeseburger and French fries"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 27,
      "Pattern Name": "I'll have ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "전 치즈버거와 감자튀김으로 할게요.",
      "English/Answer": "I'll have a cheeseburger and French fries.",
      "Scrambled": "French / fries / a / have / I'll / cheeseburger / and"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 여행이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 여행이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the trip.",
      "Scrambled": "for the trip"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 여행이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the trip.",
      "Scrambled": "trip / wait / can't / I / for / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 경기가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 경기가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the game.",
      "Scrambled": "for the game"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 경기가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the game.",
      "Scrambled": "wait / for / can't / game / I / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to camp.",
      "Scrambled": "to camp"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 캠핑이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to camp.",
      "Scrambled": "to / camp / wait / I / can't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 다시 돌아가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 다시 돌아가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to go back again.",
      "Scrambled": "to go back again"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 다시 돌아가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to go back again.",
      "Scrambled": "wait / again / I / to / can't / back / go"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 내 오래된 친구들을 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 내 오래된 친구들을 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to see my old friends.",
      "Scrambled": "to see my old friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 내 오래된 친구들을 보고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to see my old friends.",
      "Scrambled": "wait / friends / see / old / I / to / my / can't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 파티가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 파티가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the party.",
      "Scrambled": "for the party"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 파티가 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the party.",
      "Scrambled": "can't / wait / for / party / I / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 영화 보러 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 영화 보러 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to go to the movies.",
      "Scrambled": "to go to the movies"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 영화 보러 가고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to go to the movies.",
      "Scrambled": "go / wait / to / I / movies / can't / the / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 홍콩에 있는 내 사촌을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 홍콩에 있는 내 사촌을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to visit my cousin in Hong Kong.",
      "Scrambled": "to visit my cousin in Hong Kong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨리 홍콩에 있는 내 사촌을 방문하고 싶어.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to visit my cousin in Hong Kong.",
      "Scrambled": "Hong / to / cousin / wait / visit / Kong / my / I / in / can't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the art class.",
      "Scrambled": "for the art class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 미술 수업이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for the art class.",
      "Scrambled": "class / can't / the / wait / art / for / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 방학이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 방학이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for my vacation.",
      "Scrambled": "for my vacation"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 방학이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait for my vacation.",
      "Scrambled": "wait / for / vacation / can't / I / my"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 새 책을 읽는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 새 책을 읽는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to read his new book.",
      "Scrambled": "to read his new book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그의 새 책을 읽는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to read his new book.",
      "Scrambled": "wait / can't / his / read / new / I / to / book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 선물들을 열어보는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 선물들을 열어보는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to open my presents.",
      "Scrambled": "to open my presents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 28,
      "Pattern Name": "I can't wait ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 선물들을 열어보는 것이 기대돼.",
      "English/Answer": "I can't wait to open my presents.",
      "Scrambled": "open / wait / my / I / to / presents / can't"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속도를 줄여야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속도를 줄여야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must slow down.",
      "Scrambled": "slow down"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 속도를 줄여야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must slow down.",
      "Scrambled": "down / must / You / slow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 에너지를 아껴야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 에너지를 아껴야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must save energy.",
      "Scrambled": "save energy"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 에너지를 아껴야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must save energy.",
      "Scrambled": "energy / You / save / must"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "wear a helmet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 헬멧을 써야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must wear a helmet.",
      "Scrambled": "wear / helmet / a / You / must"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 규칙을 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 규칙을 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must follow the rules.",
      "Scrambled": "follow the rules"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 규칙을 따라야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must follow the rules.",
      "Scrambled": "must / rules / follow / the / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 네 손을 씻어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 네 손을 씻어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must wash your hands first.",
      "Scrambled": "wash your hands first"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 네 손을 씻어야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must wash your hands first.",
      "Scrambled": "wash / first / must / hands / your / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 지금 당장 119에 전화해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 지금 당장 119에 전화해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must call 119 right now.",
      "Scrambled": "call 119 right now"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 지금 당장 119에 전화해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must call 119 right now.",
      "Scrambled": "now / call / right / 119 / must / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음식을 낭비해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음식을 낭비해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not waste food.",
      "Scrambled": "not waste food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 음식을 낭비해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not waste food.",
      "Scrambled": "must / waste / not / You / food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 숲에서 요리해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 숲에서 요리해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not cook in the forest.",
      "Scrambled": "not cook in the forest"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 숲에서 요리해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not cook in the forest.",
      "Scrambled": "must / forest / the / in / not / cook / You"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 조용히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 조용히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must be quiet.",
      "Scrambled": "be quiet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 조용히 해야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must be quiet.",
      "Scrambled": "be / must / You / quiet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거짓말을 해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거짓말을 해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not tell a lie.",
      "Scrambled": "not tell a lie"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거짓말을 해서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not tell a lie.",
      "Scrambled": "You / tell / not / lie / must / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 휴대 전화를 꺼야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 휴대 전화를 꺼야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must turn off your cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "turn off your cell phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 휴대 전화를 꺼야 해.",
      "English/Answer": "You must turn off your cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "turn / must / your / You / phone / off / cell"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업 중에 간식을 먹어서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업 중에 간식을 먹어서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not eat snacks during class.",
      "Scrambled": "not eat snacks during class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 29,
      "Pattern Name": "You must ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 수업 중에 간식을 먹어서는 안 돼.",
      "English/Answer": "You must not eat snacks during class.",
      "Scrambled": "during / not / must / You / class / eat / snacks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 목록을 작성해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 목록을 작성해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should make a list.",
      "Scrambled": "make a list"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 목록을 작성해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should make a list.",
      "Scrambled": "list / make / you / I / should / think / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에게 사실을 말해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에게 사실을 말해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should tell him the truth.",
      "Scrambled": "tell him the truth"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그에게 사실을 말해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should tell him the truth.",
      "Scrambled": "think / him / tell / the / truth / you / should / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 줄넘기를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 줄넘기를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should jump rope every day.",
      "Scrambled": "jump rope every day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 줄넘기를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should jump rope every day.",
      "Scrambled": "you / day / think / every / jump / I / rope / should"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 균형 잡힌 식사를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 균형 잡힌 식사를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should have a balanced diet.",
      "Scrambled": "have a balanced diet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 균형 잡힌 식사를 해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should have a balanced diet.",
      "Scrambled": "you / a / diet / have / think / I / should / balanced"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 분실물 보관소를 확인해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 분실물 보관소를 확인해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should check the lost and found.",
      "Scrambled": "check the lost and found"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 분실물 보관소를 확인해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should check the lost and found.",
      "Scrambled": "found / and / I / should / lost / you / think / the / check"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 따뜻한 물을 많이 마셔야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 따뜻한 물을 많이 마셔야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should drink lots of hot water.",
      "Scrambled": "drink lots of hot water"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 따뜻한 물을 많이 마셔야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should drink lots of hot water.",
      "Scrambled": "drink / you / hot / of / should / water / think / lots / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 경찰에 알려야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 경찰에 알려야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should report it to the police.",
      "Scrambled": "report it to the police"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그것을 경찰에 알려야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should report it to the police.",
      "Scrambled": "to / should / you / it / police / I / report / think / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 문제를 다시 검토해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 문제를 다시 검토해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should review the problem again.",
      "Scrambled": "review the problem again"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그 문제를 다시 검토해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should review the problem again.",
      "Scrambled": "again / you / think / problem / should / review / I / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 안경을 써야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 안경을 써야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should wear glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "wear glasses"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 안경을 써야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should wear glasses.",
      "Scrambled": "you / glasses / think / wear / should / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 먹지 말아야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 먹지 말아야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should not eat at night.",
      "Scrambled": "not eat at night"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 먹지 말아야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should not eat at night.",
      "Scrambled": "eat / night / I / think / at / should / not / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임을 제한해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임을 제한해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should limit computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "limit computer games"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 컴퓨터 게임을 제한해야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should limit computer games.",
      "Scrambled": "think / computer / should / limit / games / you / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 점심 도시락을 가져가야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 점심 도시락을 가져가야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should take your lunch box.",
      "Scrambled": "take your lunch box"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 30,
      "Pattern Name": "I think you should ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 네 점심 도시락을 가져가야 할 것 같아.",
      "English/Answer": "I think you should take your lunch box.",
      "Scrambled": "think / your / I / should / lunch / take / you / box"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better exercise daily.",
      "Scrambled": "exercise daily"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 매일 운동하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better exercise daily.",
      "Scrambled": "better / exercise / You'd / daily"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우산을 가져가는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우산을 가져가는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better take an umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "take an umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 우산을 가져가는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better take an umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "better / umbrella / an / take / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그냥 자는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그냥 자는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better just go to bed.",
      "Scrambled": "just go to bed"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 그냥 자는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better just go to bed.",
      "Scrambled": "go / to / better / just / bed / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 선생님 말씀을 듣는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 선생님 말씀을 듣는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better listen to your teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "listen to your teacher"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 선생님 말씀을 듣는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better listen to your teacher.",
      "Scrambled": "better / teacher / to / listen / You'd / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 숙제를 하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 숙제를 하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better do your homework first.",
      "Scrambled": "do your homework first"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 먼저 숙제를 하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better do your homework first.",
      "Scrambled": "homework / better / do / first / your / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 10시까지 집에 오는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 10시까지 집에 오는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better come home by 10 p.m.",
      "Scrambled": "come home by 10 p.m."
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 오후 10시까지 집에 오는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better come home by 10 p.m.",
      "Scrambled": "better / home / You'd / p.m. / by / 10 / come"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 비닐봉지를 쓰지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 비닐봉지를 쓰지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not use plastic bags.",
      "Scrambled": "not use plastic bags"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 비닐봉지를 쓰지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not use plastic bags.",
      "Scrambled": "not / use / bags / You'd / plastic / better"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너무 많은 음식을 먹지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너무 많은 음식을 먹지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not eat too much food.",
      "Scrambled": "not eat too much food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 너무 많은 음식을 먹지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not eat too much food.",
      "Scrambled": "not / food / better / eat / You'd / too / much"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 예의를 갖추는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 예의를 갖추는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better be polite.",
      "Scrambled": "be polite"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 예의를 갖추는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better be polite.",
      "Scrambled": "polite / You'd / better / be"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다시 늦지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다시 늦지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not be late again.",
      "Scrambled": "not be late again"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 다시 늦지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not be late again.",
      "Scrambled": "better / again / late / be / not / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 말하기 전에 생각하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 말하기 전에 생각하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better think before you speak.",
      "Scrambled": "think before you speak"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 말하기 전에 생각하는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better think before you speak.",
      "Scrambled": "better / speak / think / before / you / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 걷지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 걷지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not walk at night.",
      "Scrambled": "not walk at night"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 31,
      "Pattern Name": "You'd better ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 밤에 걷지 않는 게 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "You'd better not walk at night.",
      "Scrambled": "at / not / night / walk / better / You'd"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여기서 기다려야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여기서 기다려야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to wait here?",
      "Scrambled": "wait here"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 여기서 기다려야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to wait here?",
      "Scrambled": "here / I / to / need / wait / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to stay at home?",
      "Scrambled": "stay at home"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 집에 있어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to stay at home?",
      "Scrambled": "home / stay / I / at / need / Do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 신발을 벗어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 신발을 벗어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to take off my shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "take off my shoes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 신발을 벗어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to take off my shoes?",
      "Scrambled": "off / shoes / take / need / Do / my / I / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨간 신호에 멈춰야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨간 신호에 멈춰야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to stop at the red sign?",
      "Scrambled": "stop at the red sign"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 빨간 신호에 멈춰야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to stop at the red sign?",
      "Scrambled": "need / the / stop / I / red / sign / at / to / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 표를 사기 위해 줄을 서야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 표를 사기 위해 줄을 서야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to line up to buy a ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "line up to buy a ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 표를 사기 위해 줄을 서야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to line up to buy a ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "line / I / ticket / buy / to / a / need / to / up / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 소유의 스노보드를 가져와야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 소유의 스노보드를 가져와야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to bring my own snowboard?",
      "Scrambled": "bring my own snowboard"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 내 소유의 스노보드를 가져와야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to bring my own snowboard?",
      "Scrambled": "snowboard / my / need / bring / to / own / Do / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 돈을 갚아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 돈을 갚아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to pay back the money?",
      "Scrambled": "pay back the money"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 그 돈을 갚아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to pay back the money?",
      "Scrambled": "pay / Do / need / to / I / back / money / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식후에 약을 먹어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식후에 약을 먹어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to take the medicine after meals?",
      "Scrambled": "take the medicine after meals"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 식후에 약을 먹어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to take the medicine after meals?",
      "Scrambled": "medicine / I / to / take / after / the / meals / need / Do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매일 연습해야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매일 연습해야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to practice every day?",
      "Scrambled": "practice every day"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 매일 연습해야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to practice every day?",
      "Scrambled": "to / need / Do / day / practice / I / every"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 은행에 가야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 은행에 가야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to go to the bank?",
      "Scrambled": "go to the bank"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 은행에 가야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to go to the bank?",
      "Scrambled": "need / bank / the / to / go / I / Do / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 경기하는 법을 알아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 경기하는 법을 알아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to know how to play?",
      "Scrambled": "know how to play"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 경기하는 법을 알아야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to know how to play?",
      "Scrambled": "play / know / I / how / Do / to / need / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오른쪽으로 걸어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오른쪽으로 걸어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to walk on the right side?",
      "Scrambled": "walk on the right side"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 32,
      "Pattern Name": "Do I need to ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 오른쪽으로 걸어야 하니?",
      "English/Answer": "Do I need to walk on the right side?",
      "Scrambled": "the / walk / I / side / Do / need / right / on / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 설거지 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 설거지 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with the dishes?",
      "Scrambled": "with the dishes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내 설거지 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with the dishes?",
      "Scrambled": "me / help / you / Can / with / dishes / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 문제 푸는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 문제 푸는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me solve this problem?",
      "Scrambled": "solve this problem"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 문제 푸는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me solve this problem?",
      "Scrambled": "problem / help / me / you / Can / solve / this"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 가방들 나르는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 가방들 나르는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me carry these bags?",
      "Scrambled": "carry these bags"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 가방들 나르는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me carry these bags?",
      "Scrambled": "bags / help / you / Can / me / these / carry"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 쓰레기 버리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 쓰레기 버리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me throw away the trash?",
      "Scrambled": "throw away the trash"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 쓰레기 버리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me throw away the trash?",
      "Scrambled": "throw / help / away / me / Can / you / trash / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 이미지 내려받는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 이미지 내려받는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me download this image?",
      "Scrambled": "download this image"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 이미지 내려받는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me download this image?",
      "Scrambled": "this / help / download / me / image / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with my homework?",
      "Scrambled": "with my homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with my homework?",
      "Scrambled": "help / homework / with / you / me / my / Can"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가방 찾는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가방 찾는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me find my bag?",
      "Scrambled": "find my bag"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가방 찾는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me find my bag?",
      "Scrambled": "find / help / bag / me / my / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 옷 거는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 옷 거는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me hang up the clothes?",
      "Scrambled": "hang up the clothes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 옷 거는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me hang up the clothes?",
      "Scrambled": "hang / clothes / help / me / you / up / Can / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 연설하는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 연설하는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with my speech?",
      "Scrambled": "with my speech"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 연설하는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me with my speech?",
      "Scrambled": "Can / with / help / you / speech / me / my"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 상 차리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 상 차리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me set the table?",
      "Scrambled": "set the table"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 상 차리는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me set the table?",
      "Scrambled": "me / help / you / table / Can / set / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 개 씻기는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 개 씻기는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me wash my dog?",
      "Scrambled": "wash my dog"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 개 씻기는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me wash my dog?",
      "Scrambled": "wash / me / you / Can / dog / help / my"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 병을 여는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 병을 여는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me open this jar?",
      "Scrambled": "open this jar"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 33,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you help me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 이 병을 여는 것 좀 도와줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you help me open this jar?",
      "Scrambled": "help / me / this / open / jar / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이유를 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이유를 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the reason?",
      "Scrambled": "the reason"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "이유를 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the reason?",
      "Scrambled": "me / tell / Can / the / you / reason"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘의 일정을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘의 일정을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me today's schedule?",
      "Scrambled": "today's schedule"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "오늘의 일정을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me today's schedule?",
      "Scrambled": "me / you / today's / Can / tell / schedule"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "스티브 잡스에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "스티브 잡스에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about Steve Jobs?",
      "Scrambled": "about Steve Jobs"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "스티브 잡스에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about Steve Jobs?",
      "Scrambled": "me / Jobs / Steve / about / Can / tell / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "현대 미술에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "현대 미술에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about modern art?",
      "Scrambled": "about modern art"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "현대 미술에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about modern art?",
      "Scrambled": "me / art / tell / you / Can / about / modern"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "지구를 지키는 방법들에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "지구를 지키는 방법들에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about ways to save the earth?",
      "Scrambled": "about ways to save the earth"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "지구를 지키는 방법들에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about ways to save the earth?",
      "Scrambled": "save / about / earth / ways / to / you / tell / me / Can / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "요리법을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "요리법을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the recipe?",
      "Scrambled": "the recipe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "요리법을 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the recipe?",
      "Scrambled": "me / recipe / you / Can / tell / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우주에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우주에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about the universe?",
      "Scrambled": "about the universe"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "우주에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about the universe?",
      "Scrambled": "universe / the / about / Can / me / you / tell"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "식량 은행에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "식량 은행에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about food banks?",
      "Scrambled": "about food banks"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "식량 은행에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about food banks?",
      "Scrambled": "about / tell / you / food / Can / banks / me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "시간에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "시간에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the time?",
      "Scrambled": "the time"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "시간에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the time?",
      "Scrambled": "me / time / the / tell / Can / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about it?",
      "Scrambled": "about it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "그것에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about it?",
      "Scrambled": "you / it / about / me / Can / tell"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 계획에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 계획에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about your plans?",
      "Scrambled": "about your plans"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "네 계획에 대해 내게 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me about your plans?",
      "Scrambled": "plans / tell / Can / about / you / me / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓의 가격을 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓의 가격을 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the price of this ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "the price of this ticket"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 34,
      "Pattern Name": "Can you tell me ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "이 티켓의 가격을 말해 줄래?",
      "English/Answer": "Can you tell me the price of this ticket?",
      "Scrambled": "of / tell / ticket / this / me / Can / price / you / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 제주도에 간 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 제주도에 간 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never been to Jeju-do.",
      "Scrambled": "been to Jeju-do"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 제주도에 간 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never been to Jeju-do.",
      "Scrambled": "I've / been / Jeju-do / never / to"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 케밥을 먹은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 케밥을 먹은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never eaten kebab.",
      "Scrambled": "eaten kebab"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 케밥을 먹은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never eaten kebab.",
      "Scrambled": "I've / never / kebab / eaten"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 노인을 만난 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 노인을 만난 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never met the old man.",
      "Scrambled": "met the old man"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 노인을 만난 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never met the old man.",
      "Scrambled": "man / old / met / I've / never / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 별똥별을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 별똥별을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never seen a shooting star.",
      "Scrambled": "seen a shooting star"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 별똥별을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never seen a shooting star.",
      "Scrambled": "seen / shooting / I've / star / a / never"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 롤러코스터를 탄 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 롤러코스터를 탄 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never ridden a roller coaster.",
      "Scrambled": "ridden a roller coaster"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 롤러코스터를 탄 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never ridden a roller coaster.",
      "Scrambled": "roller / a / ridden / I've / coaster / never"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 태국 음식을 먹어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 태국 음식을 먹어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never tried Thai food.",
      "Scrambled": "tried Thai food"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 태국 음식을 먹어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never tried Thai food.",
      "Scrambled": "I've / tried / food / never / Thai"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 한국 드라마를 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 한국 드라마를 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never watched a Korean drama.",
      "Scrambled": "watched a Korean drama"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 한국 드라마를 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never watched a Korean drama.",
      "Scrambled": "drama / I've / watched / Korean / a / never"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 사고에 대해 들은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 사고에 대해 들은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never heard about the accident.",
      "Scrambled": "heard about the accident"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그 사고에 대해 들은 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never heard about the accident.",
      "Scrambled": "heard / never / I've / accident / about / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 애완동물을 키워본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 애완동물을 키워본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never had a pet.",
      "Scrambled": "had a pet"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 애완동물을 키워본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never had a pet.",
      "Scrambled": "pet / had / never / a / I've"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그것들을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그것들을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never seen it.",
      "Scrambled": "seen it"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 그것들을 본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never seen it.",
      "Scrambled": "never / seen / it / I've"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 봉사 활동을 해본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 봉사 활동을 해본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never done volunteer work.",
      "Scrambled": "done volunteer work"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 봉사 활동을 해본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never done volunteer work.",
      "Scrambled": "done / never / I've / volunteer / work"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 알라딘에 관한 이야기를 읽어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 알라딘에 관한 이야기를 읽어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never read a story about Aladdin.",
      "Scrambled": "read a story about Aladdin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 35,
      "Pattern Name": "I've never ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 한 번도 알라딘에 관한 이야기를 읽어본 적이 없어.",
      "English/Answer": "I've never read a story about Aladdin.",
      "Scrambled": "about / never / Aladdin / read / I've / story / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "Have you ever done it?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 김치를 먹어본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever tried kimchi?",
      "Scrambled": "tried kimchi"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 김치를 먹어 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever tried kimchi?",
      "Scrambled": "tried / kimchi / Have / ever / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 펭귄을 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 펭귄을 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever seen a penguin?",
      "Scrambled": "seen a penguin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 펭귄을 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever seen a penguin?",
      "Scrambled": "seen / Have / a / ever / you / penguin"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤 수업을 받아본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤 수업을 받아본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever taken a dance class?",
      "Scrambled": "taken a dance class"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 춤 수업을 받아본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever taken a dance class?",
      "Scrambled": "dance / taken / class / ever / a / Have / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 디즈니랜드에 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 디즈니랜드에 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever been to Disneyland?",
      "Scrambled": "been to Disneyland"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 디즈니랜드에 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever been to Disneyland?",
      "Scrambled": "been / Have / you / to / ever / Disneyland"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 텐트를 쳐 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 텐트를 쳐 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever put up a tent?",
      "Scrambled": "put up a tent"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 텐트를 쳐 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever put up a tent?",
      "Scrambled": "up / you / Have / ever / put / tent / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 샘의 엄마를 만나 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 샘의 엄마를 만나 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever met Sam's mother?",
      "Scrambled": "met Sam's mother"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 샘의 엄마를 만나 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever met Sam's mother?",
      "Scrambled": "met / ever / Sam's / mother / you / Have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토끼에게 먹이를 줘 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토끼에게 먹이를 줘 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever fed a rabbit?",
      "Scrambled": "fed a rabbit"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 토끼에게 먹이를 줘 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever fed a rabbit?",
      "Scrambled": "Have / rabbit / fed / a / ever / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요가를 해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요가를 해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever done yoga?",
      "Scrambled": "done yoga"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 요가를 해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever done yoga?",
      "Scrambled": "yoga / done / you / Have / ever"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 캠핑을 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 캠핑을 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever gone camping?",
      "Scrambled": "gone camping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 캠핑을 가 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever gone camping?",
      "Scrambled": "gone / ever / Have / you / camping"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 부모님을 위해 요리해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 부모님을 위해 요리해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever cooked for your parents?",
      "Scrambled": "cooked for your parents"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 부모님을 위해 요리해 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever cooked for your parents?",
      "Scrambled": "for / parents / your / Have / you / ever / cooked"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해리포터 시리즈를 읽어 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해리포터 시리즈를 읽어 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever read the Harry Potter series?",
      "Scrambled": "read the Harry Potter series"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 해리포터 시리즈를 읽어 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever read the Harry Potter series?",
      "Scrambled": "series / Harry / read / ever / Potter / you / the / Have"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거리에서 돈을 주워 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거리에서 돈을 주워 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever found money on the street?",
      "Scrambled": "found money on the street"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 36,
      "Pattern Name": "Have you ever ...?",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "넌 거리에서 돈을 주워 본 적이 있니?",
      "English/Answer": "Have you ever found money on the street?",
      "Scrambled": "found / street / the / money / ever / you / Have / on"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 튼튼해질 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 튼튼해질 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could be strong.",
      "Scrambled": "be strong"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "난 튼튼해질 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could be strong.",
      "Scrambled": "strong / could / wish / be / I / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤을 잘 출 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤을 잘 출 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could dance well.",
      "Scrambled": "dance well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "난 춤을 잘 출 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could dance well.",
      "Scrambled": "dance / wish / well / I / I / could"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 대통령이 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 대통령이 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could become president.",
      "Scrambled": "become president"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "난 대통령이 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could become president.",
      "Scrambled": "president / become / wish / I / I / could"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전 세계를 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전 세계를 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could travel all over the world.",
      "Scrambled": "travel all over the world"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "난 전 세계를 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could travel all over the world.",
      "Scrambled": "over / travel / all / could / world / I / the / I / wish"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 시험에서 A를 받을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 시험에서 A를 받을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could get an A on the English test.",
      "Scrambled": "get an A on the English test"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어 시험에서 A를 받을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could get an A on the English test.",
      "Scrambled": "get / wish / A / English / on / an / I / the / test / I / could"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고양이를 키울 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고양이를 키울 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could raise a cat.",
      "Scrambled": "raise a cat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "난 고양이를 키울 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could raise a cat.",
      "Scrambled": "raise / I / I / wish / a / cat / could"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 오래 머물 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 오래 머물 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could stay longer.",
      "Scrambled": "stay longer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 오래 머물 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could stay longer.",
      "Scrambled": "wish / longer / stay / could / I / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 우주로 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 우주로 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could travel to space someday.",
      "Scrambled": "travel to space someday"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "난 언젠가 우주로 여행할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could travel to space someday.",
      "Scrambled": "someday / space / could / wish / I / to / travel / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 가수가 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 가수가 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could be a singer.",
      "Scrambled": "be a singer"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "난 가수가 될 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could be a singer.",
      "Scrambled": "could / singer / a / wish / be / I / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 많은 친구가 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 많은 친구가 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could have more friends.",
      "Scrambled": "have more friends"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "난 더 많은 친구가 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could have more friends.",
      "Scrambled": "friends / I / have / I / could / wish / more"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 달 위를 걸을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 달 위를 걸을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could walk on the moon.",
      "Scrambled": "walk on the moon"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "난 달 위를 걸을 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could walk on the moon.",
      "Scrambled": "could / wish / I / moon / walk / I / on / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 잘 말할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 잘 말할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could speak English well.",
      "Scrambled": "speak English well"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 37,
      "Pattern Name": "I wish I could ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "난 영어를 잘 말할 수 있으면 좋겠어.",
      "English/Answer": "I wish I could speak English well.",
      "Scrambled": "speak / wish / English / well / could / I / I"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "선물 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "선물 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the gift.",
      "Scrambled": "the gift"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "선물 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the gift.",
      "Scrambled": "you / gift / Thank / for / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "자리 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "자리 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the seat.",
      "Scrambled": "the seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "자리 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the seat.",
      "Scrambled": "for / Thank / the / you / seat"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너의 조언 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너의 조언 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for your advice.",
      "Scrambled": "your advice"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "너의 조언 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for your advice.",
      "Scrambled": "advice / Thank / for / your / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리를 초대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리를 초대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for inviting us.",
      "Scrambled": "inviting us"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "우리를 초대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for inviting us.",
      "Scrambled": "inviting / Thank / you / us / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제를 도와줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제를 도와줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for helping me with my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "helping me with my homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내 숙제를 도와줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for helping me with my homework.",
      "Scrambled": "with / you / for / me / helping / Thank / my / homework"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "책 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "책 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the book.",
      "Scrambled": "the book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "책 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for the book.",
      "Scrambled": "Thank / book / for / the / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "와 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "와 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for coming.",
      "Scrambled": "coming"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "와 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for coming.",
      "Scrambled": "coming / Thank / you / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저를 학교까지 태워 주셔서 고맙습니다.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저를 학교까지 태워 주셔서 고맙습니다.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for giving me a ride to school.",
      "Scrambled": "giving me a ride to school"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "저를 학교까지 태워 주셔서 고맙습니다.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for giving me a ride to school.",
      "Scrambled": "you / to / ride / giving / school / Thank / for / a / me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저녁 식사 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저녁 식사 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "dinner"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "저녁 식사 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for dinner.",
      "Scrambled": "for / you / dinner / Thank"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "친절하게 대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "친절하게 대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for your kindness.",
      "Scrambled": "your kindness"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "친절하게 대해 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for your kindness.",
      "Scrambled": "kindness / for / you / Thank / your"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 돌봐 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 돌봐 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for taking care of me.",
      "Scrambled": "taking care of me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "나를 돌봐 줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for taking care of me.",
      "Scrambled": "me / you / care / Thank / for / taking / of"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "네 휴대전화를 빌려줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "네 휴대전화를 빌려줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for lending me your cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "lending me your cell phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 38,
      "Pattern Name": "Thank you for ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "네 휴대전화를 빌려줘서 고마워.",
      "English/Answer": "Thank you for lending me your cell phone.",
      "Scrambled": "you / your / lending / cell / me / phone / Thank / for"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 문을 잠그도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 문을 잠그도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to lock the door.",
      "Scrambled": "lock the door"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 문을 잠그도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to lock the door.",
      "Scrambled": "sure / door / to / lock / Make / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 TV 소리를 줄이도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 TV 소리를 줄이도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to turn down the TV.",
      "Scrambled": "turn down the TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 TV 소리를 줄이도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to turn down the TV.",
      "Scrambled": "to / Make / down / turn / sure / the / TV"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 선크림을 바르도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 선크림을 바르도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you put on sunscreen.",
      "Scrambled": "put on sunscreen"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 선크림을 바르도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you put on sunscreen.",
      "Scrambled": "on / sunscreen / you / put / Make / sure"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 너무 늦지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 너무 늦지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you're not too late.",
      "Scrambled": "you're not too late"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 너무 늦지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you're not too late.",
      "Scrambled": "you're / not / sure / late / too / Make"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 네 우산을 잊지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 네 우산을 잊지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't forget your umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "don't forget your umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 네 우산을 잊지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't forget your umbrella.",
      "Scrambled": "your / Make / sure / forget / you / don't / umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 네 교통 카드를 가져오도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 네 교통 카드를 가져오도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to bring your transportation card.",
      "Scrambled": "bring your transportation card"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 네 교통 카드를 가져오도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to bring your transportation card.",
      "Scrambled": "your / Make / to / sure / bring / transportation / card"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 내일까지 그 책들을 반납하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 내일까지 그 책들을 반납하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you return the books by tomorrow.",
      "Scrambled": "return the books by tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 내일까지 그 책들을 반납하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you return the books by tomorrow.",
      "Scrambled": "you / by / books / sure / return / Make / the / tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 서로 다투지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 서로 다투지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't argue with each other.",
      "Scrambled": "don't argue with each other"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 서로 다투지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't argue with each other.",
      "Scrambled": "argue / Make / you / each / sure / don't / with / other"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 따뜻한 옷을 입도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 따뜻한 옷을 입도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to wear warm clothes.",
      "Scrambled": "wear warm clothes"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 따뜻한 옷을 입도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to wear warm clothes.",
      "Scrambled": "warm / Make / clothes / to / sure / wear"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 나에게 다시 전화하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 나에게 다시 전화하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you call me back.",
      "Scrambled": "call me back"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 나에게 다시 전화하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you call me back.",
      "Scrambled": "Make / me / back / call / sure / you"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 똑같은 실수를 하지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 똑같은 실수를 하지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't make the same mistake.",
      "Scrambled": "don't make the same mistake"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "절대 똑같은 실수를 하지 않도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure you don't make the same mistake.",
      "Scrambled": "don't / you / Make / sure / mistake / same / the / make"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 케이크를 시원하게 보관하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 케이크를 시원하게 보관하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to keep the cake cool.",
      "Scrambled": "keep the cake cool"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 39,
      "Pattern Name": "Make sure ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "꼭 케이크를 시원하게 보관하도록 해.",
      "English/Answer": "Make sure to keep the cake cool.",
      "Scrambled": "cake / Make / keep / cool / sure / to / the"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 생각해 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 생각해 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me think.",
      "Scrambled": "think"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 1,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 생각해 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me think.",
      "Scrambled": "think / Let / me"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 하나 보여 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 하나 보여 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me show you one.",
      "Scrambled": "show you one"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 2,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 하나 보여 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me show you one.",
      "Scrambled": "you / me / Let / one / show"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 책을 읽어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 책을 읽어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me read you a book.",
      "Scrambled": "read you a book"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 3,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 책을 읽어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me read you a book.",
      "Scrambled": "you / Let / read / me / book / a"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화를 사용할게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화를 사용할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me use your phone.",
      "Scrambled": "use your phone"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 4,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 전화를 사용할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me use your phone.",
      "Scrambled": "your / phone / Let / me / use"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 내 친구에 대해 말할게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 내 친구에 대해 말할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me tell you about my friend.",
      "Scrambled": "tell you about my friend"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 5,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 내 친구에 대해 말할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me tell you about my friend.",
      "Scrambled": "about / tell / me / Let / you / friend / my"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너의 자전거를 탈게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너의 자전거를 탈게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me ride your bicycle.",
      "Scrambled": "ride your bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 6,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너의 자전거를 탈게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me ride your bicycle.",
      "Scrambled": "Let / your / bicycle / me / ride"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 질문을 좀 할게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 질문을 좀 할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me ask you some questions.",
      "Scrambled": "ask you some questions"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 7,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너에게 질문을 좀 할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me ask you some questions.",
      "Scrambled": "you / me / Let / ask / questions / some"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 먼저 내 재킷을 가져올게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 먼저 내 재킷을 가져올게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me get my jacket first.",
      "Scrambled": "get my jacket first"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 8,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 먼저 내 재킷을 가져올게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me get my jacket first.",
      "Scrambled": "my / me / get / first / jacket / Let"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 맞춰 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 맞춰 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me guess.",
      "Scrambled": "guess"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 9,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 맞춰 볼게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me guess.",
      "Scrambled": "me / guess / Let"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 사진을 찍어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 사진을 찍어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me take your picture.",
      "Scrambled": "take your picture"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 10,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 네 사진을 찍어 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me take your picture.",
      "Scrambled": "Let / take / your / me / picture"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가족을 소개할게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가족을 소개할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me introduce my family.",
      "Scrambled": "introduce my family"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 11,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 내 가족을 소개할게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me introduce my family.",
      "Scrambled": "family / me / my / introduce / Let"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking I",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 안아 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "",
      "Scrambled": ""
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Speaking II",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 안아 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me give you a hug.",
      "Scrambled": "give you a hug"
    },
    {
      "Pattern #": 40,
      "Pattern Name": "Let me ....",
      "Section": "Unscramble",
      "Question #": 12,
      "Korean/Question": "내가 너를 안아 줄게.",
      "English/Answer": "Let me give you a hug.",
      "Scrambled": "give / hug / you / me / Let / a"
    }
  ]
};